What's up guys, bueng What's up man, what's up
Qué pasa chavales bueng Qué tal hombre
man What are you doing, what do you
qué tal hombre Qué hacéis qué os
tell each other so little What does my ricki say How are we?
contáis poco Qué dice mi ricki Cómo
I'm fine and you How's very fine, the
estamos Yo bien y tú Qué mu bien la
truth is, cool, what does he tell you so
verdad fresquito qué te
little, I'm telling you I came up
cuenta poco poco yo te digo he subido
because a lady was calling me
porque estaba una señora llamándome
names and in the end we put the whole
cosas y al final hemos puesto la de tod
Yeah, that's what they told me that you've been
Sí eso me han dicho que has estado
insulting an older person No yes, the one who
insultando a una persona mayor No sí la
said she wants to
que ha dicho que quiere tritur arme que
crush me, she wants to crush me yes, she's
quiere triturar
been insulting me on
sí hacerme papilla me estado insultando
so many occasions before I came in Are you
en Sas ocasiones antes de que yo entrara
going to put a restraining order on
le vas a poner una orden de alejamiento
the lady too?
también a la
No, but it's disrespectful to women
no pero sea la falta respeto a la mujer
Yeah, just like Yai, the same as Yai What did she
Sí igual que yai lo mismo que yai Qué te
tell you, she wants to, well, she wants to
ha dicho que quiere bueno que me quiere
kill me, she wants to give me a degree Javi I know
matar que me quiere titular Javi Yo sé
that you don't think that's bad when
que a ti eso no te parece mal cuando lo
your owner does it But an older lady is
hace tu dueño Pero una señora mayor a mí
n't going to tell me that, you'll understand, no, no, no, I don't
no me va a decir eso tú comprenderás no
have a [ __ ] idea, eh, I
que va que va no tengo ni [__] idea eh
'm asking you I come from
os estoy preguntando Yo vengo de
telesalseo I mean, no, I didn't find out And
telesalseo O sea no no me he enterado Y
what's up tonight, eh  pipi Estrada
qué habido esta noche eh pipi Estrada
we've had pipi Estrada messing things up real
hemos tenido a pipi Estrada liándola
good, big
bien
pipi from that era br now let's
tocho sea pipi de la época br ahora ya a
see things are calm but well
ver está tranquilita la cosa pero bueno
listen to me then the lady has disrespected you
escúchame entonces la señora te ha falta
and you disrespected her or rather mutually yes it has
respeto y tú a ella o sea mutuamente sí
been a reciprocal and very
ha sido una cosa recíproca y muy
romantic thing if you ask me Oh but what
romántica si me preguntas Ah pero de qué
have you discussed well about her three
habéis debatido bueno de sus tres
husbands No it wasn't a debate actually
maridos No no ha sido debate en realidad
she started calling me everything she's
ella me ha empezado a llamar de todo ha
back like last time calling me a
vuelto como la última vez a llamarme
liar how about you little man and all
mentiroso qué tal poco hombre y todo
this and well I reminded her that she's at
esto y pues yo le he recordado que tiene
an age to rethink doing these
una edad para replantearse hacer estas
things she's at an age to call you a
cosas tiene una edad para llamarte
liar she's at an age to be in
mentiroso tiene una edad para estar en
a space with young kids calling
un space con chavalitos jóvenes llamando
people who make content on the
mentiroso a gente que hace contenido en
internet liars yes she has it Up to what age are you
internet s la tiene Hasta qué edad tú
too but yours isn't new eh
también pero lo tuyo no es nuevo eh
Up to what age can hom men I don't know
Hasta qué edad se puede hom men No lo sé
now leaving at 40 to go for a
ahora partir a los 40 para dar una
walk that's called ageism I mean
vuelta eso se llama edadismo O sea ya
something else new eh I mean part of the
otra cosa nueva eh o sea ya parte de la
xenophobia it was time damn ageism
xenofobia tocaba [__] el edadismo
too No man one more thing don't be like
también No hombre una cosa más no sea en
that  I know that social networks and
plan que yo sepas las redes sociales y
the media are for
los medios de comunicación son para todo
everyone, no, I mean, the usual gossip.
el mundo no o sea el salseo de toda la
Gossip and rumour have in
vida El salseo y los chismes han sido de
fact been for people older than
hecho para personas más mayores que que
young people, young people are
los jóvenes que los jóvenes estamos
now getting into gossip, it's okay,
ahora metiéndonos en el salseo est bien
talk. No, no, I'm not saying, let's go, I mean, I don't know. H.
habla No no digo yo vamos o sea no se H
No, yes, you're right. How come I don't agree with you,
No sí ti la razón Cómo no te I a dar la
man? At what age, more or less,
razón tío A qué a qué edad más o menos
can you stop consuming
se puede dejar de consumir
gossip? Stop consuming gossip when
salseo dejar de consumir salseo a la que
you get bored of those topics. I suppose not.
te aburran esos temas Supongo no cada
Everyone will have their own age. You said she was a
uno tendrá su edad la has dicho [__]
crazy [ __ ], the lady, and an old [ __ ] too, and an
loca la señora y [__] vieja también y
old [ __ ]. Yes, what time is it?
[__] vieja Sí qué tiempo es él mes
Last month when you criticised me for a
pasado cuando me criticaste por una
conviction for calling someone old,
condena por decirle vieja a alguien
eh, I understand that this is for tomorrow's video,
eh esto entiendo que es para el vídeo de
or when is this? This is
mañana o para cuándo es esto esto estoy
live, why already, but I'm saying the
en directo por qué ya pero digo los
excerpts, the cl, the ones I invented the
extractos los cl los que te inventé el
title for. And what title did I
título Y eso qué título me he
invent from the last space that a
inventado del último space que una
49-year-old lady ate me up?
señora de 49 años me papeo
Factor. Tell me that with you, you can't
factor dime eso con tuad no puedes
say it. Jai, you can't say it. Yes, I can.
decirlo Jai no puedes decir s si puedo
Look at Factor.  tell me another tell me another title
Mira factor dime otro dime otro título
fact is fact is left of Boomer is
fact es facto es quedado de Boomer es
facto factor not facto facto or facto
facto factor no facto facto o facto
according to and and the lie and the lie what
según y y la mentira y la mentira cuál
was in the
era en el
title that a 49 year old lady
título que una señora de 49 años
showed that she was not right in the head
demostró que no estaba bien de la cabeza
Ah and on top of that the psychiatrist But well
Ah que encima er psiquiatra Pero bueno
why was she not right in the
por qué no estaba bien de la
head I mean he called you a liar he called you a
cabeza o sea te ha dicho mentiroso te ha
liar he called me a liar he
mentiroso me ha dicho mentiroso me ha
told me that I lie about everything and every time I
dicho que miento en todo y cada vez que
asked him What he was telling me I don't know
le preguntaba En qué me decía no sé
you tell me and I said well look if he
dímelo tú y he dicho pues mira si me
's calling me a liar when I
está diciendo mentiroso cuando te
ask you do you want me to tell you what I'm lying about well
pregunto quieres que te diga yo en qué
then I start telling you
miento pues con empiezo yo a decirte
lies whatever that is that you came Yes yes
mentiras lo que sea eso has venido Sí sí
to get up esp a little bit you were
a levantar esp un poquito que estabais
already going around it Perfect
ya dándole vuelta mismo Perfecto me
seems fine to me but before that I'm going to answer
parece bien pero antes me va respondo
the little things man the first one is Yes yes what do you
las cosillas tío la primera es Sí sí qué
think about the hitman thing what's
opinas del tema de los sicario cuál es
your point eh huge historical nonsense and I do
tu punto eh payasada enorme histórica y
n't know what crazy [ __ ] you're making up it
no sé qué [__] locos estáis inventando
's a lie no like dasas he's never done
es mentira no en plan dasas no ha hecho
that until he told me  prove
eso nunca hasta que no me lo demuestres
the truth is that I don't believe it okay okay
la verdad es que no me lo creo vale vale
No but you take it as a lie you who are
No pero lo das por mentira tú que eres
his colleague you take it as a lie do you understand
su colega lo das por mentira entiendes
Spanish or now since you are in Andorra
el español o ahora como estás en andorra
No yes but since you are Andalusian Lu and you
No sí pero como eres andal Lu y lo
have it pronounced like that the accent
tienes así pronunciado el acento te
I ask you do you take it as a lie what
pregunto lo das por mentira lo que ha
he said eh For me coming from Delo
dicho él eh Para mí viniendo de delo
man imagine man okay okay
hombre imagínate hombre vale vale
coming from Delox or talking about Dallas
viniendo de delox o hablando de Dallas
what do you think is worse coming from
qué es lo que te parece peor viniendo de
Delox okay perfect Okay that's the answer
delox vale perfecto Ok esa la respuesta
that I wanted Cool secondly the subject that
que que quería Guay segundo el tema de
r's mother died in prison
que la madre de r falleció en la cárcel
What do you think of this discord eh if it's
Qué te ha parecio este discord eh si es
true lie I don't know but bringing in
verdad mentira no lo sé pero meter a las
mothers seems like an outrage to me
madres me parece una barbaridad el
Dallas's comment seems like an
comentario de Dallas me parece una
outrage to me bringing in mothers seems like an outrage to you
barbaridad meter a las madres te parece
bringing in mothers girlfriends cousins
una barbaridad a ti mete a las madres a
children
las novias a las primas a los hijos a
nephews I ask Met the mothers
los sobrinos pregunto Met a las madres
seems like an outrage to you Javi yes or no do you
te parece una barbaridad Javi sí o no te
think it's a nice comment Javi don't
parece a ti un comentario bonito Javi no
answer me with a question please  I'm
me respondas con una pregunta porf te lo
asking the mothers does it seem like
estoy preguntando a las madre te parece
a
una
barbarity to you I'm talking I'm
barbaridad estoy hablando Yo estoy
talking to me to the mothers does it seem like
hablando yo me a las madres te parece
a barbarity to you Ricky you've been with me for 5 minutes
una barbaridad Ricky llevas 5 minutos
Rick don't get nervous you've been with
conigo Rick no te pongas nervioso llevas
me for minutes and you're already nervous I
minutos conmigo y ya estás nervos he
came chill talk chill don't be but
venido chill habla chill no sea pero
answer
responder
questions ask about ethics no I'm not
preguntas pregun lo de la ética no no te
asking you Seriously it
pregunto En serio
seems like a creature Does it seem right to you jav I mentioned
parece criatura Te parece bien jav menci
the mothers no it doesn't seem right to me okay it
las madre no no me parece bien dicho
's funny that you say it you say it that's it
vale es curioso que lo digas tú lo digas
why Because I told you your
tú ya está por qué Porque te dije tu
mother shouldn't be proud of you when you've
madre no estar orgulloso de ti cuando tú
been through the whole [ __ ] eh fight we have
llevas toda la [__] eh pelea que tenemos
mentioning my family to your family what have I
mencionando a mi familia a tu familia qu
said about your family before you
he dicho de tu familia antes de que
mentioned my mother Yeah yeah before you
mencionaras a mi madre Sí sí antes de
mentioned my mother what said about
que mencionaras a mi madre que dicho de
your family dude Like man the only thing I
tu familia chul Cómo tío lo único que lo
said was once because your mother wouldn't
dije fue una vez por tu madre no se
feel proud what have I said about your
sentiría orgulloso qué he dicho de tu
family before mentioning that Ricki You
familia antes de mencionar eso ricki Tú
have the balls said Ricki you have
tienes los huev dicho ricki tú tienes
losi what have I said about your family if you're
losi qué he dicho de tu familia si me
going to interrupt me devil I silence you
vas a interrumpir [__] te silencio
but don't answer [ __ ] I respond but it's that I
pero no responde [__] respond pero es
'm answering you no  you leave me is that you have well after saying that
que te estoy respondiendo no me dejas es
when you go stop
que tien pues des dec eso cuando e vas
calm down you've been with me for 5 minutes
alto tranquilo llevas 5 minutos conmigo
Yeah don't get upset let me talk
Ja no te alteres que me dejes hablar
Ricky okay but relax a little
Ricky vale pero pero relaja un poquito
Damn but relax you've been here for 5 minutes
[__] pero relaja tú que llevas 5 minutos
Look you've been super chill when you've
Mira has estado super chill cuando has
been here with the kids I
estado aquí con los chavales estos te
feel you Superior and now with me You're already
siento Superior y ahora conmigo Ya estás
nervous with age Ah I V
con los nervios con la edad Ah me V
superior I dress superior talking to
superior me visto superior hablando con
them no no to you I think no thank you very much you've
ellos no no a ti cre no muchas gracias
only been believing yourself believing yourself
solamente has creyéndote creyéndote
superior in front of the kids with me
superior delante de los chavales conmigo
not believing me now you're the psychiatrist no no with
no creyéndome hora tú eres el psiquiatra
me No it
no no conmigo No a mí me comen los
pisses me off Ah well that's better for me better another
[__] Ah pues eso me mejor mejor otra
no Well what do you want me to V And
no Bueno qué quieres que te V Y
we start with your lies if it
empezamos con las mentiras tuyas si te
seems okay to you to mention mothers Ricky
parece bien mencionar a las madres Ricky
again yes yes again again I want to
otra vez sí sí otra ve otra vez quiero
hear it I loved it depends in
escucharlo me ha encantado depende En
what context Wait a moment now
qué contexto Espérate un momento ahora
okay depends in what context of
vale depende En qué contexto por
course if you're messing with a
supuesto si se estás metiendo con una
mother no Of course not Oh come on why did
madre no Claro que no Ay ent tú por qué
you mess with my mother at what point did I
te metiste con mi madre en qué momento
mess with  your mother Ricky at what
me metí con tu madre Ricky en qué
point have I messed with your family
momento he metido con tu familia antes
before you mentioned my mother in your
de que tú mencionaras a mi madre en tu
live show shamelessly don't answer
directo sin vergüenza no me respondas a
a question with another question Ah now I
una pregunta con otra pregunta Ah ahora
can't if you do it it's fine
no puedo yo si lo haces tú está bien
but if I do it it's wrong Oh we repeat
pero si lo hag yo está mal Ay repetimos
Javi we repeat at what point have I
Javi repetimos en qué momento me he
messed with your family before you
metido con tu familia antes de que tú
mention is my mother again Ricky
mencionas es a mi madre otra vez Ricky
tell me once tell me once Ricky
dime una vez dime una vez Ricky otra vez
tell me again one Ricky you haven't stopped
dime una Ricky tú no has parado de
mentioning the family the whole time you have
mencionar a la familia en todo el tiempo
n't stopped mentioning the family
no has parado de mencionar la familia
messing with her when have I messed
metido con ella cuánd me he metido yo
with your mother say that my mother isn't
con tu madre decí que mi madre no está
proud of me that messing with your mother
orgullosa de mí eso meterme con tu madre
is messing with you
es meterme contigo
clown Okay so when have I messed with your
payaso Vale entonces cuando me metido tu
family I haven't said that you
familia Yo no he dicho que te hayas
messed with my family I said that you don't
metido con mi familia he dicho que no
stop mentioning it said Ah and that
paras de mencionarla dicho Ah y te
bothers you and that's why he says that about meim
molesta eso y por eso dice lo de miim
yeah So what the [ __ ] criticize that
sí Entonces qué [__] critica que se
the family is insulted and that you mess with the
insulta la familia y que te metas con la
family Ricky what a loop no no but that
familia Ricky que bucle no no pero que
I don't mess with your family I
yo no me meto con tu familia te pedí
apologize for  mention your mother something that
perdón por mencionar a tu madre cosa que
you have not done with me that is a lie that
tú no has hecho conigo eso es mentira
is a lie Where is that that is to me you have me
eso es mentira Dónde está eso eso está a
added on discord and you have not
m me tienes en discord agregado y no me
sent me anything that is in public in
has mandado nada eso está en público en
a live here at the salsera Ah one of
un directo aquí en la salsería Ah de
those that everyone in my
estos que ve todo el mundo de mi
community sees of course that is why it has reached me
comunidad claro por eso me ha llegado
Of course of course to your community to your
Claro claro a tu comunidad a tu
community to your community I have to
comunidad a tu comunidad le tengo que
put little I so that they see my live streams
poner poco yo para que vean los directos
to my community no but at least he's
míos a mi comunidad no pero por lo menos
going to apologize to me be
va a disculparte conmigo ser
man enough to send it to
suficientemente hombre para enviármelo a
me uncle at least well to talk to
mí tío por lo menos buo para hablar con
a little boy I don't have to be a man
un niño pequeño no tengo que ser hombre
but ah not even to apologize for
pero ah ni para disculparse por
mentioning his mom no mu when I mention the
mencionar su mom no mu cuando mencion la
Excuse me don't mention you Ricky if you
Disculpa que no te menciones Ricky como
mention my children again I'm going to
vuelvas a mencionar a mis hijos voy a
dorre I'll knock your glasses off with a slap And
dorre te vuelvo la gafa de un guantazo Y
also I'm going Tom report Tom whatever
además que voy Tom denuncia Tom las que
comes out of your balls I'm
te salga de los [__] te lo estoy
telling you very seriously I'm going to fit in I'll grab the
diciendo muy en serio me encajo cojo el
[ __ ] right now and I'll slap you
cocho ahora mismo y te pego un bofetón
so I look at you how she has become look at her
que te mir có se ha puesto miralo
my mother well everything my mother well  but I'm
mi madre bien todo mi madre bien pero yo
yours I curse you because you're an
la tuya Yo me cago en ti que eres
idiot your poor mother isn't to
gilipolla tu madre la pobre no tiene
blame for anything if you mention
culpa de nada como vuelvas a mencionar a
the kids again I'll take the car I'll plant myself wherever you
los niños cojo el coche me planto donde
are and your glasses will fly off you're finding out I
estés y te vuelan las gafas te estás
have balls you want me to
enterando que tengo [__] quieres que
do it tomorrow you tomorrow ha I'll
lo haga mañana mismo tú maana ha me
plant myself wherever necessary for a cute
planto donde haga falta para un pintam
girl like you wherever necessary and I'll take
mona como tú donde haga falta y te cojo
you and five like you don't care you want me to
a ti y a cinco como tú te vale quieres
do it tomorrow What a good
que lo haga mañana mismo Qué buen
example of Father Javi The example of a
ejemplo de Padre Javi El ejemplo de
father that's going to open your head if you
padre que te va a abrir la cabeza como
keep saying things kids you're giving
sigas diciendo cosas hijos estás dando
man you're giving an example f the example you
tío está dando un eemplo f el ejemplo
're giving
que estás dando
t if they touch my dick and
t como me toquen la [__] y vuelvas a
mention a minor again example man I'd be
mencionar a menor ejemp tío me daría
ashamed I'd be ashamed I'd be
vergüenza me daría vergüenza me daría
ashamed I'd be
vergüenza me daría verguen me daría
ashamed if you mention minors again
vergüenza como vuelv a mencionar menores
well you're friends with someone well you're friends go on do
pues eres colega de uno pu eres colega
n't mention them it's the
de uno anda que no los mencion es la
last time Ricky that you do it have you made yourself
última vez Ricky que lo haces te ha
clear it's the last time you
quedado clarito es la última vez que lo
do it because I'll plant myself wherever the [ __ ] you are
haces porque me planto donde [__] estés
And if it's not in
Y si no es en
andor Calm down a little  Please calm down
andor Cálmate un poquito favor Cálmate
a little, he's going to leave you and
un poquito está Se te está yendo y
tomorrow he's going to tell me to my face
mañana te ti el me lo va decir la cara
because in my face then you put a
porque en la cara luego pones orden de
restraining order you coward you're a coward eh this
alejamiento [__] que eres un [__] eh
is the last time Ricky seen how he has him
es la última vez Ricky visto como lo
educated look we got it
tiene educado mira lo hemos conseguido
gentlemen we got it out have you seen how he has him
señores lo hemos sacado habis visto como
educated jav you want us to
lo tiene educado jav quieres que
talk about Why do you have That difference
hablemos de Por qué tien Esa diferencia
towards adas you want us to talk I
hacia adas quieres que hablemos quiero
want us to talk about what's up to me Ah you want us to
quieres que hablemos de lo que sabe
want us to talk about what he knows you want us to talk about what happens in
quieres que hablemos de lo que pasa en
your little house that you don't want it to be known
tu casita que no quieres que se sepa por
there first I'm going to ask you questions
allí primero te voy haido preguntas
okay You made up something Oh tomorrow I'll
vale Te inventaste invent Ay que mañana
take the car to a kilometer Ay Ay Ay
te c el coche a pill kilómetro Ay Ay Ay
if you want I told you that tomorrow
si quieres te he dicho que mañana mismo
I'll come and slap you eh No yes yes
voy y te pego un bofetón eh No sí sí
calm down yes it's recording differently
tranquilo si está grabando diferente
But if I'm telling you you
Pero si es que te lo estoy diciendo
want that you want that you
quieres que lo quieres que lo tte
also don't mind if I tell you the
también te te molesta que te diga la
truth Well the truth is that your
verdad Bueno pues la verdad es que a tu
mother should be ashamed of what you
madre le tiene que dar vergüenza tú lo
're doing on the internet yes
que estás haciendo en interet sí que a
my mother  you have to be ashamed and you say you have
mi madre tiene que vergüenza y a tu di
no reason to be ashamed you have no
no le tiene que vergüenza a tu no tiene
shame in what you do Take a
vergüenza lo que haces tú Date una
turn you want me to answer you because
vuelta quieres que te conteste porque
you are a liar or not come well that's how I like it That's how
eres un mentiroso o no venga pues así me
I like understanding the
gusta Así me gusta entendiendo los
ranges Javier understanding the ranges
rangos Javier entendiendo los rangos
but the range the range that you are that is no no
pero el rango el rango que tú estás eso
the range It's that you keep talking
es no no el rango Es que sigu la drando
while I profit from the [ __ ]
mientras yo me lucro de las [__]
who do live [ __ ] what are you
que hacen directo [__] de qué te
profiting from jon if you are alds imo you have
estás lucrando jón si estás aldís imo
become your when your account I will
has convertido tu cuando tu cuenta te
pass you the YouTube studio Come on and and you
paso el estudio de YouTube Vamos y y te
put it on I will pass you what he got from YouTube
pones te paso lo que me sacó de YouTube
talking about you from the owner and you come to my
hablando de ti del dueño y te pasas a mi
team quickly Javier you come to my
equipo rapidito Javier te pasas a mi
taking it quickly come on and I don't have to
levando rapidito vamos y yo no tengo que
extort with [ __ ] that I know about your
extorsionar con [__] que se de tu
private life and your intimacy for you to
vida privada y tu intimidad para que me
make videos for me please you have to
hagas vídeos favor t tú tienes que
intimidate girls to take the an
amedrentar a niñas para llevarte las an
Torres so that you Why don't you show it
Torres para que te Por qué no lo enseñas
cool Why don't you show it do you give me
chulo Por qué no lo enseñas me das
permission to put the
permiso para poner la captura de
screenshot on the live right now
pantalla en el directo ahora mismo de
what the screenshot of  what yours eh
qué la captura de qué tuya eh
intimidating a girl that you
amedrentando a una niña con que le
did a live broadcast on her if she didn't give you back the
hacías un directo si no te devolvía los
200 bucks if you're going to show the messages
200 pavos si vas a mostrar los mensaje
from both parties yeah of course Sure sure sure
de ambas partes sí supuesto Claro claro
of course Yes yes without any
claro por supuesto Sí sí sin ningún
problem Put whatever you want because
problema Pon lo que tú quieras por que
you want well let's put it How do
tú quieras pues vamos a ponerlo Cómo
you threaten a girl because that's what
amenazas tú a una niña porque es con las
you dare with one thing you how do you
que te atreves una una cosa tú cómo
define girl wh What age do you define
defines niña qu De qué edad defin las
girls I'm going to put the capture and now you
niñas Voy a poner la captura y ahora tú
answer me I don't say why at 30 years old
me respondes no digo porque con 30 años
you wanted to [ __ ] a person who is
quisiste follarte a una persona que
the age of what you're calling a
tiene la edad de lo quea estás llamando
girl then be careful yes be careful
niña entonces ten cuidado sí ten cuidado
because this is going to be heard later you
porque esto luego va a sonar por allí
know how
sabes
[ __ ] awesome how you've gotten my God
sarte [__] cómo te has puesto Dios mío
Tomorrow how is it It's not that my dick bothers me
Mañana cómo está No es que me sua la
when since two plus two
[__] cuando desde los de dos más dos
is two when they didn't get on your
son dos hace cuando no te sacaban de tus
nerves to not my nerves it's not that this
casillas a no de mis casillas no es que
is the last time that you're going to mention
es la última vez que tú vas a mencionar
my children because if you have a
a mis hijos porque si tienes la [__]
dirty dick your mouth is dirtier the
sucia más sucia tienes la boces la
next time I'll talk Yeah well before I talk
próxima hable Sí pues antes de que hable
about my mother you better shut your little mouth
de mi madre mejor te calla la boquita Te
you put your head down you base the lo
pones la cabecita para abajo basas el lo
cco you get think Mad hab I
cco pillas piens Mad hab yo a tu madre
hadn't mentioned your mother more [ __ ]
no le había mencionado más gilipolla Así
I like it like that I g to you yes an [ __ ] g
me gusta así me g a ti sí un gilipolla g
to me mention whatever you want but
a mí me menciona lo que tú quieras pero
come on every time I mention my mother
vamos que siempre que mencion mi madre
knows what she has what I have what I have you
sabá lo que tiene qué tengo qué tengo me
go to you my answer you my answer your
vas a ti mi respuesta ti mi respuesta tu
answer and your answer What is my
respuesta y tu respuesta Qué es mi
answer has made you get out of your tuus
respuesta te ha hecho sacarte de tuus
Casillas with I told you very clearly ri you
Casillas con te dicho muy claro ri lo
have given it javima time but I'll tell you
has dado javima vez pero que te lo digo
again next time you mention my
otra vez próxima vez que menciones a mis
children I'll go wherever you are and I'll turn your
hijos voy a donde estés y te vuelvo las
glasses back on you if you
gafas si te
want to mention my mother I'll have to
quieres que menciones a mi madre tendré
mention whoever I want because
que mencionar a quien yo quiera porque
you are free to go out
tú está tomado de la libertad que sal
do what you see Rick do what you
haz lo que tú veas Rick haz lo que tú
see you're going to go into the owner's operand mode
veas vas a pasar al modo operand del
don't threaten with ages and pal but
dueño no amenazar con ages y pal pero si
yes I'm telling you very clearly if you
es que te lo estoy diciendo clarísimo si
mention again
vuelves a mencionar a
What is it that you don't understand
Qué es lo que no entiendes
Ricky what are my children doing here What's
Ricky qué pintan aquí mis hijos Qué
my mother doing here again you're going to say the
pinta aquí mi madre otra vez vas a decir
same thing Well to  can you shut up
lo mismo Pues a callar puedes a callar a
shut up you how the D [ __ ] you how he
callarte tú como te folló el D como te
put the dala [ __ ] in you that you still can't get over it r we've
metió la [__] del dala que no la supera
moved on to dal it had to
todavía r ya pasamos al dal ha tenido
happen
que pasar
to you can't since her dalala
al no puedes desde que her dalala te
raped you the other day
metió aquella violada el otro día en
live dude already took me out ardala already take it
directo tío ya me sac ardala ya me
out she's already shat herself and said [ __ ] she
sacala ya se ha cagado y ha dicho [__]
threatened him it's been recorded she's
le ha amenazado ha quedado registrado me
eating me alive you can see I'm nervous I'm
está comiendo vivo se me ve nerv tengo
40 years old what in What have I shat myself
40 años en qué en En qué me he cagado En
What have I shat myself that you're pulling
qué me he cagado que te has puesto a
out dala man what are you doing dala here we
sacar dala tío qué pintas dala aquí
're talking you and me what are you doing dala it's not that you
estamos hablando tú y yo qué pintas dala
're completely it's hard for you to
no es que estás completamente te cuesta
have it in your mouth dude it's not hard for you
tenerlo en la boca tío poco te cuesta
ten Bo to say that have you seen your Twitter and
ten Bo decir eso has visto tu Twitter y
your channel have you seen your channel
tu canal has visto tu canal
Javi I don't know I don't know have you seen your channel and your
Javi No sé no sé has visto tu canal y tu
Twitter yes Javi I've seen it I'm very
Twitter sí Javi lo he visto estoy
proud dude he's very proud
orgullosísimo tío está orgullosísimo
okay Hey not like my
vale Oye no como mi
mother Let me put the ura on you
madre Me dejas que que te ponga las ura
or what to me no I have them I have
o qué a mí a mí no yo las tengo yo tengo
the entire discord recorded if you're going to
el discord completo grabado si vas a
show parts of it and  mine
mostrar las partes de ella y las mías
for whatever you want and in case what
por lo que quieras y en caso de que lo
you show is not equivalent to what
que muestres no se equivalga a lo que
was there because the message has already been deleted, don't
había porque ya borrado mensaje no te
worry, I will also expose them, let it be
preocupes que yo los expongo también que
known that if I have not done it at
conste si yo no lo he hecho por petición
her request, I understand that she has also
de ella entiendo que a ti también te ha
asked you that you want to stay out of it, but
pedido que quieres estar al margen pero
if you are going to publish it there, I have your
si la vas a publicar allá tú tengo tu
permission to put the
permiso para poner la captura de
screenshot where you start to intimidate a
pantalla donde empiezas a amedrentar una
girl as I already told you the other day. You do not
chavala como ya conté el otro día no No
have permission to put the
tienes permiso para poner la
full conversation as I told you. Yes,
conversación completa como te dicho Sí
but I saw you putting them. The screenshots one
pero te las vi poniendo Las capturas una
by one,
por una
okay, one by one. Yeah, of course, from the
vale una por una Ajá claro de la
full conversation. Yes, yes, so that you
conversación completa Sí sí para que tú
can explain them to me, okay. Yes, from the
me las vayas explicando vale Sí de la
full conversation. Yes, okay, come on
conversación completa Sí vale venga
first. We have one here where you be
primero Tenemos aquí una donde tú
careful, careful because if you put things
cuidado cuidado porque como pongas cosas
that, to explain it, I'm
que para explicarlo tea que doca la niña
not going to do it, so be careful
no lo voy a hacer entonces ten cuidado
what you put and the girl has asked you
lo que pone y la niña te ha pedido a ti
personally, which I also know, not to
personalmente que también lo sé que no
expose her and not to give her information. Hey,
la exponga y que no de sus datos Oye por
why did you act like a newbie when she
qué te has hecho el nuevo cuando te ha
brought up you? Here, people say that you were going to
sacado Aquí la gente lo de que ibas a
take three girls to  Andorra why did you
llevar tres niñas a andorra por qué te
act like a newbie if you knew it
has hecho el nuevo si tú lo sabías
Because it's a
Porque es
lie but let's see here when they brought
mentira pero a ver aquí cuando te han
up the subject girls are jav what three
sacado el tema niñas son jav qu tres
girls are chicken Paula and tired those
niñas son pollo Paula y cansita esas
three girls who were going to come to the debate
tres niñas que iban a venir al debate A
What Excuse me eh one was going to go to Andorra to
qué Perdona eh una iba ir a andorra a
record a video with you and the other two
grabar un vídeo contigo y las otras dos
you were going to take them to the debate to the debate
te las ibas a llevar al debate al debate
What oh you know no I will know No you
A qué ah tú sabrás no Yo sabré No tú
are the one who has this information that is
eres el que tien esta información que la
giving it as valid to the debate What the
está dando por válida al debate A qué
hell were these two going to come Okay let's go part
[__] iban a venir estas dos Bueno vamos
by part okay first first let's go
por parte vale primero primero vamos
but answer answer Javier What were
pero responde responde Javier A qué iban
these two going to come to the debate first let's go
a venir al debate estas dos primero
with Paula no no no first what
vamos con Paula no no no primero lo que
you said [ __ ] you're a man of your word you bring
has dicho [__] so un hombre de palabra
up a subject finish it close it no
me sacas un tema termínalo ciérralo no
Prim let's go with Paula and then we'll go with
Prim vamos con Paula y luego vamos con
another and then come with Paula come with Paula I gave
otra y luego venga con Paula venga con
you the opportunity by the way
Paula te di la oportunidad por cierto
Paula you mixed up her name and she didn't want to
Paula liaste su nombre y ella no quería
be public I'm telling you again Yes you
ser pública te lo digo de nuevo Sí tú
said a lot of things about her in
contaste un montón de cosas de ella en
the debate and she didn't mention her and I didn't
el debate y ella te no la mencioné y no
do anything that  you relate
hice nada que la relacionas
to her name now let's go to
con su nombre ahora vamos a
each I gave you the opportunity to
cada te di la oportunidad de hacerte
literally become rich become independent
literalmente rica independizarte
abandon a toxic and
abandonar una situación tóxica y
negative situation to be your life Ah this for
negativa para ser tu vida Ah esto para
you taught the whole conversation no You
ti enseñado toda la conversación no Tú
believe this message comes the first thing we
te crees este mensaje viene lo primero
talked about let's go reading little by
que hablamos a vamos a ir leyendo poco a
little is that this is not the beginning
poco es que esto no es el principio
loser This is not the beginning if I
pringado Esto no es el principio si le
tell you that because that's what she asked me
digo eso porque es lo que ella me pedía
what she wanted to get out by telling her
lo que quería sacarse contando su
testimony What had happened to her with
testimonio Lo que le había pasado con
Dala was that leaving her house because of a
dala era eso salir de su casa por una
toxic situation improving the movements with
situación tóxica mejorar las movidad con
her partner because she couldn't live well I'm
su pareja porque no podía vivir bueno es
not going to tell her private life
que no lo voy a contar su vida privada
man [ __ ] how hard she fell you were going to
tío [__] qué fuerte caído la ibas a
be literally rich for her to go
ser literalmente rica para que fuera
talk about money it was a lot of money okay for her to
hablar de pastón era un pastón vale para
go tell her story This was
que fuera a contar su historia Esto fue
a What is a request from her called
una Cómo se llama una solicitud suya
she wanted to do
ella quería hacer
this I mean you were practically going to
esto O sea que prácticamente le ibais a
pay a girl to go
pagar a una chavala para que fuera a
talk about what you wanted that
hablar lo que ustedes queríais eso
because you make things up this what
porque te inventar cosas esto qué ha
happened So why were you going to
pasado Entonces para qué le ibais a
pay her to tell her testimony with
pagar para que contase su testimonio con
Dallas her story with him and yes well I
Dallas su historia con él y sí pues yo
have conversations here  with her It's not
tengo aquí conversaciones con ella No es
that I have conversations with
que yo tengo aquí conversaciones con
her here and she told me no and I don't
ella y ella me ha dicho que no y yo
either if I'm the one who talked to
también si yo soy el que hablado con
her you know if you came last to
ella sab si tú has llegado al último a
this man I'm the one who talked to her
esto tío yo so el que hablé con ella por
why are you making up that we were going to tell her to
qué te inventas que le íbamos a decir
make up things what are you talking about I
que se inventara cosas qué hablas yo
have conversations with her here in
tengo aquí conversaciones con ella en
which she tells me that Dalas hasn't
las que me dice que Dalas a ella no le
done anything bad to her Oh and I have screenshots
ha hecho nada malo Ah y yo tengo captura
and What chats the ones you
y chats de What los que que me has
asked me not to tell Javier but
pedido que no lo cuentes Javier pero
come on they've been together that she's taken
vamos que han estado juntos que ha hecho
photos they've given each other gifts
fotos que se han hecho regalitos
private conversations how they
conversaciones privadas cómo lo
planned everything I have everything I have everything and
planearon todo tengo todo tengo todo y
you don't have that information because the
tú esos datos no los tienes porque la
girl You've probably already seen
chavala Ya te habrás podido comprobar
that she's not entirely well and she didn't want it to be
que no está del todo bien y no quería
done in public but Ricky that's what's
que se hiciese en público pero Ricky es
wrong with it is wrong with him that he wanted to expose or
malo tiene de malo que quisa exposear o
rather let's see if I understand one thing you
sea a ver si yo entiendo una cosa tú
take a girl who knows Dallas from
coges a una tía que conoce a Dallas de
whatever no girl comes to me and
lo que sea no una tía me viene y me
enters me No I don't take anything Javi the thing
entra No yo no cojo nada Javi la cosa
properly a girl talks to me enters me
con propiedad una tía me habla me entra
because she has something with Dallas  that wants to
porque tiene algo con Dallas que quiere
share starts the story properly
compartir empieza así la historia con
but there's nothing wrong with it not
propiedad pero no tiene nada de malo no
what she wants to
lo que quiere
share Yeah yes, there's a
compartir Sí sí que tiene de malo tío un
lot of things wrong with it, man, well she tells me
montón de cosas pues a mí ella me dice
no Of course what's she going to tell you that
que no Claro qué te va a decir ella que
what you want is for you to defend her
lo que quieres es que la defiendas
because she knows that it pisses me off
porque sabe quea que me toque los
if I feel like it I'll tell it and I have
[__] si me sale de la poa lo cuento y
n't done it out of deference because the
no lo he hecho por deferencia porque la
girl isn't well but well she's not
chavala no está bien pero bueno esa no
well and pollo is perfect
está bien y pollo sí está perfecta
true when did I say that no no I'm
verdad cuándo he dicho eso no no te
asking you what she considers But it's
pregunto que esa considera Pero está
okay
bien
now don't talk loudly it's not that you
ahora no hables por lo alto no es que
're saying that now it's like it doesn't
estás diciendo que ahora esta como no te
suit you volume this one is not well
conviene volumen esta esta no está bien
but pollo can't pollo is perfect
pero pollo no puede pollo está perfecta
no pollo is perfect no the Face can't
no pollo está perfecta no el Face no me
stop the volume what the [ __ ] Don have they
puede parar el volumen qué putad Don te
done to you eh you can talk here eh pollo
han hecho eh aquí puedes hablar eh pollo
is perfect I don't know how Pollo is
está perfecta yo que sé cómo está Pollo
I don't know her in person that girl what
yo no la conozco en persona esa chavala
's that she's talking nonsense all the time
que es que está todo el tiempo hablado
can you talk well what if you
tontería puedes hablar bien qué que si
can talk well and stop
puedes hablar bien y dejarte de
fussing laughter and that's what you don't
aspaviento risa y es es lo que no
understand Ha What is it that you
entiendes Ja Qué es lo que no entiendes
're telling me  that girl is not
me estás diciendo que esa chavala no
well because you are no longer interested in that
está bien porque ya no te interesa esa
girl because she is the one who says now that
chavala porque es la que dice ahora que
d has not done anything to her but poll I
d no le ha hecho nada pero poll
have not said that either Ah do you
no lo he dicho eso nunca tampoco Ah
consider that pollo is well dismiss me from I
consideras que pollo está bien esame
consider that pollo is a girl
de Considero que pollo es una chavala
who has many problems the truth and
que tiene muchos problemas la verdad y
you take advantage of her no and you take advantage
te aprovechas de ella no y te aprovechas
of her no sorry what did you think that
de ella no perdón qué te has pensado que
is my ar in 2016 Jai no no no no s that
es mi ar en 2016 Jai no no no no s esa
time listen that you take advantage of her
época escucha que te aprovechas de ella
and her state to use the counterweapon
y de su estado para usar la contra arma
against Dallas that [ __ ] er r you get that
contra Dallas esa [__] er r sacas eso
Javi where do you get that from well I get that from the fact that
Javi de dónde sacas eso pues eso lo saco
I have audio of pollo and pollo is the one who
de que tengo audio de pollo y pollo es
tells you that she has a
la que te cuenta a ti que tiene un
contract with Dallas she shows you a photocopy she
contrato con Dallas te enseña fotocopi
is the one who puts you in contact with Paul p
es la que te pone en contacto con Paul p
that about pollo then will she be reported
eso de pollo entonces estará denunciadas
If that exists No yes if it depended on you
Si eso existe No si si dependiera de ti
yes because the truth is that you did not
sí porque la verdad es que a ti te
give a [ __ ] about pollo Sorry Yes yes yes
importó una [__] pollo Perdón Sí sí si
yes pollo really of the cult cancer
si pollo realmente del cáncer de secta
that you have set up the pis is not even pollo
que tenéis montados los pis es ni pollo
if pollo really had had a
si pollo realmente hubiese tenido un
confidentiality contract how is it
contrato de confidencialidad como se
invented  okay you would have [ __ ] up
inventa vale tú la hubieras [__]
because in your videos in order to have
porque tú en tus vídeos con tal de tener
a weapon against support you would have given
un arma contra poyo te hubieras sudado
a [ __ ] that they would have reported him no
la [__] que le hubieran denunciado no
mm yes
mm sí
clown you are fantastic you have an idea
payaso te sale fantal tienes una idea
to not do these things listen no And
para no hacer estas cosas escucha no Y
you are already starting to have hair on your
tú ya empiezas a tener pelo en los
balls to not be
[__] para para no serc
ridiculous if we talk about [ __ ] I am here
ridículo si qui hablamos de pollas estoy
too I have no problem
yo también no tengo ningún problema
I am very proud dude Okay yeah yeah
estoy muy orgulloso tío Bueno ya ya eh
chicken eh this girl I consider that she is
pollo eh esta chica Considero que está
very screwed in many factors for things that she
muy puteada en muchos factores por cosas
has talked to me if I think she is
que ha hablado conmigo si creo que está
very screwed but not in any of the
muy jodida pero no en ninguno de los
videos that I have made I have confirmed or
vídeos que he hecho he confirmado ni he
assured that she has anything with him I have
asegurado que tenga nada con él he
assumed that yes because of the things that she has
supuesto que sí por las cosas que ha
published and the things that we have been able to
publicado y las cosas que hemos podido
see I have assumed in something but I have never
ver He supuesto en algo pero nunca lo he
taken it as valid I have shown anything nor has she
dado por válido he mostrado nada ni ella
confirmed that she has anything signed with him
confirmado que tenga algo firmado con él
never what a clown mythomaniac and liar
nunca vaya payaso mitómano y mentiroso
that you are made I mean you are like ordal
que estás hecho o sea estás como ordal
gr past you have never never considered
gr pasado nunca nunca has considerado
that pollo had a contract and you have
que pollo tuviera un contrato y has
made a [ __ ] series and a [ __ ] debate
hecho una [__] serie y un [__] debate
based on pollo based on pollo supposed I have
basado en pollo basado en pollo supuesto
told you the supposed that she has it
te lo he dicho el supuesto que lo tiene
Of course yes but I never noo  How come
Claro que sí pero yo nunca noo Cómo que
I've never confirmed it it's assumed
yo nunca lo he confirmado es supuesto
that he has it because of the things he publishes
que lo tiene por las cosas que publica
that he's said
que ha dicho
but you're telling me that you've
pero que tú me estás diciendo que tú has
made a [ __ ] series a [ __ ] series
hecho una [__] serie una [__] serie
about Dallas contracts based on
sobre los contratos de Dallas basado en
chicken it's not like a 30 year old guy making
pollo no es que un chico de 30 haciendo
contracts for some young girls Cos do
contratos a una Cos de las chavalas
you want to keep talking about
jóvenes quieres que sigamos hablando de
this topic or do we change Ricky we're
este tema o cambiamos Ricky estamos
talking about this topic and we're going to
hablando de este tema y lo vamos a
finish it do you want to change it now because
terminar quieres cambiarlo ya porque no
you're not interested in what I asked
te interesa los que yo te preguntado a
you you haven't finished it How little The
ti no lo has terminado Qué poquito Las
screenshots of the pa this No what the [ __ ] what the
capturas de la pa esta No qué [__] qué
[ __ ] what the [ __ ] are we going to
[__] qué [__] qu vamos
all of the context that you found out about the
toas del contexto que te enterado del
context you've dropped your little mouth quickly C joke
contexto te has cado la boquita rápido C
not even kidding not even kidding puppy
coña ni de coña ni de coña cachorrito
deer not even kidding not even
ciervo ni de coña ni de
kidding but but since you've got my support I'll
coña pero pero como me has sacado apoyo
answer you I mean all your videos I have got your
te respondo O sea todos tus vídeos yo yo
support you have got support
te he sacado apoyo tú has sacado apoyo
Yeah what are you
Sí qué
saying Yeah yes yes you've got out saado well
dices Sí sí sí has sacado tú saado bueno
Okay then chicken has come out
Vale pues ha salido pollo ha salido
chicken has come out salt you have brought out
pollo sal has sacado tú has sacado a
Paula chicken little song with little song you have shat yourself
Paula pollo cancita con cancita te has
with  Paul lasted 2 seconds
cagado encima con Paul durado 2 segundos
with the capture with chicken you don't know what the
con la captur con pollo no sabes qué
[ __ ] to say what are you doing calm down Ricky
[__] decir qué haces calma calma Ricky
calm down calm down chicken has come out cal I'm
calma calma ha salido pollo cal estoy
chicken uncle lost tece Thank you very much Yes yes
pollo tío perd tece Muchas gracias Sí sí
to divert attention But chicken has come out
para desviar la atención Pero ha salido
the conversation and I'm
pollo la conversación y yo te estoy
answering you about chicken we continue with
respondiendo lo de pollo seguimos con
Paula's captures no no no
Las capturas de la Paula no no no ha
chicken has come out you brought out Pollo okay
salido pollo tú has sacado a Pollo vale
okay Ricky But only you have talked about
vale Ricky Pero salo tú has hablado de
chicken a 20 year old girl okay we continue
pollo una niña de 20 años vale seguimos
with Paula So not with
con Paula Entonces no con las
Paula's conversations not with whoever you
conversaciones de Paula no con quien tú
want if you are the one who is
quieras si eres tú el que me está
interrogating me Javier Okay but we are not going to
interrogando Javier Vale pero no vamos a
interc the questions you have asked me
interc las preguntas me has preguntado
a lot of things let me
un montón de cosas déjame alguna
ask some now I will ask you one one [ __ ] you have
pregunto ahora te pregun una una [__] me
asked me many things answer whatever
has preguntado muchas cosas respond lo
you want but one one it's not that
que tú quieras pero una una no es que
we have to end this that's why I
tenemos que terminar con esto por eso
say about raed's mother man
por eso digo lo de la madre de raed tío
how how that you have not made a video about it
có cómo eso no has hecho un vídeo al
or how and if you have done it what did you
respecto o como y si lo has hecho qué
think man yes I did but we are going to
has opinado tío sí lo hice pero vamos a
talk about this r And what did you think what did you
hablar de esto r Y qué has opinado qué
think let's talk about This okay
has opinado vamos a hablar de Esto vale
No  what did you think about
No qué has opinado de lo de la madre
Ricki's mother's case let's talk about this and then we'll
ricki vamos a hablar de esto y luego te
PR you What do you think if I say that
PR Qué te parece que diga que lo de la
Ra's mother died because of her in
madre de ra murió por su culpa en la
jail What do you think about that not
cárcel Qué te parece eso que no me
changing the subject let's continue with
cambies de tema que vamos a seguir con
Paula we're going to clear the owner and
Paula vamos a blanquear al dueño y a
keep charging not so that
seguir cobrando no para que entre
money comes into the house very well let's see very well let's
pastita en casa muy bien a ver muy bien
see an example of a [ __ ] mother bl example
a ver un ejemplo de [__] madre bl ejemp
of a [ __ ] mother you are blanque You are an
de [__] madre eres blanque Eres un
example of a [ __ ] mother I don't want to talk about
ejemplo de [__] madre no quiero hablar
things that don't interest you because you know what the
cosas que no te interesan porque sabes
other says publicly
que lo que cuenta el otro públicamente
If you speak badly of him and you don't agree
Si hablas mal de él y no está de acuero
with what he did you
con lo que la hecho
[ __ ] you are stupid I'm
gilipolla eres tonto
literally going to answer when
literalmente voy a responder cuando
terando no because I've been asking myself
terando no porque me estado preguntando
porita about
porita por
everything Javi you are the pet of the gr t er the
todo Javi eres la mascota del gr t er la
pet of anyone delo de Willy
mascota de cualquiera de delo de Willy
de winu of anyone Here I have I have
de winu de cualquiera Aquí
if we teach to see how much
tengo tengo si enseñamos a ver cuán
each one of us charges man Teo I live do
cobramos cada uno hombre Teo vivo
you think you are a kid capud Then you're right if you
crees estud capud Enton tienes razón si
charge more you have r pass pass
cobras más tienes r pas pasa
capture You have a lot of
captura Tienes mucho
money Here it is here is a capture
dinero Aquí está aquí está una captura
where you try  intimidate the girl to
donde intentas amedrentar la chavala a
queer page with context in case it can be
queer pag con contexto por si puede sera
what I said and nothing open directly telling
lo dich anc nada abrir directo contando
how a girl from my own
cómo me ha robado una chica de mi propia
city robbed me but it's funny that a
ciudad perino gracia me hace que una
girl steals my face and now she
chavala me roben la cara y ahora me pida
apologizes for
perdón por
spending it
gastármelo
for free I tell her a girl I don't
de gratis le digo una chavala no me
feel like opening directly telling I don't know what What do I
apetece abrir directo contando no sé qué
say to her come on explain it what does she tell me let's see
Qué le digo yo venga explícalo qué me
explain it no no
dice ella a ver explícalo no no
explain it no show it she told me she was going
explícalo no enséñalo me ha dicho que
to show the full conversation
iba a enseñar la conversación completa
exp here I see that you are
exp aquí yo veo que tú estás
intimidating the girl what a
amedrentando a la chavala vaya ejemplo
real example eh Javi I'm telling you seriously what an
de verdad eh Javi te lo digo en serio
example Tito you are setting
vaya ejemplo Tito estás dando un ejemplo
such a terrible example to the gossip community
tan pésimo a la comunidad del salseo
as a man or rather you are God horrible I will
como hombre o sea estás Dios horrible te
give you the context if you want you won't
doy el contexto si quieres que no te lo
believe it but oh well And if not I will show
vas a creer pero bueno Y si no mostraré
the screenshots since I have seen that you
Las capturas ya que he visto que a ti te
have sweated it I understand that the girl does not care that you
la has sudado entiendo que la niña te da
are failing the word that you
igual que estás fallando la palabra que
gave to her not to show
le diste a ella de no Mostrar las
things answer now by  what are you
cosas responde ya por qué estás
intimidating the girl, let's say it was
amedrentando a la chavala vamos que esba
a little bit of attention that the girl didn't
un poquito la atención de que la niña no
want me to publish it, she's
quería que lo publicara lo está
showing it no But why are you
enseñando no Pero por qué estás
intimidating the girl that you wanted to
amedrentando a la chavala que te querías
take to Andorra paying her very well
llevar a andorra pagándole muy bien
because I pay the money for the train she takes out
porque pago el dinero del tren se saca
the tickets she shows it to me and
los billetes me lo enseña y me hace
ghosts me for 7 days after 7 days I
ghosting durante 7 días a los 7 días le
say Hey this is tomorrow are you taking the train no
digo Oye esto es mañana coges el tren no
And he says no the truth is I haven't
Y me dice no la verdad es que no me he
spent the money on anything else and I can't pay you
gastado el dinero para otra cosa y no te
back and I say man you're
lo puedo devolver y le digo hombre a mí
not going to steal from me I put the
no me vas a robar te he puesto los
trains so you could upload this if I don't
trenes para que subieras esto si no
exchange the ticket and give me back the
descambio el billete y me devuelves el
money no I can't give it to you sorry
dinero no no te lo puedo dar lo siento
goodbye and it keeps dripping after a while I
adiós y me sigue goteando al rato le
say listen to me I don't feel like opening a
digo escúchame no me apetece abrir un
live telling you that you robbed me No not even
directo contando que me has robado No ni
telling the [ __ ] that I had told him
contando la [__] que me había contado
that I wasn't going to tell him But well eh I don't
que no le iba a contar Pero bueno eh No
know what he gives me back the money after 5 10
sé qué me devuelve el dinero a los 5 10
minutes he gives me back the money let's go
minutos me devuelve el dinero vamos que
intimidate her and you  He returned the money, no
la amedrentar y te devolvió el dinero no
Ricky, no Javi, I didn't tell him that if he
Ricky No Javi No le dije que si me
stole from me, he would say that he had stolen that
robaba contaba que me había robado eso
for you to intimidate, yes, you know what
para ti amedrentar sí Tú sabes lo que es
intimidation is, he is showing some
amedrentar está enseñando unas
conversations, a user and the profile of
conversaciones un usuario y el perfil de
a girl who wants to be anonymous and does
una chavala que quiere ser anónima y que
n't want this to be shown, that she
no quiere que se muestre esto que ha
trusted you thinking that she was going to
confiado en ti pensando que iba a
hurt me, that you talked about this that is, let's say that
hacerme daño que tú hablaras de esto que
for your age, it
está vamos que para la edad que tienes
seems you don't have two summers left, let's see, that is
parece te faltan dos veranos a ver eso
intimidating, that is intimidating because you
amedrentar eso es amedrentar s porque tú
don't, kid, be there, you don't know, kid, now
no chaval estar tú no sabes chaval ahora
how is she, you know, you don't know how the chal
cómo estará sab tú no sabes la chal
be now, you just fooled me that you
estar ahora me acabas de vasilar de que
earn a lot of money, you're
ganas mucho dinero yedras a una chavala
much more, Jen for
mucho más Jen por
200, intimidates for 200, but it's that you
200 amedrenta por 200 pero es que te
're making up your story, you're
estás inventando tu película te la estás
believing it at 40 years old, this You are the
creyendo con 40 añitos esto Eres el
pride of the house, eh, let's go again with
orgullo de la casa eh otra vez vamos con
the houses,
las casas
Rick, I can't mention the
Rick no puedo mencionar tampoco la
structure either, no, I don't ask, I can't
estructura no no pregunto Tampoco puede
talk either, I can't talk, no, teos, I'm
hablar Tampoco puede hablar no teos te
coming again tomorrow  can you
calient otra vez viene mañana puedes
talk calmly can you talk calmly
hablar calmado puedes haar calmado
calmly if he's out of your mind
calmado si está fuera de tu casilla
okay no it seems not but well for 200
bien no parce que no pero bueno por 200
euros for 200 euros intimidate a
euritos por 200 euritos amedrenta a una
girl because she spent 200 euros you just made it up
chavala porque se gastó 200 eur te lo
queo yes we have seen
acabas de inventar queo si hemos visto
the capture on the screen Ricky we have
la captura en la pantalla Ricky hemos
seen the capture you have hidden the
visto la captura has escondido el
context that you want and when I have
contexto que te d la gana y cuando lo he
explained it you have ignored it
explicado te la has pasado por el [__]
in fact look you don't even remember the
de hecho mira ni te acuerdas del
context that you ricki intimidate the
contexto que te ricki amedrentar a la
girl to tell the truth riamu riamu
chavala que diga la verdad riamu riamu
you are scared daddy you sent me to
estás asustadizo papi que me mandaste a
block me from my other account why did
bloquear de la otra cuenta mía para que
this happen is a video what I'm
ha pasado esto es un vídeo lo que esto
listening to are you scared r What's going on What's going on
escuchando tienes miedito r Qué pasa Qué
Oh [ __ ] okay okay [ __ ] I had
pasa Ah [__] vale vale [__] se me había
forgotten to think that this is on discord dude
olvidado pensar que est er discord tío
what's going on riamu Are you scared I
pas qué pasa riamu Estás asustado Yo
just want to know if he's scared
solamente quiero saber si está asustado
And he's going to send me too he's going to
Y me va a mandar también me va me va a
want to censor me from this account too
querer censurar de esta cuenta también
here poncito to listen to the truth
aquí poncito a escuchar la verdad a
listen to the truth of the of of  your God
escuchar la verdad del de de de tu Dios
so calm down porv past what
así que acalmar porv pasado qué ha
happened what
pasado qué ha
happened that the riamu took me out of my
pasado que me que el riamu me sacó de mi
main Twitter account he took the
cuenta principal de Twitter me sacó el
space and blocked me so I couldn't get
espacio y me bloqueó para que no pudiera
in anymore
entr más
ra raet Listen to me it wasn't
ra raet Escúchame yo no he sido
literally I just uploaded you or rather and
literalmente Te acabo de subir o sea y
the main one I haven't even blocked you You're welcome I mean I don't
la principal ni siquiera te he bloqueado
know why it won't let you
De nada o sea no sé por qué no te deja
upload literally we can continue we can continue we can continue
subir literal podemos segir podemos
please
podemos seguir podemos seguir por favor
Twitter error cl yes it is m no plan okay
error de Twitter cl sí es m no plan vale
Ricky tell me what the one from
Ricky cuéntame qué es lo que tenía la de
Crdoba had because she tells me that there's
Córdoba porque a mí me dice que ya no
nothing wrong with her anymore tell me what you think
tiene nada de maloi cuéntame qué opinas
about ra's mother her mother's uncle I think she's
de la madre de ra tío de su madre Creo
going to like it okay to talk let's
que s le va a parecer bien habl vamos a
finish let's finish this then we
terminar vamos a terminar con esto luego
talk about what you want end with what
hablamos lo que tú quier termina con lo
you think is okay no cool dude I'll
que a ti te parea bien no Mola tío yo te
take out things that you don't like because the
saco tem que no te gustan porque al
owner gets angry and you don't want to
dueño se te enfada y no quieres
answer I know you're not going to leave topics
responder yo lo sé no vas a dejar temas
in the middle you're not going to run away from any topic dude
a media no vas a huir de ningún tema tío
but if you haven't finished Paula's one you have
pero si no me has terminado el de Paula
n't finished  of chicken you haven't
no me has terminado el de pollo no me
finished me well let's finish it let's
has terminado pues vamos a terminarlo
finish it let's finish it let's finish it and you
vamos a terminarlo vamos a terminarlo y
don't want to discuss it and you don't want to
no quieres discutirlo y no quieres
discuss it ra Yeah but first let's finish what we're
discutirlo ra Sí pero primero vamos a
talking about even
terminar lo que estamos hablando aunque
if you're nervous let's finish it okay What is it why were you going to pay her a fortune and get that girl from Crdoba out of poverty if that girl tells me that she has nothing wrong with Javi Javi asked me I don't know if she has told you if you know her situation at home
contado si conoces su situación en casa
but it is very unsustainable and very serious and it
pero es muy insostenible y muy grave y
is the main and only reason why she
es el principal motivo y único por el
no longer wanted her
que ya no quería que se supiera ni su
name or her username or her photo or anything to be known you have
nombre ni su usuario ni su foto ni nada
exposed it because you're a notes
lo has expuesto porque eres un notas lo
you have exposed it and this kid is going to
has expuesto y esta chaval le va a
look for problems because this is going to
buscar problemas porque esto le va a
reach people who were no longer
llegar a la gente que ya no le
interested in it reaching them and she is very
interesaba que le llegase y está muy
pissed off if you ask me something and I
puteada si me preguntas algo y te
answer you don't like what I
respondo no te gusta qui que le
do to her But what was wrong
hagao Pero qué es lo malo que tenía
with her let her tell you she hasn't
sobre dala ella que te lo cuente ella no
given you all the conversations you don't
te ha pasado todas las conversaciones no
have everything she tells me that she
lo tienes tú todo ella me dice que no
has absolutely nothing Ah well  if she doesn't
tiene absolutamente nada Ah pues si no
have anything that gives you permission Let her go up and
tiene nada que te dé permiso Que suba y
give you permission for me to show it that I
te dé permiso a que yo lo enseñe que lo
show everything and I don't care tell it let her
muestro todo y me la pela cuéntalo que
give it to you that if she gives you permission no I
te lo dé que si te da permiso no no
can't because they are things between her and
puedo porque son cosas entre ella y
Dallas I can't answer her because
Dallas no puedo responderla porque me a
the girl is going to report me that she is not well
denunciar la chavala que no está bien
but the girl is not stupid for those
pero la chavala no es tonta para esas
things tell it let her tell what I mean
cosas cuéntalo que cuente de qué O sea
Dallas had committed any crime
Dallas había cometido algún delito
against
contra
her crime not that I know of crime has not
ella delito no que yo sepa delito no ha
cheated on her partner then what your your
engañado a su pareja la entonces que ti
things your things that you would break her
tuo cosas tuo cosas que tú le partiría
mouth if you saw them eh Dallas you who
la boca si las vieras eh a Dallas tú que
love him very much then If no it is not a
lo quieres mucho entonces Si no no es
crime but it is very serious it is very serious
delito pero es muy grave es muy grave
very very serious but if it is not a crime But I
muy muy grave pero si no es delito Pero
tell you that if she says Ah yes it is not a crime Does
te digo que si ella dice Ah si no es
everything seem fine to you Javi No
delito Te parece bien todo Javi No
Tell me Ah that's why I say that Be careful with
Dímelo Ah por eso eso digo Cuidado con
the words because later you don't see if they are going to
las palabras que luego no veas si te van
throw it at you a lot e No it is not a crime but
a echarlo harto e No no es delito pero
for example look I'll give you an example
por ejemplo mira te pongo un ejemplo
okay of things that the girl told me and
vale de cosas que la chavala me contó e
to you that a guy who takes 10  years old
a ti que un tío que le saca 10 añitos
with the one who wants to do
con el que quiere bueno hacer cositas
sexual things without his girlfriend finding out would it
sexuales sin que su novia se entere te
seem okay to you to give him the diets of what he
parecería bien pasarle las dietas de lo
has to eat to lose the
que tiene que comer para bajar los kilos
necessary weight to like him would that
necesarios para gustarle eso te
seem okay to you for that you were going to pay him
parecería bien para eso le ibas a pagar
Ricky I mean you were going to are you in favor
Ricky O sea tú la ibas a estás a favor
of eating disorders Javi do you
de los trastornos alimenticios Javi te
think it's okay that I'm freaking out I mean
parece bienate que estoy flipando o sea
your bastion against dala was to make
tu bastión contra dala era hacer
a girl a millionaire how much were you going to
millonaria a una niña cuánto le ibas a
pay her for that man I mean I have some
pagar por eso tío o sea yo tengo una
news she can tell you she man
noticia ella que te lo diga ella hombre
no no to that amount of money you have never
no no to esa cantidad de dinero no lo
seen in your life I knew what Hi
has visto en la vida sabía lo que Hi va
that girl is going to carry but let
a llevar esa chavala pero que te lo
her tell you let her tell you Come on you were going
cuente ella que te lo cuente ella Vamos
to pay him I was going to pay him of
que le ibas a pagar iba a pagarle por
course Yes yes okay you were going to pay him to
supuesto Sí sí vale ibas a pagarle para
sit down and tell eh
que se sentara a contar eh
Dallas so that he could lose weight okay No no
Dallas para que perdiera peso vale No no
no that is an intimate part of his
no eso es una parte íntima de su
testimony in fact I told you because that
testimonio de hecho te lo contado porque
is what seems less serious to me for what I
es lo que me parece menos grave para lo
already wanted to expose the serious ones were The
que ya quería exponer lo grave eran Las
screenshots the videos the audios that was the
capturas los vídeos los audios era lo
serious thing That was  hard the truth and it
grave Eso era lo duro la verdad y me
makes me a lot it really pisses me off that you
hace mucha me da bastante tirria que te
laugh Javi it really pisses me off that you
rías Javi me da bastante tir que te rías
laugh but I mean you were going to take a girl you were going to make her rich then the medrent Ase because she owed you 200 he left he paid them religiously he paid them religiously Med rented no I didn't do it yes the medrent hase we have put the capture here on the screen he didn't steal from me he
captura aquí en pantalla no me robó me
stole it from me and I told him you're not going to steal from me he
lo robó y le dije no me vas a robar me
gave me back the money because I said I'm going to
devolvió el dinero porque dije voy a
tell that you stole from me since I didn't want to
contar que me has robado como no quería
be a public figure I wasn't going to even
ser un personaje público no iba Ni a
tell it about Dallas since I didn't want to be a
contarlo del Dallas como no quería ser
public figure he said take take I'll
personaje público me dijo toma toma te
give you the money that's it it's my turn
devuelvo el dinero ya está me toca la
but that's it let's see what you call it when
pua pero ya está a ver cómo se llama que
you take a girl with your influence
tú cojas a una chavala con tu influencia
and threaten her that you're going to open a
y la amenaces con que vas a abrir un
live broadcast exposing her if she doesn't want you to
directo exponiéndola si ella no quiere
expose her for If that had happened it's
que la exponga para Si eso hubiera
called If that had happened it would be
pasado se llama Si eso hubiera pasado se
called
llamaría
intimidating you can't be that stupid Ricky
amedrentar no puede ser tan tonto Ricky
well Okay then to that girl you
bueno Vale pues a esa chavala a la c
mentioned  you were going to take her to Andorra
mentaste la ibas a llevar hasta andorra
and you were going to aag the old ladies the old ladies
y le ibas aag a las viejas a las viejas
from the other channel I understand that with this
del otro canal entiendo que con estas
[ __ ] they believe everything she says but
[__] se creen todo lo que dice pero
of course you're talking to Pea who has
claro estás hablando con Peña que tiene
the conversations I mean
las conversaciones O sea tú no tienes
you don't have anything to you, neither her things with
nada ti no te ha pasado ni su cosas con
d nor the chat niame Let's see send me What's Up Put
d ni los chat niame A ver mándame el Qué
something about that girl that gives you
Pon Pon algo sobre esa chavala que te dé
permission Upload it, let her give you permission if you've
permiso Súbela que te dé permiso ella si
already made it public you've already
ya la has hecho pública ya la has
doxxed her Put it Put it here eh Put it in here I'll
doxeado to a ella Ponla Métela aquí eh
show you everything
Métela que de permiso lo enseño todo que
with permission because I give permission to Ricko one moment
de permiso doy permiso a ricko un moment
your [ __ ] conad moment They're
su movidas conad momento Es que me están
telling me that my mic is lowered and I
diciendo que el micro mío se baja y no
have no [ __ ] idea why dude I have
tengo ni [__] idea del Por qué tío tengo
the mic very low Today I hope he
el micro bajísimo Yo hoy Espero que me
throws it at me I hope that I hope you all
lo eche Espero que espero que me lo
throw it in my face it's that I don't know why the [ __ ]
echéis en cara es que no sé por qué [__]
the mic is lowered alone dude I mean what the [ __ ]
se baja el micro solo tío O sea qué [__]
poetic [ __ ] can someone call it is
[__] poética lo puede llamar alguno
you c not lowering my mic okay
eres tú c no bajándome el micro vale
okay listen to me eh Ricky me  are you going to teach
vale escúchame eh Ricky me vas a enseñar
something about that supposedly very serious thing, are
algo sobre ese supuesta cosa gravísima
you going to teach me things about a girl
tes para enseñarte cosas de una niña
talking to Dalas Jai, how morbid is
hablando con Dalas Jai tú qué morvo te
that to you, tell me, I mean without proof?
da eso a ti cuéntame o sea sin pruebas
Don't believe me, what proof gives you permission to
No créeme qué prueba que te dé permiso a
the
la
girl? I have put the capture here,
niña yo Yo te he puesto aquí la captura
her with Dalas. No yes, because I am
ella con dasas No sí porque formo yo
part of the conversation what I have
parte de la conversación lo que yo tengo
of her with Dallas is of her with Dalas,
de ella con Dallas es de ella con dasas
I am not part of it, Dallas does not give permission and
yo no formo parte Dallas no da permiso y
she does not give permission, how am I going to
ella no da permiso có que yo lo voy a
teach it, [ __ ], eh, but you have
enseñar gilipolla eh pero tú tienes
conversations with them, short, eh, No,
conversaciones con ellas corto eh No
short, it's you, son, escame, short, Javi, you
corto eres tú hijo escame corto Javi tú
have a lot of nerve for the age that I've been
tienes [__] para la edad que llevo
here, I know, you have conversations with her
aquí yo lo tú tienes conversaciones con
where she tells you. This is worth it.
ella donde ella te cuenta Esto vale
Show me those conversations that you
Enséñame esas conversaciones que tú
have with her, conv, I can't
tienes con ella conv que no puedo
tell you what she tells me that is a
decirte lo que me cuenta que es
revelation of secrets from
revelación de secretos de la vida
Dalas's private life, Javi, that I am not part
Privada de Dalas Javi que no formo parte
of those conversations or those
de esas conversaciones ni de esas
activities, damn, I'll make sure that
actividades [__] yo yo me encargo de que
I make sure that Dala does not report you,
yo me encargo de que dala no te denuncie
selo no no no  the girl gets
selo no no no la chavala consigue el
her permission m d to report me
permiso de ella m d que me denuncie me
like it's Dallas' privacy no
igual que es privacidad de Dallas no
good and the girl's life also
bueno y de la vida de la chica también
tells some private things of hers of course Okay
relata cosas suyas privadas claro Bueno
but get her permission get
pero consigue permiso de ella consigue
her permission I show everything the girl is not
permiso de ella enseño todo la chica no
going to report you she can't you know you know
te va a denunciar no puede sabes sabes
perfectly well that she doesn't have the money for
perfectamente que no tiene economía para
that no economy hoop and you're not going to
eso no economía aro y tú no le vas a
pay all the lawyers No pimp that you
pagar todos los abogados No chulo que
go after the girl for the
vas detrás de la chavalita para el
lawyer so they file a complaint on me throw it away
abogado para que me tiren denunci tira
You are the clown I Rich a girl
tú Tú eres el payaso I Rica a una niña
because she is obsessed with Dallas
porque está obsesionado con el Dallas
because she asked me for the money damn the
porque me pidió el dinero [__] la
girl was in a precarious situation
chavala estaba en una situación precaria
of balls co balls he passes me to the
de [__] co [__] le pasa al
microphone so he has to get
micrófono mío para que se tenga que
off alone dude that changes the subject
bajar solo tío eso cambia de tema vaya
maybe I'll comb your hair again come on Ricky You don't
ser que te peine otra vez venga Ricky No
comb anyone's hair No matter how many times you repeat it
peinas a nadie Por más que lo repitas
dude really accept it dude
tío de verdad asúmelo tío esta etapa
you have to overcome this stage you are making a
debes superarla estás haciendo un
fool of yourself and you're on your Twitter account
ridículo y estás en tu cuenta Twitter
at 40 years old how you
con 40 años cómo te lo
eat it come on and now you put me now me
comes venga y ahora me pones ahora me
now you put me a doggy emoji And already cool cool
ahora me pones un emoji de perrito Y ya
and already  and there this Okay then
chuli chul y ya y ahí este Vale entonces
no, you're not teaching me anything No, you can't
no me no me enseñas nada No no me puedes
teach me anything, I don't have permission for the girl to
enseñar nada no tengo permiso a la chica
show it ask her and I'll show you everything I'll
enseñarlo pídeselo y te lo muestro todo
pass it to you if you want okay Perfect
te lo paso si quieres vale Perfecto
Okay but one thing you're telling me
Bueno pero una cosa tú me estás diciendo
no what the [ __ ] Javi [ __ ] off eh
que no que [__] Javi a tomar por culo eh
pass me what you talked about with Dalas that day
pásame lo que hablaste con Dalas el día
of our debate don't talk on WhatsApp
ese de nuestro debate no hable WhatsApp
send it to me don't talk at all I can't send you
pásamelo no hable nada no te puedo
anything Ah well go to suat that day
mandar nada Ah pues vete ese día a suat
with WhatsApp Take a screenshot and
con WhatsApp Haz una captura y me lo
send it to me V What's up, let's see if nothing comes out
manda V Qué hay a ver si no sale nada
that day come on show it to me and let's
ese día venga enséñamelo y queé te
show you what I talked about with him it does
enseño lo que yo haya hablado con él que
n't matter to you if you're not
no te importa a ti sí
part of the conversation you don't
no formas parte de la conversación no
even need authorization but if it's just that I do
necesitas ni autorización pero si es que
n't feel like it but let's see ry Ah
no me da la gana pero vamos a ver ry Ah
V okay okay let's go you have no proof that you
V vale vale vamos que no tienes prueba
weren't the one who told you get out
de de que no fuiste el que te dijo vete
of there he's talking about the contr
de ahí que está hablando de los contr
contr I don't know that it wasn't him not the one who
contr no sé que no fue él no el que te
told you let's see or so According to your
lo dijo a ver o sea Según tu
logic you accuse me of something that didn't
lógica tú me acusas de una cosa que no
happen and I have to prove to you
ha pasado y yo te tengo que demostrar
that  it hasn't happened Hey, what about calling my
que no ha pasado Oye y lo de llamar a mi
partner a [ __ ], Casillo, a
pareja perra casillo una conversación
private conversation? Ah ah, and is a
privada Ah ah y te parece bien una
private conversation okay? I'm asking
conversación privada ya ya te pregunto a
you ethically, I know that ethics are
ti éticamente que sé que la ética te
a little difficult for you, you have it from that, I'm going to tell you, I'm
cuesta un poquito la tienes de la eso
going to tell you again, I'm
te lo voy te lo voy te lo voy a volver a
going to repeat it again, a
repetir te lo voy a volver a repetir una
private conversation and you have responded
conversación privada y tú has respondido
in public, humiliating
en público humillando a conversación
private conversation, humiliating Lis How how,
privada humillando a Lis Cómo cómo ri
laughing at her tumor accusing tumor Javi
riéndote de su tumor acusando tumor Javi
how I laugh at her Ricky Ricky you can
cómo me río de su Ricky Ricky puedes
talk calmly Ricky you can talk
hablar tranquilo Ricky puedes hablar
calmly Wait wait before you continue
tranquilo Espera espera antes de seguir
talking, you can talk calmly, don't get
hablando puedes hablar tranquilo no te
stressed out, don't get stressed out seriously r you can
agobies no te agobies serio r puedes
talk calmly, it's that he hasn't been
hablar tranquilo es que no le andado el
[ __ ] around I think today he's open straight thinking,
[__] pienso hoy abierto directo pensando
say, look, riy is nervous eh you can
decir mira nervioso está riy eh puedes
talk calmly V example V example you
hablar tranquilo V ejemplo V ejemplo
're giving Ricky can you talk calmly
estás dando Ricky puedes habla tranquilo
you're 27 years old Ricky I'm 40
que tienes 27 años Ricky vo tener 40
Javier I'm already talking to you calmly Yes yes
Javier ya estoy hablándote tranquilo Sí
calmly, then I'll put a
sí tranquilísimo luego te pongo una
screenshot in which maybe you bark, it will
captura en la que a lo mejor te metes
look more realistic with how
ladridos que quedas más realista con el
angry you've gotten  red you've
cabreo que te has pillado lo rojo que te
gotten cocky no but that's not being
has puesto chulo no pero eso no es
mad I've told you that the m of
ningún cabreo eso te lo he dicho la m de
Seriously and I'll reaffirm it to you Okay but
En serio y te lo reafirmo Bueno ma
tomorrow we'll see it on Twitter they're going to
mañana lo vemos en Twitter que le van a
make memes for sure I don't care I
hacer memes seguro to a mí me da igual
'll confirm it again if you want I'll
te lo vuelvo a confirmar si quieres te
put it if you want I'll put it to you that to
lo pongo si quieres te lo pongo que a
my friends
míos
uncle like Ricky let's go to let's go
tío como que Ricky vamos a lo de vamos
Sorry by the way let me comment
Perdona por cierto djame coment
together dog and to my friends that he
unito perro y a colegas míos con los que
got along well with, I thought that he did wrote to him
se llevaba bien creía que sí le escribió
privately saying Look dude Don't do that
por privado diciendo Mira tío No hagas
lad thing on live r a
lo de lad en el directo r un
little that's a lie I'll prove it that's a
poco eso es mentira lo demuestro eso es
lie Prove it Okay I'm going
mentira Demuéstralo Vale Voy
wait okay
espérate vale
look what's not to him Open to friend tell him dude
mira que no le Abre a colega decirle tío
this car barking that they told me you did
esto de car ladrado que me han dicho que
woof woof Look that's a lie
has hecho guau guau Mira eso es mentira
don't come on Ricky Look look look what you're
no venga Ricky Mira miro miro eso que tú
telling me is because I Warn me you
me dices es porque me Avis me has
changed the subject now we go back to
cambiado de tema ahora volvemos a lo de
liy's okay Yes yes what I have Rio about the
liy vale Sí sí lo de que me he Río del
tumor I'm waiting for him to answer me
tumor estoy esperando a que me responda
you're very good at  attention let's see
que se te da muy bien la atención a ver
okay eh what they're mentioning to me is
vale eh eso que me están mencionando es
utbh that in a live they were
utbh que en un directo me estaban
telling me that he had
diciendo que había
barked did he said Javi Oliveira No no he
ladrado hizo dijo Javi oliveira No no
said said gu gu the one that Ricky and then
dijo dijo gu gu la que Ricky y entonces
I told him gave Wow what has happened to
yo le dije dio Wow lo que le ha dado a
Ricky he said
Ricky dijo
Teach me r you can talk Ricky you can
Enséñame r puedes hablar Ricky puedes
talk and why are you writing to him man
hablar y por qué le escribes tío
So Ricky you can talk I'm talking I'm talking I'm
Entonces Ricky puedes hablar estoy
talking you're acting like a
hablando estoy hablando estoy hablando
clown man it's gotten
estás haciendo el payaso
carried away I didn't want to say you can
tío se ha liado no quería decir puedes
talk and it got carried away but he's at his age forgive him
hablar y se ha liado pero es la edad
excuse me listen that's it's a drag
perdónale disculpar esame eso va tira
Ricky Can you talk seriously I'm
Ricky Puedes hablar en serio que estoy
talking Javi I'm talking damn
hablando Javi que estoy hablando [__]
okay that utbh thing they came to me and
vale eso de utbh yo me vinieron y me lo
told me And I said Hey Hey how am I
dijeron Y yo le dije Oye Oye como se
supposed to get along with him I told him did you
supone que me llevo con él le dije te
start barking let's go on a live show and
has puesto a ladr arme en un directo y
he
él me
said to me p your audio p No I'm not going to
dijo p el audio tuyo p El no no voy a
put any audio here I'm putting
poner aquí ningún audio estoy poniendo
the capture I want to hear it I want to
la captura Quiero escuchar lo quiero
hear Javi I want to hear how he
escuchar Javi Quiero escuchar cómo le
says please don't do woof woof Press
dice porfa no haga guau
Play I know Sergio doesn't
guau Dale al Play sé que a Sergio le da
care Press Play Ricky I'm not going  to
igual Dale al Play Ricky que no voy a
put on an audio of Sergio or mine in a
ponerte un audio de Sergio ni mío en una
conversation that maybe we mentioned
conversación que a lo mejor mencionamos
other things and then he'll have the balls to
otras cosas y luego tendrá huevo a
ask me for the decy gadura I asked you for
pedirme el decy gadura Yo te he pedido
the audio of licy to shut up already the
el audio de licy que te calles ya el
audio of this and what do you answer Answer
audio de esto y qué contesta Contesta
something dude answer You're teaching me
algo tío contesta Tú me está enseñando
this c subject you
esto c tema
can't talk you don't talk dude you don't talk
no pue hablar no hablas tío no hablas
Ricky I said to Sergio It's true that
Ricky a Sergio le dije Es verdad que me
you barked at me live so that he can
has ladrado en directo para que me lo
tell me if it's true and he told me
diga a mí si es verdad y él me dijo que
no that p aio is it true that you said that
no que p aio se verdad que has dicho eso
Play the audio liar Play the
Pon el audio mentiroso Pon el
audio play it the aud in the audio
audio ponlo la Play el aud en el audio
tells me something about his personal life that
me dice una cosa de su vida personal que
you know is not known
tú sabes que no se sabe
yet okay you're right not his not yours yours
todavía vale tienes razón no el suyo no
your audio no because he
el tuyo el tuyo tu audio no porque
surely mentioned But look look
seguramente menciono Pero mira mira
mention what he mentions Look Ricky Look at
menciona el qué menciona Mira Ricky Mira
the screen before barking what he
la pantalla antes de ladrar qué
mentions have you started to L adame me in your
menciona te has puesto a L adarme en tu
free live they passed me this cap And
directo de free me han pasado esta cap Y
what does he answer me he won't tell it to you Well if you
qué me contesta él no te la adr Bueno si
want no I'm not going to tell you out of
quieres no no te lo voy a decir por
deference Sergio answer but if you do
deferencia Sergio respond pero si haces
something else behind  that upfront You
otra cosa por detrás que por delante
're making him look bad, not me No, not
Estás dejándolo mal tú a él no a mí No a
him at all Just know that
él nada no Simplemente que sepas que
going crying to your buddies who you
irle llorando a tus coleguitas a los que
think are good with you because
piensas que se bien contigo porque en
live it seems that it affects you when
directo da a entender que te afecta que
people tell you that he barks So you're freaking out about the
la gente te diga que ladra O sea que te
dog thing Rick of dogo Hey, they
raya lo de perro Rick de perroo Oye me
told me not to bark at you You shouldn't have said that
dicho no te ladrar No hubieras dicho eso
ri Ricky here leave if he's a person with
ri Ricky aquí dej si es una persona con
whom I'm supposed to be cordial
la que se supone que tengo cordialidad
if he starts messing with me I'm going to
si se pone a meterse conmigo le voy a
answer him but he's telling me
contestar pero él me está diciendo que
no if it doesn't affect you if it doesn't affect you no and no it's not
no si no te afecta si no afecta no y no
just that he tells me no it's that
solamente es que me diga que no es que
he takes So that there are no misunderstandings and he
el coge Para que no haya malentendidos y
edits it without me asking him so
lo edita sin que yo se lo pida entonces
if you're telling me that behind his back he
si tú me estás diciendo que por detrás
says something else you're making
dice otra cosa lo estás dejando mal tú a
him look bad because he saw Javi he says it because he
él porque ha visto Javi lo dita porque
saw that it affected you dude he sends it to
ha visto que te ha afectado tío lo manda
edit you see that when Sergio
editar tú vees que cuando a m Sergio
makes reference to something like bald with horns
haga referencia a calvo a cuernos a algo
I say something to him
yo le diga algo
dude laugh because that doesn't affect me being
tío risa porque eso no me afecta a ti
called a dog affects you that's why
que te digan perro te afecta por eso le
you ask me to remove it you just started
pides que lo quit acabas de ponerte a
saying dude something about Sergio to his face
decir tío una cosa de Sergio por la cara
leaving him in a bad way in which he is not here
dejándolo mal en la que él no está aquí
dude Yeah yeah yeah he's screwed Sergio
tío Sí sí sí está [__] Sergio mañana
wakes up tomorrow screwed dude But why are you doing
se levanta [__] tío Pero por qué haces
that dude why can't you defend yourself
eso tío tú por no te puedes defender
with me and with dala with me with dala And
conmigo y con dala conigo con dala Y por
why do you mention dala Chunky meat because
qué mencionas dala Cacho carne porque
all all the anger you have is what
tod toda la rabia que tienes es lo que
happened to you in the debate but what's coming
te pasó en el debate pero que viene
I'm talking to you okay come on let's
estora Estoy hablando contigo vale venga
talk lolco you today eh full
vamos a hablar lolco tú hoy eh full
lolco okay Ricky okay continue let's
lolco vale Ricky vale sigue vamos vamos
continue talking about your lies we
a seguir hablando de tus mentiras no
weren't into that or that the definitive one is
estábamos en eso o eso la definitiva es
that D one day said that
que D en su día dijo se le van a acabar
all his lies are going to end Which ones have to
Todas sus mentiras Cuáles se tienen que
end yet Which ones are left This is going
acabar todavía Cuáles han quedado Esto
to touch me again my ex my
va otra vez a tocarme a mi ex a mi
partner we talk yes what about yours
pareja hablamos si quees de la tuya
we talk about raed what do you want to talk about
hablamos de raed de qué quieres hablar
dude okay I want to talk about putting little
tío vale quiero hablar de hacerle poco
emphasis on the hitmen I was
hincapié a lo de los sicarios me ha
surprised how badly you bad that V
sorprendido lo mal que te mal que V
little incap what you've done dude ha I
poquito incap que has hecho tío ha
want you to talk to me about Why did you
quiero que me hables de Por qué te
make up the other day that  Dallas was
inventaste el otro día que Dallas estaba
on vacation in
de vacación en
Dubai Where is dasas Jai eh Right now I don't
Dubai Dónde está dasas Jai eh Ahora
know where he was but yesterday he
mismo no sé dónde andaba pero ayer
was in Madrid not at e's No yes
estaba en Madrid no en lo de e No sí
Well yesterday for one thing the doctor But
Bueno ayer por una cosa el médico Pero
where he is permanently You do know because I know that you
dónde está fijo Tú sí lo sabes porque sé
know where he is permanently in Dubai
que lo sabes dónde está fijo en Dubai
okay he is in Dubai perfect What is he doing in
vale está en Dubai perfecto Qué hace en
Dubai living no What is he doing Why is he
Dubai vivir no Qué hace Por qué está
living in Dubai and not in Spain or not in
viviendo en Dubai y no en España o no en
Andorra or not in Cyprus Why in Dubai
andorra o no en chipre Por qué en Dubai
ask him what I know because of the
pregúntaselo a él yo que sé por los
taxes it will be I don't know no the good yes
impuestos será No sé no lo bueno sí
because of taxes because he can pay with
pores impuestos porque puede pagar con
crypto I imagine I don't know what do you know
cripto me imagino No lo sé yo que sé tú
why are you in Andorra because of the
por qué estás en andorra por los
taxes it is much cheaper for me everything is
impuestos me sale mucho más barato todo
worth it well I imagine that it will be his
vale pues me imagino que lo suyo será
But why are you making up that he is not going to the
Pero por qué te inventas que no va al
debate with you and that day he was on
debate contigo y ese día estaba de
vacation in Andorra if you had made it up let's
vacaciones en andorra si te lo habías
see the first thing really messed up I have
inventado a ver lo primero teal liado yo
never said that he was on
no he dicho Nunca que estuviera de
vacation in Andorra like many I have
vacaciones en andorra como muchos he
said that he was on vacation in
dicho que estuviera de vacaciones en
Dubai in Dubai in Dubai
Dubai en Dubai en Dubai
Why did you make up that that he was on
Por qué te inventaste eso que estaba de
vacation he is or on vacation or
vacaciones está o de vacaciones o
doing interesting fiscal things
haciendo cositas Fiscales interesantes
there  because for another reason let's see you
allí porque por otro motivo a ver
posted a tweet literally saying
pusiste un tweet literalmente diciendo
Dallas He should have come to the
Dallas Tendría que haber venido hoy al
debate today he told me he couldn't for a
debate me dijo que no podía por un tema
medical reason and yet He's on vacation
médico y sin embargo Está de vacaciones
in Dubai and you posted a photo the night before with
en Dubai y pusiste una foto la noche an
his girlfriend yeah and the night before his girlfriend
su novia sí y la noche anterior su novia
uploaded a story at an event in Dubai
subo una historia en un evento en Dubai
Javi what do I do let's see what the photo is
Javi qué hago a ver cuál es la foto
pass it on damn the story of
pasársela [__] la historia de la
all the gossip accounts ao I
pusieron todas las cuentas salseo ao la
have it saved send it to you damn look
tengo guardado te la manden [__] mir
Look at the response on the tweet take off the
Mira la respuesta del twit quita la
camera and look at the response on the tweet in
cámara y mira la respuesta del twit por
case you smell a dick See if she
si te huele una [__] Mira a ver si la
finds it there's a story of Elisy a
encuentra hay historia de elisy una
screenshot of Elis From the day before of The
captura de Elis Del día anterior de Lo
Doctor's Thing the one who is at an event it will be
del Médico la que está en un evento será
crypto it will be a party maybe a
cripto será una fiesta a saber un evento
public event What event was it I know an
público Qué evento era yo que sé un
event from the day before they looked at
evento del día anterior a que le mirasen
a tumor or something in the hospital in Spain I'm going
un tumor o algo en el hospital de España
to ask what hital are they in Madrid
vo a preguntar mo hital están en Madrid
esp Wait wait what event
espa Espera espera Qué evento
was Javi I don't know are you saying it's
era Javi Yo qué sé estás diciendo que es
an event in Dubai no [ __ ] if they are
un evento en Dubai que no [__] si están
in Dubai and upload a photo at an event I
en Dubai y sube una foto en un evento
understand that no  it's an event in marquees
entiendo que no es un evento en marquees
but how do you know that that
pero cómo sabes que ese evento en
specific event was in Dubai because it's a day
concreto era en Dubai porque es un día
that Javier was in Dubai and why do you
que estaba en Dubai Javier y por qué
know it's in Dubai where does it say
sabes que está en Dubai dónde lo pone
because the day he drove to Madrid was
porque el día que condujo a Madrid fue
the next one he made the [ __ ] video
el siguiente que hizo el [__] vídeo
saying that they had been traveling for 16 hours
diciendo que llevaban 16 horas de viaje
[ __ ] he said it and that's short [ __ ] that
[__] lo dijo él y eso es corto cabrón el
event was in Spain Ricky I know
evento ese era en España Ricky yo sé
which one it is and why the [ __ ] did they drive 16
cuál es y para qué [__] condujeron 16
hours in Spain From what city what city
horas en España De qué ciudad qué ciudad
16 hours in the car jier Ricky from one day
16 horas de coche jier Ricky de un día
to the next but I don't know
para otro pero no me
city what city obviously the
ciudad qué ciudad evidentemente el
event was not in Spain obviously
evento no era en España evidentemente
ricki you make it up you make it up with a
ricki te inventas te inventas con una
photo from April not with a photo from
foto de abril no con una foto del
Sunday you made it up the other day
domingo te inventas el otro día en
live that that photo is not from those
directo que esa foto no es de esas
vacations of course not but the thing is that
vacaciones por supuesto que no pero es
d hasn't uploaded a photo of Dubai this
que d no ha subido foto de Dubai esta
season [ __ ] So how do you know what
temporada [__] Entonces cómo sabes qué
day he is in Dubai and that you didn't just
día está en Dubai y que no me acabas de
tell me that he lives there you just doxed what
decir que vive allí acabas de doxear lo
you Ricky let's focus and answer me I'm
tú Ricky vamos a centrarnos y contestame
going to be honest Yes, when
a te voy a ser sincero Sí yo cuando
I say that he is in Dubai s I already know  what is he
pongo que está en Dubai s Ya sé que está
seeing in Dubai I already knew this I
viendo en Dubai Ya lo sabía esto te lo
asked you so you can confirm it and
preguntado para que lo confirmas tú y
then you can't get angry at him Look
luego no puedas echar bronca de Mira
how he doxes me isn't it great that he doxes
cómo me doxea no es super que doxea
so now that you know you'll
entonces ahora que lo sabes sabrás
also know that the shirtless photo is in
también que esa foto sin camiseta es en
Dubai right it's not from this time But it is
Dubai verdad no es de esta época Pero es
in Dubai Ricky okay Javi Can you
en Dubai Ricky vale Javi Puedes
answer please put a tweet It's
responder por fa pones un tweet Es que
very sen it's very simple and you
es muy sen es muy sencillo y le das la
turn it around so as not to answer no but it's that you do
vuelta para no contestar no pero es que
n't want to answer it's a coward
no quieres responder es muy [__] esto
why do you make this up the one who
por qué te lo inventas el que me
made me up got scared and gave me 200 excuses
invento se asustó y me puso 200 excusas
the last excuse was a medical problem
la última excusa fue un problema médico
but right now He's on vacation in
pero ahora mismo Está de vacaciones en
Dubai he wasn't on vacation in Dubai And
Dubai no estaba de vacaciones en Dubai Y
what is Dubai doing at an event that
qué está haciendo Dubai en un eventi que
the girlfriend uploads photos from the day before what she was
la novia sube fotos del día anterior que
doing well that the photo
estaba haciendo bueno eso de que la foto
is from that same moment you don't
es de ese mismo momento lo sabes tú no
know it's a [ __ ] Story that you upload
quillo es una un [__] Story que subes
when you go out partying t V handsome and you
cuando sales de fiesta t V guapo y lo
upload it damn it's a Story there isn't even a
subes [__] es un Story no hay ni un
post damn And that is it is it's at the same
post [__] Y eso es es en el mismo
moment because you say so Oh [ __ ]
momento porque lo dices tú Ay [__]
detective dude  40 years old Javi it's whatever
detective tío de 40 años Javi es lo que
you want Look, it's done, let's finish it's
tú quieras Mira ya está vamos a acabar
whatever you want but why don't you
es lo que tú quieras pero por qué no
answer and I'll put you open your mouth and it won't work for you, that's it, answer
contestas y te pono abre la boquita y no
dude, you don't
te cunde ya está contestas tío no
answer if you don't answer, I'm
contestas si no contestas tú te estoy
asking you, do you know that photo of D, that
preguntando sabes que la foto de D esa
's in Dubai, yes or no, the one with the t-shirt, that
es en Dubai sí o no la de camiseta esa
photo? No, now okay, it's in Dubai or it's not in Dubai, it's
foto No ahora vale es en Dubai o no es
a photo in Dubai from April,
en Dubai es una foto en Dubai de abril
okay, in Dubai from April, perfect, in the
vale en Dubai de abril perfecto yo en el
TT I say that he's on vacation in Dubai
TT digo que está de vacaciones en Dubai
since he hasn't uploaded photos in Dubai from this
como no ha subido fotos en Dubai de esta
season, I'm uploading the last photo that he uploaded
temporada subo la última foto que subió
in Dubai which is an extract from a ril from
en Dubai que es un extracto de un ril de
Li there ri Ricky but let's see Ricky, you
Li allí ri Ricky pero vamos a ver Ricky
were lying, they caught
estabas mintiendo están pillado
lying, you make it up and that's it, say it.
mintiendo te lo inventas y ya está dilo
Hey, about your grandfather tonight, he doesn't
Oye lo del abuelo esta noche que no se
take his pills, something else, yes, yes, a
toma las pastillas otra cosa sí que sí
lot of insults, a lot of insults because of his
muchos insultos muchos insultos por la
age and all that stuff, but it's
edad y todo el rollo peroo es par
insulting, okay, Ricky, but this? This
insultante vale Ricky pero que esto Esto
is a lie of yours, that's why the lady didn't
es una mentira tuya por eso la señora no
know that it affected you. That's it, I'm
sabía que te afectaba lo de la Ya está
not telling you any more, it's but this is a
no te digo más está pero que esto es una
lie  that you make up not for
mentira que tú te inventas no para
filthy you filthy me not like you said no
guarro tú guarro yo no como tú decías no
What a lie that he wasn't in Dubai nor was he on
Qué mentira que no estaba en Dubai ni
vacation he had a
estaba de vacaciones estaba con un
medical problem yes a medical problem
problema médico sí un problema médico
that was driving him within
que le estuvo conduciendo dentro de
Spain for an event that was there 16
España por un evento que fue allí 16
hours going around I suppose all of
horas dándole vueltas Supongo a to
Andalusia and Galicia not in streaks or what
Andalucía y Galicia no en rachitas o qué
Javi what he's talking what he's talking about himself in his
Javi qué habla qué habla el mismo en su
video he says I've been driving for 16 hours
vídeo dice llevo 16 horas conduciendo
from what [ __ ] city in Spain from
tal desde qué [__] ciudad de españa de
one event you go to another you go to Madrid that
un evento vas a otra vas a Madrid que t
you you to the center with 16 hours of with no
tú al centro con 16 horas de con ninguna
time what the [ __ ] man are you falling but
vez de qu [__] tío se te cae la pero
Ricky is that let's see or rather are you
Ricky es que vamos a ver o sea me estás
telling me that you're telling me that
diciendo que me estás diciendo no se
nothing is falling Ricky don't repeat
está cayendo nada Ricky no repitas mal
things wrong that no no no they are not going to
las cosas que no no no se van a
become a truth look how I
convertir en una verdad mira cómo te
make you not answer Look how I ask you as a
hago no responder Mira có te hago por
question where was I Where was Javi
pregunta dónde estaba Dónde estaba Javi
Where was I the day before the
Dónde estaba d el día de antes del
hospital Where was well I would leave wherever I
hospital Dónde estaba pues saldría de
was and take the car and I
donde estuviera y cogería el coche y
would be on my way to Madrid like he
estaría de camino a Madrid como él te
told you and And from wherever and wherever I was you
dijo y Y de dónde y dónde estuviera tú
are his friend you know where  I was in
eres su colega tú lo sabes dónde estaba
Dalas to drive 16 hours we
Dalas para conducir 16 horas lo sabemos
all know Where was I if the day before I
todos Dónde estaba si el día antes
was in Dubai or was I somewhere else
estaba en Dubai o estaba en otro lado
that I was in Spain okay I was in
que que estaba en España vale estaba en
Spain I was in Spain and why did he have to
España estaba en España y por qué tuvo
drive 16 hours from Spain to
que conducir 16 horas desde España a
Madrid Why
Madrid Por qué
tell me why Well that's why I don't know
cuéntame por Pues eso pues yo que sé dio
why I would stop anywhere I know the
porque pararía donde sea yo que sé la
route man I'm going to hurt you with this
trayectoria tío harte mal con esto
buddy but it has no explanation there's
compadre pero que no tiene explicación
no place that you can do
que no hay ningún sitio que te hacerte
16 hours by car to Madrid from
16 horas de coche hasta Madrid des de
Spain that there isn't one that there isn't one but
España que no lo hay que no lo hay pero
let's see Ricky well it will be 16 in total
vamos a ver Ricky pues serán 16 en total
and it will be eight and eight for the return No I don't
y serán ocho y ocho para la vuelta No yo
know I have no [ __ ] idea I Andalusian tour they have
que sé no tengo ni [__] idea yo tura
made it tourist Andalusia I was going I wasn't going
andal han hecho turística Andalucía iba
Ricky I wasn't going okay But
yo no iba Ricky yo no iba vale Pero
anyway come on important topic
bueno de todas maneras venga tema
although even if I was man Right now you
aunque aunque estuviera hombre Ahora
're laughing putting it in doubt
mismo te estás riendo poniéndolo en duda
putting it in doubt when
poniéndolo en duda cuándo
Sorry in this TT you're not
Perdona en este TT tú no lo estás
putting it in doubt Ah that t put it in
poniendo en duda Ah que ese t ponerlo en
doubt When is that tweet Javi from
duda de Cuándo es ese tweet Javi de
When is that tweet of mine the day before
Cuándo es ese twit mío el del día antes
the 6th  from the 6th and on the 6th he
del día 6 del día 6 y el día 6 de ha
said that I gave him a tumor But you
dicho que le hici ti un tumor Pero tú lo
were questioning it or not no I haven't
estabas poniendo en duda o no no no he
said anything about a tumor because nobody
dicho nada de un tumor porque nadie
knew he had a tumor or that
sabía que tenía un tumor ni que le
anything was wrong with him he told you a problem a
pasaba nada te dijo un problema un
medical problem a medical problem
problema médico un problema médico me
sounds familiar excuse of I'm sorry I have soccer
suena excusa de Lo siento tengo fútbol
Yes when he told me I'm not going to the debate because of
Sí cuando me dijo no voy a el debate por
a problem I told him put it on the day you
un problemtico le digo ponlo el día que
want no I can't it's going to be a problem
quiera no no puedo va a ser un problema
for a long time you spent the whole
de mucho tiempo te pegaste toda la
week well the week you didn't spend the
semana bueno la semana no te pegaste los
10 days
10 días
mentioning let's see if I have the
mencionando vamos a ver si tengo los
clips let's see if I have the clips let's
clips lo vamos a ver si tengo los cl a
see put it put it put it Put it on let's see I
ver ponlo ponlo ponlo Pon lo vamos a ver
ask you a question you spent from the
te hago una pregunta te pegaste desde el
day of the debate until yesterday mentioning in
día del debate hasta ayer mencionando en
all your videos even in the one about
todos tus vídeos hasta en el en el de
peace Give Dallas that if he didn't want to
paz Dad a Dallas que si no ha querido
come that if he messed up on me in
venir que si se ha cagado de mí en el de
Abi's what Abi's video What are you saying in
Abi qué vídeo de Abi Qué dices en el de
Didy's Ricky calm down it's because you
didy Ricky tranquilízate que es que
're very nervous but if you're the one
estás muy nervioso pero si eres tú el
who doesn't vocalize what you're telling me
que no vocaliza queé me estás contando
no And you vocalize a lot Ricky But
no Y tú vocaliza mucho Ricky Pero por
why AC say to Babi buddy you're
qué AC decir para Babi compadre estás
very nervous Ricky Calm down
muy nervioso Ricky Cálmate que no pasa
nothing's wrong really listen to me don't worry
nada de verdad escúchame no te agobies
there we've got you don't worry
ya está te hemos pillado no te agobies
what you've got Ricky well you
el qué has pillado Ricky pues que no
're not able to tell me from which city he's
eres capaz de decirme desde qué ciudad
going to Madrid in 16 rii and what the [ __ ] do I know well how do
se va a Madrid en 16 rii y yo qué [__]
n't you know mouth shut
sé pues como no lo sabes boca cerrada
dog mouth shut but Shut up the [ __ ] filthy
perro boca cerrada pero Cállate la [__]
mouth you have like the dick
boca sucia que tienes tú como la [__]
dilipa that you invent that he's on
dilipa que te inventas que está de
vacation in Dubai Oh lowering That's how I
vacaciones en Dubai Ay rebajando Así me
like it dude to the level of the kids
gusta quillo al nivel de los chavalitos
that he's on vacation in Dubai But
que está de vacaciones en Dubai Pero
because you've come out of your dick about
porque te has salido de la [__] lo de
the dirty dick that Where does it come from but
la [__] sucia eso De dónde sale pero
apart from that it's not only that you invent
aparte no solamente es que te inventes
this thing about the vacation that Cos that you
esto de las vacaciones que Cos que te
invent the restraining order and you
inventas la orden de alejamiento y no la
haven't mentioned it again Come on then
has vuelto a mencionar Hala Venga pues
Okay we're in the order The next thing is
Vale estamos en la orden Lo próximo es
my ex I'll give you a heads up so you don't
mi ex te voy adelantando para que no se
forget the topics come on we're already
te olvides los temas venga estamos ya
for the order what else Eh he hasn't
por la orden qué más Eh no le ha vuelto
mentioned her again because the Coward didn't have the
a mencionar porque el Cobarde no tenía
balls to come for her for  that hasn't been
huevo de venía por ellaa por eso no ha
mentioned again Ah they keep
vuelto a mencionar Ah que sigen
maintaining that you had a
manteniendo que tenías una orden de
restraining order man Because the [ __ ] audio thing
espérate tío Porque lo del [__] audio me
is really pissing me off but you can't imagine they
está tocando los [__] pero no te
keep mentioning you
puedes hacer una idea siguen mencionando
keep claiming that you have a
sigues afirmando que tienes una orden de
restraining order with Dallas no I've never
alejamiento con Dallas no nunca he
signed that What do you mean no Ricky yes I
firmado eso Cómo que no Ricky si yo te
've clicked on you saying restraining order no that it
he puesto click diciendo atamiento no
's requested Yes yes in
que está solicitada Sí sí en instancia
higher instances you told me the last call
superiores me dijiste la última llamada
correct memory bu boy you still
correcto memoria bu chico lo sigues
maintain it no
manteniendo no
clown it's a little bit edgy that one I think the
payaso está raya un poquillo esa yo creo
dog thing does touch your heart a little bit
que lo de perro sí que te toca un poco
Ricki you still maintain it I don't maintain it I
la fibra ricki lo sigues manteniendo no
maintain it okay And
lo mantengo lo mantengo s vale Y
then when you challenged him to a debate in
entonces cuando le retaste a debatir en
person that it was a
persona que era una orden de
restraining order for being 40 years old This is
acercamiento para tener 40 años Esta es
original but you already tried it when it happened
original pero ya la probaste cuando pasó
and it wasn't funny I should have turned off
y no fue divertida debería haber cortado
the tap with this joke because it didn't go down
el Grifo con esta broma porque no entró
well here or in Latin America listen to me eh No no no I'm not
bien aquí ni en latam escúchame eh No no
requesting a restraining order
no no le solicito orden de acercamiento
but I have the power to see it without
pero tengo potestad para poder verlo sin
any problem Hey hey and the police stations
ningún problema Oye oye y las comisarías
are closed now not as of  the
están cerradas ahora no a partir de las
3 at the administrative level Yes they are
3 a nivel administrativo Sí están
closed you can confirm it on Google or
cerradas lo puedes confirmar en Google o
get there the purge, that's
llegarte tú allí la purga aquello
not the purge what you were before
no la purga lo que ha sido tú antes
crazy lost that has been the
loquito perdido eso sí que ha sido la
purge well well when I laugh at
purga bien bueno cuándo me río del tumor
Lycium's tumor go on that he doesn't answer me Look,
de licio va que no me lo responde Mira
well it's time that well now I know the
pues ya está la hora que pues ya se a la
time to go if I have to go visit you
hora que ir si te tengo que ir a visitar
eh come on let's go close one that was
eh vamos vamos que cerr una que te
closed Do me a favor no no but If you
cerrada Hazme favor no no pero Si
close the police stations at 3 in the
cierras las comisarias a las 3 de la
afternoon from 3 in the afternoon I
tarde a partir de de las 3 de la tarde
can go look for you let's go let's see a
puedo ir a buscarte vamos a vamos a ver
clip of yours from the live setting what an
clip tuyo del directo poniendo vaya
example you're giving Ha I would be
ejemplo estás dando Ja me daría
ashamed to see with your age and I would be
vergüenza ver con tu edad y me daría
very ashamed man I'm telling you man
mucha vergüenza tío te lo digo de hombre
to man Eh well well man that you
a hombre Eh bueno bueno de hombre eso ti
t is still you're still half c you're still
t todavía está todavía estás a medio c
half c listen to me already and
todavía estás a medio c escúchame yaas y
everything No if I have a while left to me
todo No si me queda un rato a mí
listen very screwed up very screwed up the image
escucha muy [__] muy [__] la imagen
that you're giving in many areas
que estás dando para en muchos ámbitos
eh In this live very screwed up man I'm telling you the
eh En este directo muy jodida tío te lo
truth that people remember you are
verdad que la gente te recuerde estas
pal [ __ ] up
pal [__]
riy  Ricky you are screwed since what they
riy Ricky [__] estás tú desde la que
gave you in the debate the other day
te dieron en el debate el otro día que
is that you are
es que estás
deate every day not to the owner Yes or yes you
deate todos los días no al dueño Sí o sí
mention it You will be his [ __ ] because
lo mencionas Tú serás su perr tú porque
even in the
hasta en el
video even in Didi's video you
vídeo hasta en el vídeo de Didi lo
brought it out you are sick you are obsessed
sacaste estás enfermo estás obsesionado
you saw I nailed it You didn't see that I nailed it you
viste lo clavé No viste que lo clavé lo
mentioned it in the video in case
mencionaste en el vídeo de por si
someone s in case someone in case someone
alguien s por si alguien por si alguien
has no context I said Dalas is going to be the
no tiene contexo dije Dalas va a ser el
typical one who uploaded a video saying they have
típico que subiera un vídeo diciendo te
deceived you about Didi and what they have
han engañado sobre Didi e lo que te han
told you is a lie indeed his video
dicho es mentira efectivamente su vídeo
is condemned but it is not because of what he
es está condenado pero no es por lo que
told you people are laughing at him
te contado la gente está riendo de él
because anyway it is quite eh that I realized
porque en fin es bastante eh que me di
that you mention it has balls what you tell me that I
que mencionas tiene [__] el qué que
mention Dallas
me digas a mí que menciono a Dallas
has balls with the 82 channels that he
tiene [__] con los 82 canales que
has talking about the owner my channel is about
tiene hablando del dueño mi canal trata
Tell me does it seem wrong to you Sorry do you think
Dime te parec mal Perdona te parecen mal
all the channels that are about d
todos los canales que se tratan sobre d
no it does not seem wrong to me how you do it I
no no me parece mal como lo haces tú me
would be ashamed in your situation to do what you
daría vergüenza en tu situación hacer lo
do I would be very
que haces me daría mucha
ashamed to do what I do that
vergüenza hacer lo que hago que
humiliate you take you out for a
humillarte sacarte a
walk throw in your face CJ intimidated
pasear echarte en cara CJ amedrentado a
a girl because she owed you 200 euros
una niña porque te debía 200 eur
sad that he owed you 200 euros If you
triste que te debía 200 euritos Si
want I'll give it to you so you don't
quieres yo te lo doy para que no
threaten the girls anymore man you're a
amenaces más a las chavalas hombre que
few years older than him tell your
le sacas unos cuantos años contar a tu
wife If you want I'll give it to you tell
mujer Si quieres yo te lo doy contar a
your wife what you can give of yourself and for what you
tu mujer lo que sabe dar de ti y por lo
do the videos you make to see
que haces los vídeos que haces a ver
Tell me Tell
Cuéntamelo
me give it to me give it to me and Tell me I'll tell you do
Cuéntamelo dámelo dámelo y Cuéntamelo Te
you want to know what he's
lo cuento quieres saber lo que va
saying about you do
diciendo las de ti quieres que lo suerte
you want me to luck Yes yes I want you to know Yes also it
Sí sí quiero que lo sepas Sí además que
's corroborated by witnesses who have
está corroborado por testigos que han
been with him do you want me to luck
estado con él quieres que te lo suerte
no no but I want
no no pero quiero
proof proof I have the testimony
pruebas pruebas Yo tengo el testimonio
of a person who knows him who has been a
de una persona que lo conoce que ha sido
very good friend of his that the
muy amiga suya que la
delox delox delo has been a friend of his
delox delox delo ha sido un amigo suyo
Yes yes his uncle Ricky I want buys we
Sí sí suyo tío Ricky quiero pras
count Yes yes s that you like the party man
contamos Sí sí s que te va la marcha tío
yes which one Well you like the party that
sí cuál Bueno te va la marcha de la que
nobody knows about at home you like the party that nobody
no se enteran en casa te va la marcha de
knows about  they find out at home d he knows it he
la que no se enteran en casa d lo sabe
can prove it and he didn't
lo puede probar y no le ha hecho falta
even need to make you sign anything he just has
ni hacerte firmar una [__] le basta
to tell you I have this and he knows it so be
con decirte tengo esto y lo sabe así que
careful with what you say because the
cuidado con lo que suelta porque de la
complaint has you scared and it makes you
denuncia te tiene cagadito y te da
afraid to take any false step
cosita a tirar cualquier paso en falso
so that he trains at home of what you
para que se entrene en casa de lo que
've been doing as he knows you have
has ido haciendo como él lo sabe tienes
confidence and you trust him it pays a lot to
confianza y confias en él te renta mucho
be on his side because if not not
estar de su lado porque si no no
only will the channel fall on you
solamente se te cae el canal se te caen
many more things will fall on you the hitmen I
muchas más cosas la de los sicarios me
believed it more Ricky and the order and the order
lo creía más Ricky y la orden y la orden
this there is no
esto no hace
need for the order the restraining order
falta la orden la orden de alejamiento
more man it's such a lie like
má hombre es que es tan mentira como
point number one I didn't make an agreement with
punto número uno no hice acuerdo con
Dallas not even when children la conil
Dallas ni siquiera cuando hios la conil
and point number two I said that I didn't
y punto número dos he dicho que no
sign said d doesn't know anything like that about Ah
firmado dich d no sabe nada así sobre Ah
no he doesn't know anything well I think so no no I
no no sabe nada bueno yo creo que sí no
think so Well I think he
no yo creo que no Bueno yo creo que algo
knows something I think Yes well You think that
sabe yo creo Sí bueno Tú crees que las
police stations close at three and you can't
comisarias cierran a las tres y no se
report them you're a crack Yes yes deln in
denunciar eres un crack Sí sí deln en
several aspects but a crack Ricki
varios aspectos pero un crack ricki
you're pathetic well at least  I wasn't
estás dando pena bueno por lo menos no
embarrassed yes you do yes you do man eh
di vergüenza sí la das sí la das tío eh
Tell me more details about that how is my
Dime más detalles sobre eso cómo me va
march going in threesomes in orgies no no I'll
la marcha en tríos en [__] no no yo me
stick with that and I'll stay completely calm
quedo con eso y me quedo tranquilísimo
since the party is celebrated there
ya que se celebre la fiesta por allí
but whatever without further invention and period and
pero o sea sin más invent y punto y
period whatever you want Stay with that
punto lo que tú quieras Quédate con eso
If you want [ __ ] wait I'm
Si tú quieres [__] espérate estoy
falling anyway It's the first time that you find
cayendo igual Es la primera vez que te
out what d talks about this about you
enteras de qué d habla de esto de ti
maybe it's the first man let's see It's that you know you know You know
igual es la primera hombre a ver Es que
what happens Ricky that
sabes sabes Sabes qué pasa Ricky que
when you dasas he doesn't have any thing like that
cuando dasas no tiene ninguna cosa así
about me well I'm completely
sobre mí pues estoy completamente
calm Ah no And why don't you have an opinion about
tranquilo Ah no Y por qué no opina de la
ra's mother And why don't you have an opinion about the
madre de ra Y por qué no opina de las
things opado yes opinionated And what do you think about the
cos opado si opinado Y qué opina del
message yes about what he sent to you what do you
mensaje sí de lo que le puso a ti qué te
think anyone can have an opinion
parece que puede opinar cualquier
about that message I'm asking you
persona de ese mensaje Te pregunto
because I don't know I don't consume your content
porque no lo sé No Consumo tu contenido
what do you think let's
qué opin a
see you just told me that he
ver me acaba me acabas de decir que que
doesn't consume Ricky No Ricky can I
no consume Ricky No Ricky te puedo
talk to you or can you or do you have to act stupid
hablar o puedes o tienes que hacer tonto
so the kids can respond
para que los chiquillos Puedes responder
I would like you to respond  you just said you
me gustaría que respond acabas de decir
just said at 27 years old that you have
acabas de decir con 27 años que tienes
clown that you don't follow my
payasito que no sigues mi
content no I don't know your content the
contenido no no conso tu contenido la
truth is the only thing Ricky last night yesterday
verdad lo único que Ricky anoche ayer
you threatened this girl from Twitter
amenazaste a la chavala esta de Twitter
so that she wouldn't tell wouldn't continue telling
para que no contara no siguiera contando
what your girlfriend did to you What Sorry What What What What What What you
lo que te hizo tu novia Qué Perdón Qué
threatened her with
Qué Qué Qué Qué la amenazaste con
complaints yes Well we'll have to catch me
denuncias sí Pues habrá que capturar mí
talking to her about that run Put it
hablando con ella de eso corre Ponla
right now show it in pants I give you
ahora mismo enséñala en pant te doy
permission yes yes I give you permission show it yes no no I'm not
permiso sí sí te doy permiso enséñala sí
saying it I show it come on
no no no lo digo yo enséñala venga
Show me my threat ens Say it I'll say it
Enséñame mi amenaza ens Di lo digo yo
Well I'm going to put the choruses for your
Bueno yo que le poner los coros a tu
wife There we are Well but you don't have the cu
mujer Ahí estamos Bueno pero los cu no
at the moment listen to me well talk We
los tienes tú de momento escúchame bueno
would have to see We would have to see
hab Habría que ver Habría que ver por
how this is over there
allí como está el esto
Javier We would have to see how the
Javier Habría que ver cómo está el
stable is According to your buddy dala We would have to
establo Según tu coleguita dala Habría
see how it is We would have to see when I
que ver cómo está Habría que ver cuando
have it I say that Shameless man is that
lo tengo yo dice que Sinvergüenza tío es
you're making it up because you don't
que te lo estás inventando porque no
have  exit like the
tienes salida como la orden de
restraining order Ricky I already invented invented Yes yes
alejamiento Ricky Ya ya invent invent Sí
Ricky Why did the girl threaten to
sí Ricky Por qué la chavala amenac con
report her Yes yes yes let's see it let's see the
denunciarla Sí sí sí a verlo a ver la
capture no but we just saw your modus
captura no pero acabamos de ver t modus
operandi with other girls with this one it is
operandi con otras chavalas con esta
also called modus no modes modus Yes yes
también se dice modus no modos modus Sí
If you can do all the
sí Si tú puedes hacer todas las
stupid things you want but that you
tonterías que tú quieras pero que la
threaten her I'm not correcting you that at
amenazas no estoy corrigiéndote que con
40 years old noar [ __ ] you would
40 años noar [__] lo
do it it's because we've already seen it we
harías es porque ya lo hemos visto
just put your capture okay I would do it
acabamos de poner captur tuya vale lo
not done done I've done it
haría no hecho hechoo lo he hecho
Prove it anything Before
Demuéstralo cualquier cosa Antes de
going back to before going back to admit
volver a antes de volver a a reconocer
that you were cuckolded because you have
que tean cuckeado porque tienes un ego
such a small ego Ricky so small
así de pequeñito Ricky así de pequeñito
How come you didn't show up until 6 in
Cómo es que no apareciste hasta las 6 de
the afternoon you woke up At 6 in the
la tarde te despertaste A las 6 de la
afternoon yesterday champion literally literally
tarde ayer campeón literalmente
Yeah well in the morning
literalmente Sí pues por la mañana
I was so over Dallas of course at the
estaba tando sobre Dallas claro a la
time I went to bed [ __ ]
hora que me acosté jilipolla
Of course of course of course Ricky of course
Claro claro claro claro Ricky claro a
what time did
qué hora
you show up you showed up just when
sobre apareciste apareciste justo cuando
the girl  He denied I appear because
la chavala lo desmintió aparezco porque
my father wakes me up saying no I
me despierta mi pare diciendo no entre
came in about Twitter no and I say yes it came to me
lo de Twitter no y digo sí me ha llegado
through waves of sleep and he starts to tell me
por ondas de sueño y me empieza a contar
and I say how how how he talked to the
y digo cómo cómo cómo habló con la
girl the girl apologized because
chavala la chavala Se disculpó porque
when she saw The real screenshots that
cuando vio Las capturas reales que le
Amanda happened to him she said okay Forgive my boyfriend
pasó Amanda dijo vale Perdona a mi novio
he's a slob to my boyfriend before
es un guarro a mi novio antes de
changing you before changing the subject and
cambiarte antes de cambiarte de tema y
talking to you about your partner come on finish
hablarte yo de tu pareja venga termina
this double chin that I gave you and now we
esta papada que te he pegado y ahora ya
change but Ricky don't
cambiamos el pero Ricky no te
proclaim yourself it's very sad no
autoproclamadas que da mucha penita no
no the audience will proclaim it to me you don't
no me lo proclamará la audiencia tú no
worry Yes yes your kid you
te preocupes Sí si tu chiquillo tú le
put the little bit I put in it and they're going to tell you what
pones el poco yo y te van a decir lo que
you want but listen to me r The M of
tú quieras pero escúchame r El M de
dog works better the Emi of dog fun
perro funciona mejor el Emi de perro fun
hurts more yes phew listen to me Ricky
duele más sí buf escúchame Ricky
eh You're going to give me you're going to give me details of
eh Me vas a dar me vas a dar detalles de
the horns that I put on and the march
los cuernos que yo pongo y de la marcha
that I like no No if it's an invention you
que a mí me va no No si es un invent ya
've already said it you're not an invention Don't
lo has dicho tú no es un invent No te
worry about the one who should care  the one who should
preocupes a la que le tiene que importar
care isn't you the one who should
al que le tiene que importar no es a ti
care is Ju it's not
al que le tiene que importar es Ju no es
you but show me something no that I have to
a ti pero enséñame algo no que te tengo
show you testimony yes I don't have
que enseñar testimonio sí no tengo
permission Javi I would like I would like I hit
permiso Javi ya quisiera yo ya quisiera
play I would like but of
yo darle al Play ya quisiera yo pero de
my own of my privacy I give you I give you
de lo mío de mi intimidad te doy te doy
permission yours yes of yours it's that man what's
permiso lo tuyo sí de lo tuyo es que tío
strong no no you can't give me
lo fuerte no no tú no me puedes dar
permission the person who told me
permiso la persona que me ha contado
this doesn't want it to be known that they
esto no quiere que se sepa que ha
told this because who told you call them
contado esto porque quién te ha contado
Who told you call them
llámala Quién te la ha contado llámala
No they won't want to they won't want to call them
No no va a querer no va a querer llámala
that person must must be listening to
esa persona debe debe estar escuchando
this live So write to me and
este directo Así que que me escriba y me
tell me if they want to tell it but they won't want to I'm
diga si quiere contarlo pero no va a
telling you they won't want to
querer ya te digo que no va a querer
because they're not in a position to get their
porque no está en una posición para
hands dirty they're not but they have
pringar las manos no lo está pero sí ha
been very close to the circle they had and
estado muy cerca del círculo ha tenido y
have a very good relationship and they have heard
tiene muy buena relación y ha escuchado
your owner say things that you wouldn't
a tu dueño decir cositas que no te
like and I'm realizing now
gustaría y me estoy dando cuenta ahora
if you're not making a fool of yourself you're
si no estás tirándote el papelón que lo
doing very well I'm
estás haciendo muy bien Me esty dando
realizing that  is that you're finding out
cuenta de que es que te estás enterando
now that you talk about them like that about you, you're
ahora de que las hablas as de ti te está
finding out now, of course it would be it would be
enterando ahora claro es que sería sería
completely it would be completely
sería completamente sería completamente
false because my son, I'm 40
falso porque hijo mío yo es que con 40
years old, as you well know, what I'm
años como tú bien sabes es que que te
telling you, my God, I don't even know how to talk to
digo Dios mío yo ya no sé ni hablar con
women anymore, I'm telling you that if you
mujeres con eso te lo digo a no s que te
're referring to a sweet threesome or if
estés refiriendo a un trío goloso o a no
they're 19 years old, that's it, that's it.
s que tengan 19 años que eso sí eso sí
Yes, man, that's what you're talking about,
Sí hombre eso me estás hablando hace una
something from a decade ago in a
cosa de hace una década en una crisis de
marriage crisis, clown, that I told you
matrimonio payaso que te lo conté por
privately, women, of
privado mujeres
course, if you're going to throw
claro es que si me vas a echar en cara
something from a decade ago in my face, I can throw it
algo de hace una década te puedo echar
in your face when you were on a
yo en cara cuando fuiste un programa de
television program and said women in
televisión y dijiste las mujeres en
Crdoba throw themselves at me,
Córdoba se me tiran a los brazos por
please yes, please, haar, that's what I
favor sí Por favor haar de eso me
love, okay? Show me what And
encanta prr vale Enséñame a lo que Y a
what I'm into, no, no, I'm not
lo que me va la marcha a mí no no te lo
going to show you, I'm doing much better than
voy a enseñar me va mucho mejor que esta
tonight you go to bed with your little eyes open
noche te acuesta con el ojito abierto
thinking about me, they've said Ricky I
pensando en mi han contado Ricky No
can't think that because it's completely
puedo pensar eso porque es completamente
made up, I think so, I think it's going  give
invent yo creo que sí yo creo que va dar
c talk I think so but oh well it's
c hablar yo creo que sí pero bueno está
fine me man, as long as you go to
bien yo tío yo con que tú te vayas hoy a
sleep tonight with the bowl of feed Med
dormir con el cuenco de pienso Med
saying [ __ ] Ricky No matter how much you
diciendo [__] Ricky Por más que me
call me a dog and no matter how much you insult me and say stupid things you
digas perro y por más que me insultes y
're making a
digas tonterías estás haciendo el
fool of yourself you have something to show me or let's
ridículo tienes algo que mostrarme o
go to your girlfriend Come on you want to talk about
vamos a tu novia Hala que quieres hablar
my girlfriend yes of course about my girlfriend you want to
de mi novia sí por supuesto de mi novia
talk for sure Yes of course you have
quieres hablar seguro Sí por supuesto
a problem with what with you with you with
tienes algún problema con qué contigo
you I have to be careful careful careful Yeah yes of course with you I have to be
contigo contigo tengo que tener cuidado
careful yes yes if
contigo tengo que tener cuidado sí sí si
you have won my thing you'll have the balls to
tú has vencias lo mío te los [__] de
make sure that I can mention
de asegurarte que yo pueda mencionar los
yours yes yes you can do it the only thing
tuyos sí si tú lo puedes hacer lo único
that happens is that I can blow your glasses off
que pasa es que te puedo volar las gafas
Ah well then be careful with what you
Ah pues entonces ten cuidadito con lo
say you yes what Are you going to do to me are
que dices tú sí qué Me vas a hacer me
you going to come hit me at all I do
vas a venir tú a pegar a mí en absoluto
n't need to threaten you already I already know
no me hace falta amenazar ya ya lo sé
Ricky what do you think he doesn't bother me with the
Ricky qué opinas no me mete con la
girl because I don't know the girl
chavala porque la chavala yo no la
and I'm very sorry it would be more it
conozco y lo siento mucho faltaría más
would be more you do it at 27 but
faltaría más tú lo haces con 27 pero yo
at 40 you do it
con 40
you do it  you do with 27 but
murado tú lo tú lo haces con 27 pero yo
at 40 I have more respect than you because you're
con 40 tengo más respeto que tú porque
mature but since you did it with liy who's
madurado pero como lo has hecho con liy
42 don't talk don't talk don't talk
que tiene 42 no hables no hables no
talking respect respect nothing
hables hablando respeto respeto nada
right or has liis done something to you what
verdad o te ha hecho algo liis a mí que
has Lis done to me when I said Well that's what I
me ha hecho Lis yo cuando he dcho Pues
ask myself why did you stick around
eso me pregunto yo para que te pegaras
there a whole live
allí un directo entero
humiliating yourself on Twitter I have
humillándose en Twitter tengo
pictures of your girlfriend
fotografías de tu novia
doing it And what do I
haciéndolo Y a mí qué me
care on Twitter for free I care
importa en Twitter gratis me importa
But Javi what is she what is she
Pero Javi qué me está qué está
trying to extort my partner with
intentando extorsionar mi pareja con
pictures of herself But what are you talking about
fotos suya Pero qué estás hablando
extorted You're laughing at liis for
extorsionada Te estás riendo de liis por
that picture when your girlfriend does it I
esa foto cuando tu novia lo hace a mí me
think it's fine that the two of them do it with you
parece bien que lo hagan las dos contigo
Why do you mention my girlfriend man we're
Por qué mencionas a mi novia tío estamos
debating about your live from yesterday
debatiendo sobre tu directo de ayer ya
But why are you talking about my girlfriend I
Pero por qué estás hablando de mi novia
mean and you have yes you have pictures of if
me refiero y tienes sí tenes fotos de si
you're making fun of lizy because she
te estás cachondeando de lizy porque se
takes those pictures you're making fun of
haga esas fotos te estás cachondeando de
your partner I don't get it it
tu pareja no me estoy cach a mí me
seems like a [ __ ] to me that I don't read the tweet I read
parece de [__] que no leo el tweet Leo
the tweet I read it right now I read it right now I
el tweet Leo leelo ahora mismo Leo ahora
read the  twet don't you say
mismo Leo el twet no te pones a decir
that it's worth it don't you say that it's worth
que vale no te pones a decir que vale
less than a macho misogynist who goes Don't
menos que un que va machista misógino No
you say that it's worth less than a who
te pones a decir que vale menos que un
goes Le el Javi G much I'm
que va Le el Javi G much lo estoy
telling you I'm telling you clown don't
diciendo te lo estoy diciendo payaso no
you say that it's worth less do you
te pones a decir que vale menos te
think it's wrong that the little mermaid is black do you
parece mal que la sirenita sea negra te
like that context Do you think it's okay Ricky
gusta ese contexto Te parece bien Ricky
what are you answering answer Yes there is t of
qué estás contestando contest Sí hay t
yours saying that it seems wrong to you it doesn't say it
tuyo diciendo que te parece mal no lo
explicitly but it's what you
pone explícitamente pero es lo que das a
imply that it bothers you that the
entender que te jode que la sirenita
new little mermaid is black who we are we are
nueva sea negra qui estamos estamos
talking about
hablando de
photos whole it is said what gives one ende okay
fotos entero se dice lo que da uno ende
okay what are you jumping on me with The
vale vale que me estás saltando con La
black Little Mermaid jav is better masi or
Sirenita negra jav es mejor masi o
amuran
amuran
masi and for you Ah You are comparing
masi y para ti Ah Estás comparando
women live you asked me I will
mujeres en directo me has preguntado tú
answer you for you Which is better has
yo te respondo para ti Cuál es mejor ha
answered a comparison of two
respondido una comparación de dos
women two human beings what do And
mujeres dos seres humanos que hacen Y
surely you are super indignant now
seguramente estás super indignado ahora
now I compare you between two women I am
ahora te comparo entre dos mujeres Yo
also going to compare you again between
también te voy a volver a comparar entre
two women why can you laugh that
dos mujeres por qué te puedes reír de
elis takes that photo and of your girlfriend
que elisis haga esa foto y de tu novia
not  eh But first of all I think what you
no eh Pero antes de nada Creo que lo que
're talking about are pictures of my girlfriend from
estás hablando son fotos de mi novia de
6 years ago I think that's the first thing you
hace 6 añoso creo que es lo primero que
're talking about and that they're from yesterday no but
estás hablando y que son de ayer no pero
from last year
del año pasado
and she's good it doesn't matter she has the [ __ ]
y tiene bueno da igual tiene el [__]
patreon active and it sells itself man
patreon activo y se se vende por sí tío
the [ __ ] [ __ ] is to pay it's a menu
la [__] [__] esta de pagar es un menú
that costs a menu that man yeah what What's
queb cuesta un menú queb tío sí qué Qué
going on What does it matter and what's happening because your
pasa Qué importa y qué pasa porque tu
girlfriend uploaded it for free on her Twitter what
novia la suba gratis en su Twitter qué
free on her Twitter are things that she
gratis en su Twitter son cosas que
published 6 years ago what 6 years Ricky
publicó hace 6 años queé 6 años Ricky
Jai How old is the photo? She's
Jai Cuántos años tiene la foto ella
233 years old right now and you're
ahora mismo tiene 233 años y me estás
telling me that she uploaded it when she was a minor Yes
diciendo que lo subió siendo menor Sí
17 or 18 yeah just turned
con 17 años o con 18 sí recién cumplido
okay let's leave you 17 right okay
vale vamos a dejarte 17 verdad vale
let's leave you ma But still
vamos a dejarte ma Pero igualmente lo de
talking about my girlfriend naked is one thing
hablar de mi novia desnuda es una cosa
because she's also young and you want to
porque también es jovencita y quies
repeat something it's not because it's not because
repetir cosit no es porque no es porque
because you brought up the subject of
porque tú has sacado el tema de la
photography, it seems
fotografía yo a mí me parece
completely respectable to me to talk about photos
completamente respetable hablar de fotos
debt 6 years ago as if that were it you
deuda hace 6 años como si fuera eso tú
talk about the
hablas de las
photos How is it that she's not naked  the
fotos Cómo que que no está desnuda las
photos She's not naked Hi you've seen her
fotos No está desnuda Hola tú la visto
tits my girlfriend
las tetas mi novia
jav we leave the subject Ricky No she doesn't
jav lo dejamos el tema Ricky No no
answer I've seen her my girlfriend Ricky we
responde la visto mi novia Ricky lo
leave the subject no no I don't want to leave it I
dejamos el tema no no no quiero dejarlo
want to talk about this have you seen her my
quiero hablar de esto la has visto mi
girlfriend Javi we leave the subject Ricky No
novia Javi lo dejamos el tema Ricky No
no we leave it yes Ricky
no lo dejamos sí Ricky se le ha visto
the entire chat has been seen No I haven't seen it Oh By the
todo el chat No no lo he visto Ay Por
way if you've seen the photos you've
cierto si has visto las cetas te has
eaten an illa as big as a cathedral Because you've
comido una illa como una catedral Porque
never uploaded anything explicit okay ri
nunca has subido nada explícito vale ri
okay Ricky okay But why do you laugh at
vale Ricky vale Pero por qué te ries de
one and the other no Wow intimidating
una y de la otra no Wow amedrentando a
a 23 year old girl being a father what am
una chavala de 23 años siendo padre a qu
I intimidating dude my partner
estoy amedrentando tío a mi pareja
intimidates by loving her So then
amedrenta con amándola Entonces entonces
you who is intimidating
tú que está amedrentando
saying this has left you
deando esto te ha
then girlfriend being a minor ning
entonces novia siendo menor ñando
supposedly
supuest
according to
segú
go sego
vay sego
esend yet I filter
esend ún yo filtr
that humiliate Ricky
ue humillo Ricky
how humiliated son what how
el qué humillados hijo el qué el qué
humiliated you why Javi for talking
humillados tú por qué Javi por hablar
invented now is your underage girlfriend naked have you
invent unuda está tu novia menor desnuda
told her that she was a minor  naked have you
le has dicho tú que era menor desnuda
seen my younger girlfriend's tits
que has visto las teta de mi novia menor
Ricky you're really spinning
Ricky estás dando una vuelta de verdad
that you're dizzying You what you're
que estás mareando Te tú lo que estás
giving is a lot of shame Yes
dando es mucha pena Sí
yes you knew that your girlfriend's move the
sí tú sabías que tu novia la movida del
other day man another day photo delicious
otro día tío otro día fot delicia en
naked in your live it's difficult the
pelotas en tu directo es chungo la
truth but oh well people what they want
verdad pero bueno la gente lo que quier
listen to me then with Ricky Stop
escúchame entonces con la Ricky Deja de
talking nonsense no no how did you put the
decir tontería no no que como pusiste la
delicious man you've already gotten really
delici tío ya ya te has puesto do los
nervous you've already lost your concentration sweating you
nervios ya te desconcentrado sudando tú
Javier you're sweating you have two
Javier estás sudando tú tienes queada do
seconds left I have a problem that you can't
segundos Yo estoy con un problema que no
imagine listen to me So
te puedes t imaginar escúchame Entonces
the other day the other day when you went to
el otro día el otro día cuando fuiste a
intimidate the girl is also
a amedrentar la chica esta también
telling him that you were going to report him yes
diciéndole que le ibas a denunciar si
you made up this intimidation no no
que has inventado tú de medrent no no
we have seen this what encouraged you we have seen it you
esto lo hemos visto lo que te alentado
have removed it
tú lo hemos visto lo has quitado
quickly in fact you told me no no we will
rapidito de hecho me has dicho no no las
see them all I asked you on twitter you skipped the
veremos todas te pedido twit has saltado
conversation and you changed the subject
conversación y me has cambiado de tema
Ricky We have seen it Javi the photo I just
Ricky Lo hemos visto Javi la foto acabo
posted on Twitter  What is that What is it
de poner en Twitter Qué es eso Qué es
What photo have you posted on Twitter creature
Qué foto has puesto en Twitter criatura
Look run Look run to Look at that
Mira corre Mira corre a Mira eso que
Tito is not going to put it live if it
Tito no lo vay a poner en directo si te
goes with you that's me reading the
va con ot eso soy yo leyendo el hilo de
keno thread that's me reading the keno thread
keno eso soy yo leyendo el hilo de keno
posting a photo of your owner's girlfriend
ponendo una foto de la novia de tu dueño
naked this What is it dude have you seen What did
en pelota esto Qué es tío has visto Qué
you think of that kenso TT I don't even know
te pareció bien ese TT de kenso no sé ni
what t is to me I have this screenshot of yours
qué t es a m Yo tengo esta captura tuya
dude what is this Wait wait Sorry sorry sorry Sorry sorry sorry sorry
tío qué es esto Espérate Espérate
Lu ball don't change the subject let's
perd Lu pelota no cambies de tema vamos
put it screen what subject Look at the photo
a ponerlo pantalla qué tema Mira la foto
Look at the photo don't change the subject don't
Mira la foto no cambies de tema no
change the subject Look at the photo Jai who
cambies de tema Mira la foto Jai que
is 40 years old and you put and you have
tiene 40 añitos y has puesto al y tú
And you are 27 and you are laughing at
tien Y tú tienes 27 y te estás riendo de
women misogynist What's wrong with that
las mujeres misógino Qué le pasa a esa
screenshot you are a misogynist that
captura eres un misógino que a las
women The younger they are, the threats are bad and
mujeres Cuanto más menores sean mal las
the threats are bad and
amenazas mal las amenazas y a los
men get complaints and
hombres le pones denuncias y órdenes de
restraining orders coward what happens in this art
alejamiento [__] qué pasa en esta ctura
when you threaten a woman with a woman
cuándo amenazado una mujer cu am mujer
give it to me sometimes times we end up [ __ ] me if you
demelo veces veces acabamos [__] yo
tell me one I'll go peacefully
con que me diga una me voy tranquilo
knowing that you had dinner tonight Ricky
sabiendo que esta noche has cenado Ricky
what's going on in this capture Tell me No
qué pasa en esta captura Cuéntame No
nothing nothing you think it's cute putting
nada nada te parecerá bonito poner a la
your owner's girlfriend naked in the middle of
novia de tu dueño en pelota en mitad de
a live you think it's cute but how do I
un directo te parecer bonito pero cómo
think it's cute I'm rationing
que me parezca bonito estoy racionando
me that capture is not edited that
yo que esa captura no está editada queé
you put it Ricky Ricky Ricky this is
la has puesto Ricky Ricky Ricky esto es
reading the keno thread okay well the thing
leyendo el hilo de keno ya bueno la cosa
is that happened no that happened man Of course
es que eso pasó no eso pasó hombre Claro
if I'm reading a thread and in note in the
si estoy leyendo un hilo y en nota en el
H he put a photo then of course I'll eat
H lo ha puesto una foto pues claro que
the photo Okay listen to me
me la como la foto Bueno escúchame de
really see removing if it's going to make you angry it's
verdad vela quitando si te va a enfadar
going to make you angry I'm going to tell you that
te va enfadar te ya te vo a decí que
if I start talking then Do you
como yo me ponga a hablaro entonces Te
think it's okay that keno to humiliate liy
parece bien que keno para humillar a liy
put that photo no Tell me the T Tell me
ponga esa foto no Cuéntame el T Cuéntame
the tweet What was the tweet the photo
el twet Qué era el twet la foto
simply laughing at her and saying the
simplemente riéndose de ella y diciendo
same thing as you that it's worth little why does he
lo mismo que tú que vale poco porque
upload this photo being what Kenzo puts
sube esta fot estando lo que ponga kenzo
if he r bad Ah okay  thank goodness I just
si él se r mal Ah vale menos mal lo
said it Damn, but it seems just as
acabo de decir [__] pero te parece igual
bad to you What do you think of what kenso did
de mal Qué te parece lo que hizo kenso
in this tet read me the TT Read it I'll repeat it to you
en este tet leme el TT Léelo te lo
Ricky are you deaf apart
vuelvo a repetir Ricky eres sordo aparte
from cuckold the context that you want
de cornudo el contexto que tú quieras
as you always do to throw it is unet de
como haces siempre para tirar es unet de
nud apart from with knot deaf it is a tweet
nud aparte de con nudo sordo es un tweet
laughing at her because she uploaded this
riéndose de ella porque suba esta
photograph m talk to your wife who is
fotografía m háblale a tu mujer cuale es
your wife
a tu mujer
buddy you are going to mess with my family I am going to
compadre te vas a meter con mi familia
say that since your
me vo a meter decir que puesto los tu
wife messing with her is not calling you a
mujer meterme con ella no es llamarte
little man [ __ ] that not messing with
poco hombre gilipolla eso no meterme con
her you are very angry Ricky Now you are going to
ella estás muy picado Ricky Ahora te vas
hit Now you are going to stick yourself for 10 days you are
a pegar Ahora te vas a pegar 10 días te
going to stick yourself for 10 days obsessed with me
vas a pegar 10 días obsesionado conmigo
like you did with Dallas No you are not
como has hecho con Dallas No tú no eres
that important [ __ ] Ah okay d is you have become
tan importante cabrón Ah vale d está has
more obsessed no no dser are you going to
obsesionado más no no dser me vas a
answer me about kenso's tweet or
contestar lo del tweet de kenso o lo
dodge it read it all Don't tell me no no
esquivas leelo entero No me digas no no
the tweet said no no read it all Ricky it
el twet decía no no leelo entero Ricky
is a tweet that you have retweeted  that you
es un tweet que tú has retuiteado que tú
have quoted that you have liked that
has citado que tú le has dado like que
you have shared it Show me the retweet
tú lo has compartido Enséñame el retweet
Show me the retweet you have not spoken you have not spoken about that
Enséñame el retweet tú no has hablado tú
Show me the
no has hablado de que Enséñame el
retweet No I have not spoken I have not even
retweet No no he hablado ni siquiera he
made a [ __ ] video and I get along well with
hecho un [__] vídeo y me llevo bien con
spirit not even made a [ __ ] video
nimo ni siquiera hecho un [__] vídeo
but show me the retweet Javi
pero enséñame el retweet Javi
V What do you think of Kenson's read it to me damn I'll
V Qué te parece el de kenson léemelo
tell you again the tweet
[__] que te lo vuelvo a decir el tweet
no you have not read it to me you have not read it to me do you
no no me la has leído no me la has leído
want me to read you all the
quieres que te lea todas las
conversations on Twitter damn that moment when you
conversaciones del twit [__] ese momento
post the photo of him naked I would
en el que pones la foto de en pelota Me
like to know what it said in that tweet with
gustaría saber qué ponía en ese twit con
that I don't care okay I'll
ese me vale
tell you if I'm interested because it does
vale Te digo si me parece interesa pues
n't say anything The only thing it says is
es que no pone nada Lo único que pone es
the photo it's a mockery of her Ah go Ah put
la foto es una burla ella Ah va Ah pon
the photo of Li is a mockery of her and you
la foto de Li es una burla ella y tú
consider that she is making fun of it and you
consideras que se está burlando ella y
can confirm it why is she going to post
lo puedes confirmar para qué va a poner
the photo if not I don't know I'm asking you
la foto si no no lo sé te pregunto
can you confirm that you are laughing at
puedes confirmar que se estás riendo de
her I'm
ella te
asking you  your point of view for you
pregunto tu punto de vista para ti se
is laughing at her for you no I don't know it's that I do
está riendo de ella para ti no no lo sé
n't know what relationship Kenzo with Li I
es que no sé qué relación kenzo con Li
don't know relationship you put it on her even in
no sé relación ti se la pusa hasta de
profile look at me I don't even know Kenzo
perfil mirao yo no conozco ni a kenzo
dude okay But what do you think It seems
tío vale Pero qué te parece Me parece
horrible to me it seems hor do you think it's horrible
horrible parece hor te parece horrible
Ricky that someone uses the photos that
Ricky que alguien utilice las fotos que
Liy takes To laugh at her not the
se hace liy Para reírse de ella no la de
girlfriend of a guy against I understand that
la novia de un tío contra entiendo que
Kenzo has a problem with dasas Well
kenzo el problema lo tiene con dasas
if she is D's girlfriend using her
Pues si es la novia de D que utilice sus
photos for that to make fun of her it
fotos para eso para mofarse de ella me
seems terrible to me it seems wrong and why do
parece fatal parece mal y por qué lo
you do it what I do Javier mte give you of
haces tú el que hago Javier mte deis de
her photos when have I put photos of her
sus fotos cuándo he puesto yo fotos de
naked I'm going to put it on the screen
en pelota lo voy a poner en pantalla
okay Well I don't know if I'm going to be able to put it
vale Bueno no sé si lo voy a poder poner
on the screen if it's censored I censored it I
en pantalla sí está censurado lo censuré
can put it Okay then you know you did it
yo lo puedes poner Vale entonces sabes
No yes okay man I
que lo has hecho No sí vale hombre
censored it out of respect for is precisely u
censuré por respeto al is precisamente u
how respectful you are a clown yes like you
qué respetuoso eres payaso sí como tú
putting her naked throwing a bed Piece
poniendo la en pelota tir una cama Cacho
of [ __ ] not a thing cuckold is that it is
de [__] no una cosa cornudo es que se
leaked without wanting because you
te filtre sin querer porque ustedes la
use it  to attack him and another
usáis para atacarlo y otra cosa que otra
thing is that I want him woman Rick if you
cosa es que lo querendo mujer Rick si tú
keep mentioning the family I've already
sig mencionando la familia Yo ya te he
told you everything that can happen to you Rick you
dicho todo lo que te puede pasar Rick tú
who pee andor I'll see your glasses you keep going
que meo andor te vuo la gafa tú sigue
Javi Put my TT Put my T put it
Javi Pon el TT mío Pon el T mío ponlo
brave put it come on lower your fumes
valiente ponlo venga bájate los humitos
Calm down Look at the chat that agrees with you
Cálmate Mira el chat que te dé la razón
there it is there put the tweet open the photo
ahí está ahí pon el twet abre la foto
he's making a fool of himself you're going to
está haciendo un ridículo que te vas a
obsess for but you don't open the photo
obsesionar durante pero no abres la foto
but you don't open the photo for whatever reason he
pero no abres la foto por lo que sea las
doesn't
fotos no las
open the photos come on what does it say read Dalas' tweets
abre venga qué pone lee los twit de
what does dala's TT from 2014 say
Dalas qué pone TT de dala del 2014 ya ya
what does Ricky say 14 yes I console myself the list from
qué pone Ricky 14 sí me conso la lista
2015 and he also recites it to me every
de 2015 y también me lo recita todos los
day saying that I threatened him then
días diciendo que le amenazo entonces
we can or we can't
podemos o no podemos
What do you think? Can that photo be
Qué te parece a ti esa foto se puede
used or would you prefer not to? Use whatever you
usar o prefieres que no Se use lo que tú
want yes to me that you use lisy
quieras si a m a mí que utilices a lisy
to mess with dala I think you're
para meterte con dala Me parece que eres
a misogynist this one  t you think I'm
un misógino a ti este t te parece
messing with lisy Yeah man the moment you
meterme con lisy Sí hombre en el momento
make the comment that any
que haces el comentario de cualquier
wanker can see your girlfriend on all
[__] puede ver a tu novia a cuatro
fours for less than what a queb costs, he
patas por menos de lo que cuesta un queb
doesn't put adas it seems fantastic that
no pone a adas le parece fantástico que
any wanker can see your girlfriend on all
cualquier [__] pueda ver a tu novia a
fours from what the men queb is going
cuatro por lo que va el men queb es vas
to deny are you going to deny that this tuv I
a negar vas a negar que este tuv no me
'm not laughing delici in that photo I'm
estoy riendo delici en esa foto me estoy
laughing that ad is a hypocrite who
riendo de que ad es un hipócrita que
says that to me in my he told me I wouldn't
dice eso a mí en mi me dijo yo yo no
be No yes I would be with a girl who does I don't
estaría No sí yo estaría con una tía que
know what I don't know how long but then
hace no sé qué no sé cuánto pero luego
we have this his real opinion about the
tenemos esto su opinión real sobre la
woman that Car on the internet Then
mujer que Car en internet Entonces
Then let's see according to your point
Entonces vamos a ver según tú punto
number one here you are not humiliating
número uno aquí no estás humillando a
lisy no I am not humiliating her you
lisy no no la estoy humillando a ella tú
are making fun of all of us who
nos estás vacilando a todos los que
are listening to this you are not a coward
estamos escuchando esto no eres un [__]
that's what happens to you you are a coward
eso es lo que te pasa que eres un [__]
that you put things and then you don't
que pones las cosas y luego no las
recognize them repertoire or you Here you
reconoces repor el repertorio oa tú Aquí
are saying that you are not
estás diciendo que no la estás
humiliating her at the moment that you say at the
humillando en el momento que dices en el
moment in which you say any any
momento en el que dices cualquiera
wanker can see your boyfriend on all
cualqu [__] puede ver a tu novio a
fours for less than it
cuatro patas por menos de lo que de lo
costs Although it goes at the moment that I
que cuesta Aunque va en el momento que
say your boyfriend thinks it's fantastic yes
dig tu novio le parece fantástico sí a
Dallas thinks it's fantastic that
Dallas le parece fantástico que
any wanker can see I don't know what
cualquier [__] pueda ver no sé qué
how much I'm laughing at Dallas for his
cuánto estoy riéndome de Dallas por su
opinion and for the photos that his
opinión y por las fotos que hace su
girlfriend takes and the opinion that his friend
novia y la opinión que tiene el amigo lo
Calis has I don't give a damn In fact that's why I
calis me la pela De hecho por eso
censored it out of deference to her because the
censuro por deferencia ella porque las
photos were more explicit things were seen
fotos eran más explícitas se veían cosas
and that's why I censored it because I don't want
y por eso la censuro porque no quiero
l is like
que l es como
[ __ ] your tweet is worse than kenso's
[__] tu tweet es peor que el de kenso
and yet you're justifying it
y sin embargo lo estás justificando
trying Oh my t is worse than putting
intentando Ah mi t es peor que ponerme
a profile picture of dala's girlfriend naked
una foto de perfil en pelota de la novia
that's worse man you add a
de dala eso es peor hombre le añades un
misogynistic comment I mean are you saying that
comentario misógino O sea estás diciendo
you think it's better that someone puts up a
que te parece mejor que qui se ponga una
picture perfidious to your owner's girlfriend let's
foto perfid a novia a tu dueño vamos a
see I think they're disgusting let's see how they
ver me parece asquerosos los a ver cómo
turn you on how ridiculous you
te calientan los cicos qué ridículo
're doing Ricky but now now then
estás haciendo Ricky pero ahora ahora
then I want to tell you how am I going to
entonces entonces quiero deciro cómo voy
get a clip of this surely
a sacar yo clip de esto s seguramente
So it seems to you that Dallas is a
Entonces te parece que Dallas Es
hypocrite  because in 2014 he did one thing and
hipócrita porque en 2014 hizo una cosa y
10 years later 10 years later nov
10 años después 10 años después nov
let's read everything let's read it all is
vamos leer tod vamos leerlo todo
worth Open open the photo let's read them
vale Abre abre la fotito vamos le los t
out loud I'll read it to you if you want because I have a
en alto te lo leoo si quieres que tengo
better voice if you spend your life
mejor vozo si te pasas la vida
teasing [ __ ] and posting pictures of
calentando pollas y colgando fotos de
your attributes then don't get so offended
tus atributos luego no te ofendas tanto
when they call you a [ __ ] he considers what
cuando te llamen zorra él considera esto
we're seeing on the screen a
que estamos viendo en la pantalla una
[ __ ] in 2014 Yes yes he considers it and he's
zorra en 2014 Sí sí lo considera y está
dating a person who does it
saliendo con una persona que lo hace a
today in 2014 he said it s Yes yes a
día de hoy en 2014 lo dijo s Sí si una
very well 2015 look a year later if
muy bien 2015 mira un añito después si
a [ __ ] shows her tits to receive
una zorra enseña las tter para recibir
attention eh Look at the same time as the one on the
atención eh Mira la misma época que el
list 201 if a [ __ ] shows her
de da lista 201 si una zorra enseña las
tits To receive to receive attention she
tetas Por recibir para recibir atención
is a generic clown but not a
es una payasa genérica más no una
brave feminist forget what quece no we haven't
feminista valiente olvidéis lo quece no
finished we haven't finished
no hemos terminado no hemos terminado
next screenshot next screenshot I
captura siguiente captura siguiente la
can put it there is no there is no there is nothing
puedo poner no hay no hay no hay nada
Everything is covered up I really have respected that
Está todo tapado de verdad he respetado
people want to see what I pay to
eso la gente quiere ver lo que pague al
Isi ual viral phenomenon Juan Guarnizo calls it
Isi ual fenómeno viral le pone Juan
eh yes we know that the girl
guarnizo eh que sí sabemos que la chica
well we don't know I don't know if it was ever
bueno no sabemos no sé si se llegó a
confirmed But well the rumors the
confirmar Pero bueno que los rumores las
speculations that they have cheated on her
especulaciones de que le han engañado
that they have done whatever and that they
que han hecho lo que sea y que se
got divorced okay viral phenomenon 2020
divorciaron vale fenómeno viral 2020
2021 2022 2023 and 2024 president of I don't
2021 2022 2023 y 2024 presidente de no
know what from Kingle I don't know this
sé qué de la kingle no lo conozco esto
winner of an elan award he I don't
ganador de un premio elan premio el no
know what has won many things and he tells her
sé qué ha ganado muchas cosas y le dice
all that for less than 3.99 it is a
alas todo eso por menos de 3,99 es un
little ironic that the price of what
poco irónico que el precio de lo que
elice has and its content is seeing
tiene elice y Su contenido está viendo
that it says this and that what you have at home
que dice esto y que lo que tiene en casa
does exactly the same answer it in
hace Exactamente lo mismo lo responda de
this way this tweet of When is it Ha
esta manera este tweet de Cuándo es Ja
this one of When is it tell me you tell me you
este de Cuándo es dímelo tú dímelo tú
tell me you from 2024 they are saying in the
dímelo tú de 2024 están diciendo en el
chat that that is
chat que eso es
false The tweet is false It is false the
falso Es falso el tweet Es falso el
t in the chat they are saying that it is false
t en el chat están diciendo que es falso
Jai your chat will agree with you chat in
Jai tu chat te va a dar la razón chat en
the chat they are saying that it is false
el chat están diciendo que es falso
because me  I reported it for having put it damn what what how
porque me denuncie por haberlo puesto
lazy the argument is
ostia qué qué qué vago el argumento es
real defense you have the real no no I
defens real tienes el real no no yo no
'm not saying it eh me no me no no the
lo estoy diciendo eh yo no yo no no el
real the real screenshot is the same if the
real la captura real es lo mismo si las
red things I only put the
cosas rojas yo le puse solo las cosas
red things but I say D's tweet you have
roja pero digo el tweet de D lo tienes
the real one and I don't have the link of that I have
el real y no tengo el link de eso tengo
the screenshot J but I say you have the real tweet
la captura J pero el tweet real digo lo
[ __ ] wait no no moment
tienes [__] espérate no no momento
moment this is going to be everywhere tomorrow
momento esto mañana va a salir en todos
your defense no no no I'm not
lados tu defensa no no no te estoy
defending you don't change the words to
defendiendo no cambies las palabras para
try to win anything Ricky Okay then it
intentar ganar nada Ricky Vale entonces
works cheap today they serve this Ricky this
sirve barato hoy sirven esto Ricky este
tet that I don't know which of when the ent 2024
tet que no sé cuá de cuando el ent 2024
this 2024 this year 2024 Juano doesn't have
esto 2024 este año 2024 Juano no tiene
Dallas 2024 blocked dude Javi Javi
bloqueado a Dallas 2024 tío Javi Javi
Javi 2024 p Juan Javi's
Javi 2024 p el [__] twet de Juan Javi lo
[ __ ] tweet puts it Juan's [ __ ] tweet 2024 that they are
pone el [__] tweet de Juan 2024 que son
cousins who won this year Ricky 2024
primos que ganado este año Ricky 2024
Juan W nison doesn't have Dallas blocked
Juan W nison no tiene bloqueado a Dallas
and I don't know what relationship they have
y yo queé sé Qué relación tienen ellos
Beyond what they invent [ __ ] about
Más allá de lo que se inventan mierd del
each other don't suck at me It's false the
uno del otro no me su lores Es falso el
T is false r incredible man then he'll see
T es falso r increíble tío luego verá
the deh talking about how to defend with he'll get
losos deh hablando de cómo defend con
angry I'll tell him here no that I thought it was
enfadará le dir aquí no que yo pensaba
n't ri Ricky Ricky [ __ ] man Juan
que no ri Ricky Ricky [__] tío Juan
Guarnizo and Dallas fought in 2020 Yeah
guarnizo y Dallas se pelearon en 2020 Sí
and you believe it and the same thing my Dallas has done to me I have
y tú te crees y lo mismo que me ha hecho
to block myself six times a
mi Dalas he de bloquearme seis veces al
year to give me [ __ ] and
año para ponerme [__] y volver a
block myself again so I don't respond to that
bloquearme para que no responda a eso
what can't I do to him Juan Guarnizo
qué no puo hacerle eso Juan guarnizo
has blocked Dallas since 2020 2021 he
tiene bloqueado a Dallas desde 2020 2021
has blocked me How do I know if he
me tiene bloqueado a mí Yo qué sé si lo
has blocked him Well I'm
tiene bloqueado Pues te lo estoy
telling you Of course you don't know you've
diciendo Claro que no lo sabes te has
eaten a
comido una captura
fake capture well Okay come on but listen to me
falsa bueno Vale venga pero escúchame
one thing argument man okay Pass me the
una cosa argumento tío vale Pásame el
tweet weak defense Pass me the tweet yes it
tweet defensa flojita Pásame el tweet sí
happened to you too from 2014 surely he hasn't
te paso también de 2014 seguro que no ha
deleted the [ __ ] thing Pass me the tweet Pass me
borrado el [__] Pásame el
the tweet pass it to me amaza
tweet Pásame el tweet me lo pasas amaza
to the Yes yes  pass me my threat the kid
a la Sí sí pásame mi amenaza la chaval
girl So these tweets from El Bueno
chica Entonces estos tweet del Bueno
apart from that tweet this tweet from 2014
aparte de ese tweet este tweet del 2014
and 2015 poor thing La La La snorts what will
y 2015 pobrecillo el La La La bufa que
happen to him later on WhatsApp this
le va a caer luego por WhatsApp este
man dude gives me the creeps and to listen Ricki do you
hombre tío me da cosa y to escuch ricki
listen to me or are you Already tired it's that
me escuchas o estás Ya cansado es que a
maybe you're tired I'm already
lo mejor estás cansado Ya de estoy
tired you're very very pedantic Javi this are you
cansado eres muy muy pedante Javi esto
tired of the humiliated you don't
estás cansado de la humillada ya no
want anymore Yes yes totally totally
quieres más Sí sí totalmente totalmente
dude totally you're tired of the
tío totalmente estás cansado de la
humiliated part you're 40 years old I'm
humillada parte tienes 40 años me estoy
feeling terrible 4 years dog bowl not
sintiendo fatal 4 años perro cuenco no
all those things your arguments No yes the
todas esas cosas tus argumento No sí las
things this that you're used to being
cosit esta que estás acostumbrado que te
told because you know that he's more right
digan porque sabes que tiene más razón
Okay then the T from 2014 and 2015 is
Vale entonces el T del 2014 y el 2015
also worth it or this one is not worth it he's
vale también o este no vale esto lo está
using this to post delicious photos there with
usando para poner fotos delicia ahí con
very little clothing it can't be Ricky the tet
poquita ropa no puede ser Ricky el tet
from 2014 and 2015 is worth it or not
del 2014 y 2015 vale o no
worth it What's it worth it Why Javi for him to
vale Para qué vale Para qué Javi para
report me for a no for him to
que me denuncie para un no para que te
report you no the tweet that I have on screen  right now
denunci no el twit que tengo en pantalla
that you're titting okay Why
ahora mismo que tú teteas vale Para qué
Yes okay so that you would say this it disgusts me
Sí vale para que daras diga esto me da
and you know knows that your partner does it
asco y sabes sepa que su pareja lo hace
and seems fine okay then okay I say
y le parezca bien vale entonces vale
me then I say that
digo yo entonces digo yo eso que los
your tweets from 2015 threatening Dallas
tweets tuyos de 2015 amenazando a Dallas
also see no Which one is which one is yours and tell me
también ven no Cuál es cuál es tú y dime
more than one Javi one in which you talk about
más de uno Javi uno en el que hablas de
breaking his mouth that you consider yourself a
partirle la boca de que te consideras
dalita the other Which one is which one is the other
dalita el otro Cuál es cuál es el otro
come on you
venga me los
deny them I tell you there's a tweet in which I
niegas te digo que hay un tweet en el
say yes I feel like it I'm not saying that I'll
que digo sí me dan ganas No digo que le
break his mouth I say I feel like it there's a
partiré la boca digo me dan ganas hay un
tweet that are threats no no for me it
tweet que son amenazas no no para mí no
's not a threat for me it's not that I
es una amenaza para mí no lo es que lo
can consider it a threat yes you can
pueda considerar amenaza sí lo puede
consider it threatening for me it's not threatening v
considerar amenaz para mí no es amenaz v
and that tweet is okay or because yours It's not okay okay
y ese tweet vale o porque tuyo No vale
okay but neither did you take many
vale vale pero tampoco tu tomo muchas
measures come on when I posted it you didn't take them
medidas dala cuando lo puse no las tomó
But then then you You threaten
Pero entonces entonces a ti Tú amenazas
a kid and The kid threatens you
a un chaval y El chaval te amenaza de
back said for me it's not a threat no
vuela dicho para mí no es una amenaza no
no I tell him I say you just said
no yo le digo yo digo acabas de decir
that he can take it as a
que lo puede tomar como una
threat  if you want Of course but he didn't do it
amenaza si quiere Claro pero no lo hizo
because he didn't report it Javi yes yes he didn't do it
porque no lo denunció Javi sí sí no lo
no Tom now it's useful to him I did
hizo no Tom ahora le sirve Yo sí que lo
report him you reported him No I reported him
denunci lo denunciaste No yo lo denunci
for calling me the trafficker and
por llamarme al tratador y
when you don't come back again to that what's
cuando no vuelvas otra vez a eso que
worth But who are you You're a loser
vale Pero tú quién eres Eres un pringado
from Seville give
de Sevilla dá
food you're a bit of a
comer eres un poco
man you mess with women you don't
hombre que te metes con las mujeres no
have balls with men I put my
tienes huev con los hombres pongos a mi
women to you weigh me let's
mujeres a ti te lo
see show it to me grind grind let
pes a ver
your owner show it to you who likes telling
muestre tu dueño que le guste contando
that about you By the way don't you think you're
eso de ti Por cierto no piensas que eres
a good person behind your back that
una buena persona a tu espalda que lo
SEP is worth mu hac I've
SEP vale mu hac
made the bucket of
le hecho el cubo de
street that I dropped the dala no ri you
rua que se me ha caído el dala no ri te
're making it up How little Well and what a
lo está inventando Qué poco Bueno y qué
[ __ ] shame Javi I think it's going to be the
[__] vergüenza Javi creo que va a ser la
first time that I consider this over
primera vez que de esto por terminado
because I'm really I'm very you're going you're going you're
porque estoy de verdad estoy muy te vas
going with your tail between your
te vas te vas con el rabito ent entre la
legs doggy style I have it so big that I
pierna perrito lo tengo tan grande que
have to hold it between my legs
me lo tengo que [__] entre las piernas
correct yes I'm going but it's that I want to
correcto sí me voy pero es que te quiero
ask you a question  things you have at
hacer una pregun cositas que tienes por
home you go you go to the town you go
casa te va te vas para el pueblo te vas
scared boo what are they cevilla it's you you
acojonados buo que están cevilla eres tú
go scared scared
te vas acojonados
me I'm tired
acojonado me estoy cansado
man I have to ask I have to
hombre tengo que pregun te tengo que
ask you about this
preguntar por la chavala esta que puso
girl who cheated on you that your girlfriend cheated on you the other
los cuernos que tu novia te puso el otro
day what the girl did you are you
día los que puso la chavala t tú eres tú
are from the school that they cheated on me
eres de la escuela de que me han puesto
again it's
los cuos otra vez
not true she will have her reasons
no ser verdad tendrá sus motivos No lo
The girl who caught
dice la chica que pilló las
her boyfriend talking to her says no the girl
conversaciones a su novio no la chica se
regretted it ch she regretted it because you
arrepintió ch se arrepintió porque tú la
threatened her because you threatened her
amenazaste porque tú la amenazaste
show it to me fake [ __ ] ch said
enséñalo falso de [__] ch dijo po
man ch said said the ch hbre the girl
hombre ch dijo dijo la ch hbre la chica
said that she was wrong
dijo que que se había equivocado se
apologize 20 times to me she was
disculpa 20 veces conmigo se había
wrong So what happened in those
equivocado Entonces qué es lo que pasó
conversations Even what
en esas conversaciones Hasta qué es lo
happened about what in that one don't yell Ricky
que pasó de qué en esa no chille Ricky
calm down you're very nervous
tranquilízate que estás muy nervioso
yelling all the time hick me but
chillado to todo el rato cateto yo pero
why are you telling me why are you telling me hick I
por qué me dices por qué me dices cateto
don't know my things he's super nervous
No lo sé mi cosas está super nervioso
dude are you doing  a ridiculous beast
tío estás haciendo un ridículo bestial
The girl says she steals some
La chica dice que trinca unas
conversations when she records
conversaciones cuando le registra el
her boyfriend's phone of your girlfriend talking
móvil a su novio de tu novia hablando
to hers Exactly Yes yes that's what the
con el suyo Exacto Sí sí eso dice la
girl says and what happens Have you seen the videos
chica y qué pasa Te has visto los vídeos
no because Dalas told you not to
no porque Dalas te ha dicho no to los
watch them that I will make one with the version
vea que le haré yo uno con la versión
that I cust and I have to believe yours you do
que a mí me cust y me tengo que creer lo
n't have to believe it You don't have to believe
tuyo no te lo tienes que creer No te
that I show the [ __ ]
tienes que creer que muestro las [__]
conversations of the girl with d and
conversaciones de la chavala con d y
me [ __ ] and what the
conmigo gilipolla y qué le dice la
girl says And what does the girl say to
chavala Y qué le dice la chavala a
Dallas no to start the girl
Dallas no para empezar la chavala
starts talking to Amanda that Amanda
empieza hablando con Amanda que Amanda
says tell me By the way, by the
le dice cuentame Por cierto que por
way, you also made up yesterday in your
cierto además te inventas ayer en tu
live that Lizy was unfaithful to Dallas,
directo que lizy le fue infiel a Dallas
esc that Dallas mistreats her, okay Oops That ends up mistreating her
esc que Dallas la maltrata vale Uy Eso
and you make it up too, he also makes it up too, he
quedar la maltrata y te inventas también
tries to flirt with this girl
tambas intenta ligarse a esta chica
Until you talk through the phones so they don't
Hasta que por hablas por los para que no
hear me, you're not a real man, you're not good at the
me escuchen poco hombre no lo del
volume, [ __ ], you
volumen se te da a ti mejor gilipolla
're really nervous, dude, you
poco hombre está fatal de nervioso tío
're on edge, dude, can you see it  all
estás de los nervios tío lo veis todos
no chat okay you make up that the girl you're
no chat vale te inventas que la ch queas
trying to flirt with this girl until she
intenta ligar con esta chavala hasta que
finds out she's the age where she
se entera de que tiene la edad de dónde
's from sorry you're trying to flirt with
es la perdona queas intenta ligar con
her you can't see the chats he has the
ella no se veen los chat tiene los chats
full chats what it says what it says in the
completos en qué pone qué pone en el
chat you should leave your boyfriend he's a Red
chat deberías dejar a tu novio es un Red
flag he doesn't have anything up with you and that's
flag no tiene nada subido contigo y eso
flirting that's flirting man taking into
es ligar eso es ligar hombre teniendo en
account that for Dallas to say hello
cuenta que para Dallas que le digan Hola
It's that they want to suck his [ __ ] yes
Es que le quieren comer la [__] sí
Dallas wanted to [ __ ] her
Dallas se la quería zumbar
very clearly I mean let's see if I understand
clarísimamente O sea a ver si entiendo
you make that up based on the fact that the girl
te inventas eso en base a que la chavala
took him on the phone esc the situation
le ha cogido el el tel esc la situación
you have in your life right now and that you
que tienes en tu vida ahora mismo y que
're talking for
estés hablando de
real man they just just
verdad tío te acaban de acabas de
caught you Ricky you're such a little man so
trincar Ricky eres tan poco hombre tan
pathetic and you have such a small ego and you
patético y tienes un ego tan pequeño y
're so obsessed and sick with the
estás tan obsesionado y enfermo con el
Dallas silent unfaithful that you just found
Dallas silencio infiel que te acabas de
out that they're cheating on you for the
enterar que te ponen los cuernos por
second time and you prefer to intimidate that
segunda vez y prefieres amedrentar a esa
girl so you don't admit it that you made it
chica para no reconocerlo que te has
all up but that version What is
inventado todo pero esa versión Qué es
Javi  that the girl has apologized
Javi que la chica se ha disculpado
because when Amanda showed her
porque cuando cuando Amanda le enseño
the real conversations she said Damn my
las conversaciones reales dijo [__] mi
boyfriend cheated on me the girl said
novio me ha engañado la chavala dijo
Damn my boyfriend lied to me Amanda Talk
[__] mi novio me ha mentido Amanda Habla
Amanda was talking to that
Amanda hablaba con ese
boy in 2021 I didn't even know and I wasn't
chico en 2021 yo no sabía ni y no
talking he replied to the seg a story
hablaba le respondió al seg una historia
send he replied thanking her
manda le respondió dándole las gracias
in 2021 Yes let's see where it says 202 my
en 2021 Sí a ver dónde pone que 202 mi
[ __ ] video I have the capture with everything
[__] vídeo tengo la captura con todo
exposed [ __ ] in my video It's in 2021
expuesto cabrón en mi vídeo Está en 2021
the boy answers a story and
el chico le responde una historia y
when the girl looks at her phone because she did
cuando la chica le mira el móvil porque
look at her phone she sees that what there is is
sí le miró el móvil ve que lo que hay es
a response from Amanda and Amanda and she says
una respuesta de Amanda y Amanda y dice
she is Amanda being unfaithful and the girl
ella la Amanda siendo infiel y la niña
on top of that with the heat doesn't realize
encima que con el calentón no s cuenta
that it said 2021 At what minute does it say
que ponía 2021 En qué minuto pone el
2021 I don't know it happens it looks big hover
2021 No lo sé pasa se ve grande pasa un
the cursor a bit and when you see a
poco el cursor y cuando veas una foto en
white photo with red things that the
blanca con cosas rojas que censuró la
boy's identity censored because I get drunk tell me
identidad del chaval porque me pedo dime
a word that you say more or less at that
una palabra que digas más o menos en ese
moment Put 2021 in the  description or Put
momento Pon 2021 en el descrición o Pon
3 years or something like that or 4 years something like that
3 años o algo así o 4 años algo así está
the capture is there in the video damn
la captura ahí en el vídeo [__] Es que
This is what happens to you for not informing yourself Ha You
esto te pasa por no informarte Ja Tú te
believe the first thing the owner tells you and
crees lo primero que te dice el dueño y
says Come on then I'm telling you this is that it doesn't say it
dice Venga pues cuento esto es que no lo
making it up that they put me on
pone inventándote que me han puesto otra
again s lo
vez s lo
p Javi is blind [ __ ] put on the
p Javi está ciego cabrón ponte la gafa
age glasses and I put I don't know what from March
de la edad y yo pone no sé qué de marzo
2021 s that he puts it let's see tell me a
2021 s que lo pone a ver dime una
word that is said in that minute the
palabra que se diga en ese minuto el
video the video lasts 28 minutes about what I
vídeo el vídeo dura 28 minut acerdo lo
said dude I don't remember I recorded it
he dicho yo tío no me acuerdo lo grabé
two days ago Put 2021 or Put I didn't
hace dos días Pon 2021 o Pon no la
know her or something like that because I didn't know
conocía o algo así porque yo no conocía
Man 2021 in fact she was already in another
Man 2021 de hecho ya estaba en otra
relationship dude if I'm not
relación tío si no me
mistaken don't put it Ricky Well don't
equivoco no lo pones Ricky Bueno no te
worry ask the cop to send it to you
preocupes pídeselo a poli que te lo
or what the [ __ ] send it to Twitter
mande o qué [__] pasárselo por Twitter
people I put that capture in the video
gente esa captura la puse en el vídeo
dude Yes in fact it zooms in on it 2021 my
tío Sí de hecho hace zoom en lo 2021 mi
editor crops it and zooms in and
editor lo recorte y le hace zoom y lo
circulates it dude  yes it puts it well no
circula cabrón sí que lo pone bueno da
matter the thing 2021 chat with The boy
igual la cosa chat de 2021 con El chaval
the girlfriend puts the tweet half a like and I
la novia pone el tweet medio like y
put how Amanda hits on my
pongo como Amanda le tira la caña a mi
boyfriend and puts Amanda pass it to me so I can
novio y le pone Amanda pásamelo que lo
see it Me too and what happens to her says
vea Yo también y lo que le pasa dice
Amanda Hahaha he cheated on you Watch the
Amanda Jajaja te ha engañado Mira la
full version and amandale passes a
versión completa y amandale pasa una
screenshot of the same chat in which it says that
captura del mismo chat en el que pone
before what she has as the
que antes de lo que ella tiene como
first message the boyfriend had
primer mensaje el novio le había
replied to her stories I'm
respondido historias a ella estoy
passing the full video the 2021 thing doesn't
pasando el vídeo completo lo de 2021 no
put it dude not the one from today not the one from yesterday
lo pone tío no el de hoy no el de ayer
haha the vi from yesterday yesterday the previous one the
jaii el ví de ayer de ayer el anterior
last one not the previous one part one the one about they cheated on
el último no el anterior la parte uno el
me again the
de me han puesto los cuernos otra vez
title says they will pass it to you now I mean they have
título lo pone te lo pasarán ahora o sea
sent you they have sent you
a ti te han mandado a ti te han mandado
Amanda's conversations with the
las conversaciones de Amanda con el
boy no no Amanda passes it to the
chico no no Amanda se la pasa a la
girl directly because the girl
chavala directamente porque la chavala
tells her You have spoken to my boyfriend
le dice Tú le has hablado a mi novio
says Amanda No look the chat is all look at
dice Amanda No mira el chat está todo
it later it's too long Ha look at it
mírelo luego es que muy largo Ja mírelo
later in full you will understand everything
luego entero que lo vas a entender todo
but don't make a fool of yourself because it is all
pero no hagan ridículo porque to está
making it up [ __ ] It's all there It's
inventando cabrón Está todo Ahí está
all there okay okay what you want
todo ahí bueno vale lo que tú quies
ask the girl if you want the
pregunta a la chica si quieres te va a
same thing is going to happen to you if it's her chats
pasar lo mismo si es que son sus chat
with dala to dala what screwed her is that
con dala a dala lo que le ha [__] es
when she found out that I was going to
que cuando se enteró de que yo iba a
expose the chas that she had with him
exponer los chas que tenía ella con él
that she gave me permission her chinaball
que ella me dio permiso le chinaball
throwing the cane and on top of that at the same
tirando la caña y encima en el mismo
time he was driving a
momento en el que estaba conduciendo un
car accompanying his girlfriend for a
coche acompañando a su novia por un
tumor to the hospital but listen to me to see
tumor al hospital pero escúchame a ver
one thing Okay Even if I start the conversation in 2021
una cosa Vale Aunque empiece en 2021 la
the girl in the twit says
la chica en el twit dice
that she continued talking while she was with you
que siguió hablando estando contigo
then she says it's a lie Javi that she got
luego dice que es mentira Javi que se
heated if I spoke to her by voice dude she
calentó si hablé yo con ella por voz tío
got heated that it's all recorded
que se calentó que está todo grabado
Look watch the video and if listen to me if they
Mira mírate el vídeo y si escúchame si
continued talking later answering
luego siguieron hablando se respondiendo
two more stories I don't care I didn't
dos historias más me da igual yo no
know Amanda dude I didn't even know who she
conocía a Amanda tío no sabía ni quién
was and that I spoke to a tiktoker in 2021
era y que hable con un tiktoker en 2021
is that I don't care is that I say to myself go up
es que me la pela es que me digo a suba
there damn if I don't know Who was the
ahí [__] si yo no sab Quién era la
move the
movida la
chentn let's see how long you've been
chentón vamos a ver cuánto tiempo llevas
with Amanda eh a year or so listen to me
con Amanda eh un año a prox escúchame
ASSUME please ASSUME that you were wrong
ASUME porfa ASUME que te has equivocado
at least that much man because you slipped
por lo menos eso tío porque has patinado
Here I have to check it it's already
Aquí lo tengo que comprobar lo tengo ya
I assure you that in my video Everything is there
te seguro yo que en mi vídeo Está todo
All the screenshots are worth seeing I will see you are
Todas Las capturas vale ver lo veré tú
going to assume that you were wrong but she
vas a asumir que te has equivocado pero
will ask me for forgiveness if you see that you were
me pedirá perdón si ves que te
wrong you will ask me Yes yes of course
equivocado me pedirás Sí sí por supuesto
you are going to assume that you were wrong
tú vas a asumir que te has equivocado
with pollo if you are a man of your word or is it still
con pollo si eres un hombre de palabra o
the same word that
sigue siendo la misma palabra que fuiste
you were eh when you promised me to ask me for
tú eh cuando me prometiste a mí pedirme
forgiveness for something else and it doesn't exist
perdón por otra cosa y no lo existe
clown Why why check your
payaso Por qué por qué revisa tus
conversations with me Ah yes totally we
conversaciones conmigo Ah sí totalmente
say it out loud do you want to talk
lo decimos en alto quieres que hablemos
about it or does it give you the creeps no you can't talk about
de eso o te da cosa no no puedes hablar
it Ah then don't tell me that I didn't
de eso Ah entonces no me digas que no te
ask you for forgiveness [ __ ] because if we can't
ped perdón gilipolla porque si no se
talk it's because the courts have
puede hablar es porque aún judicialmente
n't given me the resolution yet that is okay
no me d la resolución que estáa vale
okay eh But say it or you are when fatal eh
vale eh Pero di o estás quando fatal eh
something that can't be talked about I speak you are
algo que no se puede hablar hablo estás
looking terrible you don't come If you want me to
quedando fatal tú no venga Sí quieres
ask you for forgiveness for what  Do you want me to
que te pida perdón por lo que quieres
apologize? You're looking terrible,
que te pida perdón estás quedando fatal
Javi? Do you want me to apologize for what you
tú Javi quieres que te pida perdón por
want me to apologize for? Yes, of
lo que quieres que te lo pida Sí por
course, okay, sure. Do you want me to
supuesto vale seguro quieres que te pida
apologize? Yes, yes, of course. Sorry for
perdón sí sí por supuesto perdón por
having put in a video that was your, I don't
haber puesto en un vídeo que era su no
know if it was insinuating, dirty old man or creepy
sé si era insinuer viejo verde o creepy
for some conversations you had with
por unas conversaciones que tuviste con
Miare asking for permission so that, no, no,
miare pidiéndole permiso para que no no
telling her not to tell her mother that you
diciéndole que no avisara a su madre que
wanted to go to bed with her, such as
querías irte a la cama con ella tal
being they are telling me they are
estando me están diciendo me están
telling me that you only show the
diciendo que tú enseñas solo el
beginning of the
principio de la
conversation yes, what you talked about, yes, it is a
conversación sí lo que hablaron sí es un
screenshot what there is
una captura lo que
But Javi, I will explain to you why Yes, but
hay Pero Javi te explico por qué Si pero
wait now we are talking about this, I am asking you for
espérate ahora hablamos de esto te estoy
forgiveness, [ __ ], don't interfer 20 in
pidiendo perdón cabrón no te inter 20 en
2021 the girl was not with
2021 la chica no estaba con
s, she was, damn, yes, she was and the chat what's happening
s estaba [__] sí estaba y el chat que le
to Amanda since 2021 that you watch
pasa a Amanda des de 2021 que te mires
the video if I explain everything, perza pissing
el vídeo si lo explico todo perza meando
is that I made a super video, I made a
es que hice un vídeo super hice un vídeo
super video something another day about this, the girl is what she
super lgo otro día de esto la chica esta
said was that Amanda was talking
lo que dijo era que estaba hablando
to him now  yes and then he
Amanda con él ahora sí y luego se
apologized because he said I posted that out of
disculpó porque dijo he puesto eso por
hot air, I hadn't seen the date of
calentón no había visto ni la fecha de
the messages or that he was the one who
los mensajes ni que era él el que le
started talking to her, well, say that, don't
empezaba habar pues pues di eso no me
tell me about the 20-year-olds, what I told you, what I
digas los de 20o lo que te he dicho lo
said, or the girl starts, but this
dicho oa la chica empieza per esto te
matters more to you than you and me, no, it's not that I give
importa más que lo de tú y mi no que no
a [ __ ] [ __ ] about it
es que eso me importa una [__] [__]
because it's nonsense, ha, that's why I
porque es una tontería de ha eso he
said I can't talk about that, no, that's why I
dicho que no puedo hablar de eso no por
said I can't talk, no, you ca
eso he dicho que no puedo hablar no que
n't talk about a judicial matter.
no puedes hablar de un tema judicial
Come on, how can you talk if you want
Vamos como podes hablar si quieres
because your word isn't worth a [ __ ]
porque tu palabra No vale una [__]
[ __ ] Because everything you talk about later, you
[__] Porque todo lo que hablas luego
talk about it out there, you said, you haven't
lo hablas por ahí dicho tú a mí no me
asked me for forgiveness and what we agreed on,
has pedido perdón y la lo que quedamos
you haven't asked me for forgiveness, of course, Jai.
tú a mí no me has pido perdón claro Jai
Of course, because nothing has been proven
Claro porque no se ha demostrado nada
judicially, buddy, but it's that it has
judicialmente compi pero es que no tiene
nothing to do judicially if Shoka
nada que ver judicialmente si al shoka
is defending him from something, to me.
lo está defendiendo de una cosa a mí Por
Why not, yes, two years ago, Jai, when I was, listen to me,
qué no sí hace dos años Jai cuando fuera
listen to this topic with you,
escúchame escucha este tema contigo
judicially, you told me, if the resolution comes out later,
judicialmente me dijiste si luego sale
but the resolution has
la resolución pero es que la resolución
nothing to do with it.  Ricky the resolution noene
nada que ver Ricky la resolución noene
Nothing we are on that I have the call I
Nada estamos en eso tengo la llamada yo
also recorded that we put it the
también grabada que lo pongamos la la
resolution has nothing to do with it
resolución no tiene nada que ver lo
we put it Javi I give it Here it is we put
ponemos Javi le doy Aquí ya está ponemos
Ricky Ricky calm down the resolution
Ricky Ricky tranquilo la resolución no
has nothing to do with it the resolution is for
tiene nada que ver la resolución es por
insults yes no no you told me I told you
insultos sí no no me dijiste te dije el
this issue of The captures of throwing the
tema este de Las capturas de tirarle la
cane Millar and all this wh and you told me
caña millar y todo esto qu y me dijiste
no because I told you are real these
no porque te dije son reales estas
captures have occurred and you tell me is that I
capturas han ocurrido y me dices es que
can not answer you no no Wait wait you
no te puedo responder no no Espera
told me is that I can not
espera me dijiste es que no te puedo
answer you and I tell you why Because there is
responder y te digo por qué Porque hay
a trial premises I say okay And you told me
un juicio predio digo vale Y me dijiste
when it is proven okay okay we will see it privately
cuando se demuestre vale vale lo vemos
okay we will see it privately but
privado vale lo vemos por privado pero
the trial
el juicio
That is that the trial what I told you to
Ese es que el juicio lo que yo te dije
ask me Forgiveness was for another
que me pidieras Perdón era por otra
series of things for which you defended the shoc
serie de cosas por la que al shoc lo
and you do not want to turn it around on me
defendías y a mí no quieres darle vuelta
because you suck his [ __ ] they
a eso porque tú le comes la [__] le
suck the [ __ ] of those who are
comen la [__] a quienes son
famous you are charging it fell directly on you
famosos estás cobrando se te cao directo
listen I tell you at least on Twitch is
escucha te digo al menos en Twitch est
watching I listen to that of the  Sorry,
viendo yo escucha eso de las disculpas
yes I did, I don't remember if it was
sí que lo hice no recuerdo si fue por
private, it's true, you fell, you
privado es verdad se caído tú se ha
fell, you left, ol Well, I know that
caído se te ido ol Bueno yo sé que
matters more Cab, but in the
importa más eso Cab pero en la
discord conversation, man, if you want to
conversación de discord tío si quieres
talk about the conversation we had on
hablar de la conversación que tuvimos
discord, you recognize that with me
por discord tú me reconoces que conmigo
you have one stick and with him you clash You have
tienes una vara y con el chocas Tienes
another one, man, just like you with me,
otra hombre pues igual que tú conmigo
with Dalas you don't
con Dalas no te
screw around anymore, but one thing is that you have
jodes ya pero una cosa es que tú tengas
a different stick to measure with one
una vara diferente de medir con una
person and with another because one you like
persona y con otra porque uno te caiga
more than the other and another thing is that
mejor que el otro y otra cosa es que
directly what you defend for one another, you
directamente lo que le defiendes al uno
throw at the other Javi who
al otro al otro le tiras Javi que te
just told you that he puts Two daggers and
acaba de decir que le mete Dos puñales y
two shots in the raes And you forgot to say
dos tiros al raes Y a ti te falto decir
that he has put you cachendo the message and
que te ha puesto cachendo el mensaje y
that when I,
que cuando yo
my
mi
partner, I have said that, let's see people,
pareja Yo he dicho eso a ver selo gente
the clip of Ja saying that with
el clip de Ja diciendo que con
loard, it's true, man. I mean, you started
loard es verdad tío O sea tú te pusiste
telling al. Oh, man, go again, go to
a decirle a al Ah tío otra ve ot ve al
tudor, you started telling him also that you were going to
tudor te pusiste a decirle también que
send him friends And that's a
le ibas a mandar amiguitos E eso es
lie, I haven't told you, I have contacts
mentira no te he dicho tengo contacto
that make sure  that she's okay, you're the
que se aseguran de que ella est bien te
caretakers no no no, her
lo médicos cuidadores no no no sus
Puerto Rican colleagues, her
colegas puertorriqueños sus colegas
Puerto Rican colleagues
puertorriqueños
Ricky what Javi what have they banned me on
Ricky qué Javi qué me han baneado en
twit man what the [ __ ] have you done because
twit tío qué [__] has hecho porque
because I threatened you H for threat or
porque te he amenazado H por amenaza o
because you doxxed the girl man you are
porque has doxeado a la chavala tío eres
a danger to the platform Well
un peligro para la plataforma Bueno
better one less scourge [ __ ] it's good it's
mejor una lacra menos [__] está bien
bad limited listen it doesn't matter The
está mal limitado escucha da igual La
Movida you're on YouTube where they
Movida estás en YouTube que donde te
throw you the members By the way the other
tiran la los miembros Por cierto el otro
day you can choose the price of the
día puede elegir el precio de los
members This is cool and twit should
miembros Esto está Guay y twit debería
implement it but I didn't know that
implementarlo pero no sabía que eso se
could be done the thing Ricky you tudor
podía hacer la cosa Ricky tú tudor te
thought it was terrible right yes you think it's terrible
pareció fatal verdad sí te parece fatal
No yes What do you think about Ray's
No sí Qué te parece lo de Ray de las
dagger And the shots What do you think if
puñal Y los tiros Qué te parece tal si
you start If you start
te pones Si te pones a
criticizing you do a
criticar haces una
PR It's that you ask me a question and you don't
PR Es que me haces una pregunta y no me
let me answer you because you're such a
dejas que te conteste porque eres tan
cowardly resp But if you start talking
cobarde resp Pero si te pones a hablar
every time I'm going to answer you, that
cada vez que te voy a responder a mí que
you defend your girlfriend I told you the
tú defiendas a tu novia te lo dije el
other day it seems [ __ ] great to me what I don't
otro día me parece [__] madre lo que no
see the logic  is that you start criticizing
veo lógica es que te pongas a criticar
when others say they're going to send you
cuando otros dicen que te van a mandar
friends and then you do it Javi I have
amigos y luego tú lo hagas Javi te tengo
to ask you man, you As a man I
que preguntar tío a ti Como hombre te
'm considering you a man, right if I
estoy considerando un hombre aécio si yo
tell you I'm going to shoot you twice
te digo voy a pegarte dos
Javi No, what do I call you if it's not
tiros Javi No cómo te llamo si no es
Javi No, I don't consider you a
Javi No que yo a ti no te considero un
man, you're a baby Ah but what you
hombre eres un bebé Ah pero lo que tú
think doesn't matter you're the last [ __ ]
opines da igual eres la última [__]
Javi you're the dog of the community Okay
Javi eres el perro de la comunidad Vale
now
ahora
when [ __ ] man can I talk or not
cuando [__] tío puedo hablar o no en
seriously man, yeah I tell you eh it would be
serio tío va sio a ti te digo eh sería
super easy to stab you twice, shoot you Does it
superfácil pegarte dos puñaladas tiros
seem just as serious to you, I'm asking you
te parece igual de grave te lo pregunto
eh, be careful with the answer because she's going to
eh cuidado la respuesta que te lo va a
see it t But why don't you answer about
ver t Pero por qué no contestas a lo de
Tudor? No no no no yes yes yes I'm going to
tudor no no no no sí sí si voy a
mention it now, does it seem just as
mencionarlo ahora te parece igual de
serious to you that I tell a person I have
grave que yo le diga a una persona tengo
contacts they make sure that my girlfriend goes out to
contactos aseguran de que mi novia salga
party quietly Does it seem just as
de fiesta tranquila Te parece igual de
serious to you, one is more direct and another is
grave una es Más directa y otra es
veiled? No no no, it seems more serious or no,
velada no no no te parece más grave o no
Ricky, one is more direct and another is V, do
Ricky una es Más directa y otra es V te
the ideas seem more serious to you?  in stard or what
parecen más grav las deas en stard o lo
I told your man the ideas in
que yo le dije a tuor hombre las deas en
stard of course but yours too ideas
stard por supuesto pero las tuyas
in you said that it turned you on
también deas en dijiste que te puso
Javi I'm going to put what I
cachondo Javi te voy a poner lo que yo
said actually that video okay Go for
dije en realidad ese vídeo vale Dale
it come on put it but in the space it can't be
caña venga ponlo pero en el space no se
heard no no but I'll see it
escucha no no pero te lo vo en el
live YouTube okay On what channel are you
directo YouTube vale En qué canal está
doing live at the salsera until they
haciendo directo en la salsería hasta
close it let's go there come on put your
cierren vamos para allá venga pon tu
reaction put your reaction
reacción pon tu reacción
so it can be seen Put the click so it can be seen
que se te vea Pon el clic que se vea
okay it's a video that will haunt you
vale es un vídeo que le va a perseguir
eh For life it's a video that will
eh De por vida es un vídeo que le va a
haunt you For life in your career, I mean yes yes
perseguir Ya de por vida en su carrera o
you are a
sea si si tú eres una
person who is kind of frowned upon because of the
persona que está medio mal vista por la
[ __ ] that people are throwing at you Well,
[__] que te está tirando la gente Pues
I don't think the best strategy is to
no creo yo que la mejor estrategia sea
make a video like that you
hacer un vídeo así
understand me the best strategy was
me entendéis la mejor estrategia era
how it was in 2019 and
como iba en 2019 y
2020 in 2029 or in
2020 en 2029 o en
2019 in 2019 what I thought of the video eh
2019 en 2019 lo que opiné del vídeo eh
but the part that it turns you on
pero la parte de que te pone cachón no
you didn't skip it  Ah what I thought doesn't
te la has saltado Ah lo que opiné no te
interest you but I understand as a
interesa pero es que entiendo como
human person that you think like that I
persona humana que eres que opines así
took this for granted that I
yo esto lo daba por hecho que también lo
had also mentioned it at some point of
había mencionado algún momento por
course But you are the only Shameless one
supuesto Pero eres el único Sinvergüenza
who said clown est you
que dijo payaso est
were
estabas
lying lying clown You are a
mintiendo payaso mentiroso Eres un
liar est I know Of course in everything in the
mentiroso est Yo sé Claro en todo en
entire live there is a specific moment
todo el directo hay un momento puntual
where I grab and say host it turns us on
donde yo cojo y digo [__] nos pone
Hearing insults and these things
cachondo Escuchar insultos y estas cosas
Of course just as no what d says is not
Claro igual que no lo que dice d no es
horny it is not an insult in
cachón no es insulto en
general but my op people are going to achieve
general pero mi op gente va conseguir la
immortality
inmortalidad
op have seen the people saying that p Of course of
op ha visto la peña diciendo que p Claro
course and yes and I can cut out a lot
claro y si y yo puedo recortar un montón
of clips of yours clown and change the
de Clip tuyo payaso y le cambio el
meaning this clip goes is Followed what
sentido este clip va es Seguido lo que
happens has no cte this this is my opinion
pas no tiene cte este este es mi opinión
But what jav that I hoped that you had
Pero que jav que yo esto esperaba que lo
done it at some point and I think it's
hubieras hecho en algún momento y me
great I took this for granted
parece genial yo esto lo daba por hecho
I already counted on that you had
yo ya contaba con que esto lo había
said this at some point of course
dicho en algún momento por supuesto
now that doesn't mean that it seemed to you that
ahora eso no quita que te pareciera que
what he said turned you on It is a
te ponía cachondo lo que dijo Es un
joking comment of little man
comentario de cachondeo de poco hombre
are you  That you turn on with your
eres tú Que te pones a cachondo con las
own hands the people who don't trust
propias manos a la gente que no confía
your fun projects cach
en sus proyectos de cachondeo cach
dance on the [ __ ] grave at their funeral
bailar en la [__] tumba en su funeral de
horny H I gave it
cachón H lo di
as a joke in my comment no And if they
de cachondeo en mi comentario no Y si te
tell it to you if they tell it to you or
lo dicen a ti si te lo dicen a ti o
one of yours how do you laugh at
alguno de los tuyos qué cachondeo te
those comments boss Well that's it
toma esos comentarios jefe Pues eso pues
Ricky I'll repeat it to you again as a
Ricky te lo vuelvo a repetir de
joke it's my comment Tom Ricky and
cachondeo es mi comentario Tom Ricky y
yes and if they tell you that they're going to
si y si te dicen a ti que te van a
send you some friends how do you take it
mandar unos amiguitos como te lo tomas
I
yo
report well with daras you reported a
denuncio bueno con daras denunciaste al
year when you [ __ ] on the
año cuando te cagaste en el
debate what when he reported her when he
debate qué cuando la denunció cuando me
publicly called me an abuser Javi
llamó maltratador públicamente Javi
then the threats didn't affect you yes
entonces las amenazas no te afectaron sí
the police added them because they asked me for a
las añadió la policía porque me pidieron
complete history of my relationship with
historial completo de mi relación con
that profile I showed him the threat and they
ese perfil le enseñé la amenaza y me
told me you have to request a restraining order
dijeron tienes que solicitar una orden
rique but when he threatened you you didn't
rique pero cuando te amenazó no
report
denunciaste
we're not he told me that I'm going to send
estamos que no me dijo que me I a mandar
some friends Well but according to you you
unos amiguitos Bueno pero según tú
requested a restraining order And all
pediste una orden de alejamiento Y todo
because you were very I requested it to
porque estabas muy la solicité a
police request Yes yes I requested it Yes yes
petición policial Sí sí la solicité Sí
but in a year we're going to turn you on
sí pero al año vamos que te pone cachón
that too or what Where are you going?
eso también o qué A dónde quieres llegar
No, you make up a complaint you
no a que te inventas una denuncia te
make up a restraining order and and and
inventas una orden de alejamiento y y y
you
te
start you start calling
pones te pones a te pones a poner de
others liars I make it
mentirosos a los demás poner me invento
all up come on [ __ ] what a drag dude very
todo no venga [__] qué pereza tío muy
soft Ho Ha I have to
flojito Ho Ja tengo que
say if you want I'll start being like you
decir si quieres me pongo a ser como tú
insults nerves talking above
insultos nervios hablar por encima la
age no if the volume thing here the good thing you
edad no si lo del volumen aquí lo bueno
can't change it dude if not you would have already
no lo puedes cambiar tío si no ya lo
done it [ __ ] sun the volume the
hubieras hecho cabrón sol el volumen el
volume is low I'm getting
volumen lo tengo bajo yo que se me está
lower by itself I don't know why Look, I'm
bajando solo no sé por qué Mira voy
talking and it's getting lower I hear you
hablando y se va bajando te escucho
overwhelmed turning up all the time how
agobiado subiendo todo el rato cómo te
worried you are when it's yours that can't be
preocupa cuando es el tuyo que no se
heard loud which by the way I'm
escucha fuerte que por cierto te estoy
listening to you great the whole time I
escuchando de [__] madre todo el rato yo
don't touch mine at any time because
no toca al mío en ningún momento porque
anyway I think it can be heard well and even
en fin creo que se escucha bien y hasta
and if not people will say it but it's very
y si no la peña lo dirá pero es muy
desirable that You did that to crypto
desable que Que le hicieras eso a cripto
dude it's almost 3:15 What what what
tío son casi son las 3:15 El qué el qué
what Sorry what AC crypto bru that you
el qué Perdona el qué AC crpto bru que
sent him you lowered the volume that I
le mandaste le bajaste el volumen que yo
lowered the volume [ __ ] Javi man another
le bajé el volumen [__] Javi tío otro
topic please is that on top of that we are
tema por favor es que encima estamos
bringing Celia crypto c here that of turning
metiendo aquí a Celia cripto c ese de
down the volume M is that I don't know
que le baja el volumen M es que yo no sé
what problem you have every time with a
qué problema tenéis cada vez con un
debate that the volume but also the
debate que el volumen pero también el
volume low di said r said the other
volumen bajito di dijo r dijo el otro
day that I didn't turn down the volume
día que yo no le bajé el volumen
Okay but anyways let's see
Bueno pero de todas maneras vamos a ver
the other day the debate that you are
el otro día el debate que me estás
mentioning to me with CR that is coming that I
mencionando con CR que viene que yo me
wanted to leave Haha what I am it's your
quería ir Ja que estoy es que son tus
lies that you are telling lies what you
mentiras que vas soltando mentiras lo
have said I combed it for you Tito What a
que has dicho te lo he peinado Tito Qué
lie you haven't combed anything Ricky tomorrow
mentira no has peinado nada Ricky mañana
when you see yourself you will obsess over me you will
cuando te veas te obsesionar conmigo
start with age you will start with The
empezarás con la edad empezarás con El
bowl and you will start to mess with women
cuenco y empezarás a meterte con mujeres
because that is what you do with women with
porque es lo que haces con mujeres con
the
los
only ones is with with the only thing you have
únicos es con con lo único que tienes
balls with women Oh and with dala
[__] tú con las mujeres Ah y con dala
what's going on that I dedicated two videos to him
qué pasa que le dedicado dos videítos
these days with d but it was if I have
estos días con d pero fue si tengo aquí
a clip of you here saying that you were scared
un clip tuyo diciendo que te daba miedo
yes it doesn't have  the one who challenged him to the debate
sí no tiene el que le Reto al debate el
what the one who challenged him to the debate doesn't have it
qué el que le Reto al debate no lo tiene
and the long ones he gives me you don't have that
y las largas que me da eso no lo tienes
no how is the owner he won't let you
no como es el dueño no te deja que
show that The what what won't let me
enseñes eso El qué el qué no me deja que
teach myself Tell me when I offer the
me enseñe Cuéntame cuando ofrezco el
debate and I change from the four he won't
debate y me cambio del cuatro no me
change from twenty something to four from
cambia del vein pico al cuatro del
four to five from five to six for the
cuatro al cinco del cinco al seis por el
study Hey one thing Before you
estudio el Oye una cosa Antes de que te
go with another lie because no it's not
vayas con otra mentira más porque no no
the same answer it's the same it's the
es el mismo respond es el mismo es el
same the one who loves you the one who loves you and
mismo el que te qui el que te quieres y
you now you take it out on me again the one who
tú ahora me lo sacas otra vez el que te
loves you and you where the girl where the
quieres y tú dónde la chavala dónde la
girl said that I laughed that When
chavala dicho que me reí eso Cuándo
where is this girl that you say eh
dónde la chavala esta que tú dices eh
that she said she made it up Where does she say she
que dijo que se lo inventó Dónde dice
made it up this girl that you
que se lo inventó la chavala esta que tú
said no no she told me later that she
has dicho no no me dijo luego que se
got heated and that she had made it up for me
calentó y que se la había inventado a mí
for md my private conversations with
por md mis conversaciones privadas con
her can you put it on me no no she doesn't
ella me la puedes poner no no ella no
want those things to be seen she lets you
quiere que se vean esas cosas te te deja
put on her conversations with
poner las conversaciones de ella con
Dalas  and yours with her from the other day except for
Dalas y tuya con ella del otro día menos
that part if you want no And if you want
esa parte si quieres no Y si quieres
ask her surely if you ask her
pregúntale seguramente si se lo pides tú
if she will pass them but she doesn't want them to
si las pasará pero no quiere que lo
broadcast it I mean she didn't want them to be seen in
emita O sea no quería que se vieran en
public I can't pass them
público yo no las puedo pasar
dude about his thing talk about his thing
tío de su movida habla de su movida
Sorry the other day you put all her
Perdona el otro día pusiste todas las
conversations with Amanda and this
conversaciones de ella con Amanda y
thing that you mentioned before at the
conasa esta que has mencionado antes al
end what There it stayed you didn't threaten
final qué Ahí se quedó no la amenazaste
her we've all seen her what's what
la hemos visto todos qu es lo que te lo
nobody saw you removed the screenshot
ha visto nadie quit quado la captura
running dude someone else must have told you on
corriendo tío te lo habrá dicho otro por
WhatsApp remove it remove it this kid
WhatsApp quítala quítala que esta chaval
finally messed up with me what r we've
al final la lió conmigo el qué r hemos
all seen here that you
visto aquí todo el mundo que la
threatened her and that I was right in the
amenazaste y que tuve razón en la
exclusive I gave the other day that you
exclusiva que di el otro día que te
wanted to take three girls from
querías llevar a tres chavalas p
Andorra but it's more it's more Well, to this, to this,
andorras pero es más es más Bueno a esto
to this you're not going to answer This
a esto a esto no vas a contestar Está
older people are failing their medication she's
mayor gente le falla la medicación está
saying
diciendo
things like noos she was going to get on three girl
cosas cu noos se iba a subir a tres tía
and tomorrow she'll make up that see the one who
y mañana se inventar que ve la qui
is m I don't care and she tells me I've
sea m me da igual se y me dice te he
denied all this no  I denied it, you
desmentido todo esto no te desmentido me
changed the subject and now you said
has cambiado el tema y ahora has dicho
that you did it, you liar, you [ __ ]
que lo haces mentido mentiroso [__]
liar, you have 40 blocks. Major Major, I don't know what the [ __ ] you ca
falso tienes 40 paros Mayor Mayor no sé
n't show me where
que cuo que no me puedes enseñar dónde
she told you that she made it up because in
ella te dijo que lo inventó porque en
public she didn't say that she made it up, she said
público no dijo que se lo inventó dijo
something else. Oh yes, she said in public that
otra cosa Ah sí queé dijo en público que
the only culprit was her boyfriend, that he didn't, that was one
el culpable solo era al novio que el no
of the things she said. It was
eso fue una de las cosas que dijo Es fue
one of the things she said. She also said
una de las cosas que dijo también dijo
that she had to apologize, just in case, as a
que se tenía que disculpar si acaso como
mom of mine and that she did it. Well, she didn't
mamand de convigo y que lo hizo bueno no
say that she did it, I told it, but she did
dijo que lo hizo lo conté yo pero sí se
apologize to us, eh. I say eh. Yes, you
disculpó con nosotros eh Ah digo eh Sí
have it in today's video or in
lo tienes en el vídeo de hoy o en el de
yesterday's, one of the two has it, it has my
ayer uno de los dos lo tiene tiene mi
chat with
chat con
her. Now it's there, the chat is in the
ella ahora sí está el chat está en el
video, I had completely forgotten, it's just that I
vídeo se me había olvidado por completo
thought, after that,
es que he pensado después de eso
we talked about things that she no longer wants to be
hablamos cosas que ya no quiere que sean
published because they are from her life, she
publicadas porque son de su vida me ha
asked me that she doesn't want to, she told you that she made it up, just in a moment of
pedido que no quiere te dijo que se lo
heat, that it was because of heat
inventó un calentón que fue por calentón
and that it wasn't true. Yes, her perception
y que no era verdad sí que su percepción
was that she was in charge, she spoke to her boyfriend and
era que manda le hablaba a su novio y
no, when he saw the
que no que cuando vio las conversaciones
band conversations he said okay, he's not fooling me, this
de banda dijo vale no me está engañando
[ __ ], like the
el cabrón este en plan las
real conversations are what
conversaciones reales son las que me ha
happened to me, he's confusing me, you're
pasado es que está liando me estás
confusing me with a lot of things, a lot of my
liando un montón de cosas mucho mi
relationship and this is fine with yours it's going
relación y esto está bien con la tuya va
well, damn it. Well, come on, you who have
bien la [__] Pues anda que tú que
spent your whole life
entonces que llevas toda tu vida
dedicated to the life of Dalas Then you
dedicada a la vida del Dalas Entonces es
're
que me estás
confusing me yeah it's there you're confusing me with a
liando sil está ahí me estás liando un
lot of things okay you're confusing me with a
montón de cosas vale me estás liando un
lot of things why are you interested in my
montón de cosas por qué te interesa mi
life with my partner what are you interested in this
vida con mi pareja qué te interesa esto
because you're lying but my relationship
porque estás mintiendo pero mi relación
let's say is more satisfactory than yours
digamos es más satisfactoria que la tuya
currently you're lying to me I
actualmente me estás mintiendo
ask Uy the one who is quiet is a jerk Javi be
pregunto Uy el que callado torga Javi
careful my relationship is more
cuidado mi relación de pareja es más
satisfactory and complete than yours
satisfactoria y completa que la tuya
currently I ask let's see they are
actualmente pregunto a ver me están
telling me they are telling me that Amanda
diciendo me están diciendo que Amanda
starts talking to him in 2021 that you
empieza a hablarle en el 2021 que tú
start with her in 2022 they are
empiezas con ella en el 2022 te están
telling you it's made up well what
diciendo inventado pues lo que te dice a
people tell you is true no Javi come on
ti la gente es verdad no Javi venga por
please no no This is what he said
favor no no Esto es lo que ha dicho
saying this is what he said ch Where
diendo esto es lo que ha dicho ch Dónde
where did the girl say that girl let's
dónde ha dicho eso la chica la chica
go to Vera pass it to me where did she say that let's
vamos a Vera pásamelo dónde ha dicho eso
go Ricky let's see you said it
vamos Ricky vamos a ver lo has dicho tú
Here Ricky calm down calm
Aquí Ricky tranquil tranquilízate
down Ricky think about what you're going to talk about he's
tranquilízate Ricky piensa lo que vas a
overwhelmed
hablar está agob perdido Ricky si me
lost Ricky if I got caught think about what you're going to talk about come on the conversations are easier nothing more than bricks the conversations your girlfriend starts with the Chinese guy in 2022 no or in 2021 the Chinese guy who talks no the conversations the boy starts with her answering a story in 2021
ella respondiendo una historia en 2021
okay But why do you make things up Avis I've explained it to you
vale Pero por qué inventas Avis te lo he
dude it's that you're very false a very
explicado tío es que eres muy falso muy
liar according to this girl's twis
mentiroso según los twis de esta chica
they're talking until recently no yes yes that's what
están hablando hasta hace poco no sí sí
the girl says and then she
eso es lo que dice la chica y luego los
deletes them and apologizes where but she
borra y se disculpa dónde pero se
apologizes saying that she made it up
disculpa diciendo que se la ha inventado
or that it was all her boyfriend's fault just no
o que todo era culpa del novio solo no
that it's the same Javi it's the same
que es lo mismo Javi es lo mismo se lo
she made it up because her boyfriend
ha inventado ella porque su novio le ha
told her that it was Amanda who started
contado que era Amanda la que le empezó
talking to her then it's the same she says it she
hablar entonces es lo mismo lo dice ella
says both things look at my video It's
dice las dos cosas mírate mi vídeo Está
all damn  look at it Rick I have you here
todo [__] mírelo Rick te tengo aquí
talking about a subject Rick I have you here I don't care I don't care I don't care You
hablando de un tema Rick te tengo aquí
're not that relevant [ __ ] I don't care No, I'm not
eres tan relevante cabrón me da igual No
going to start the conversation
te no me voy a poner la conversación
girl because right now I might as well
chavala que ahora mismo ya igual
talk to you about things that I have
hablarte de cosas de vde que tengo
calm down because he's very nervous
tranquilate que que está muy nervioso
Ricky if you're nervous why did I
Ricky si estás tú nervioso de que te he
tell you that you're taking the horns that no
dicho que t m lleva la cornamenta que no
Ricky are you sure not my son
Ricky estás seguro que no hijo mío yo ya
at this point in life I'll
a estas altura de la vida pella luego le
give him the explanation later okay okay Ricky Ricky The
da la explic vale vale Ricky Ricky La
girl says that she made it up where does she
chica dice que se lo inventó dónde lo
say it I'm just asking you that not
dice te estoy preguntando solo eso no el
yesterday's video or today's I already uploaded two
vídeo de ayer o el de hoy Ja subido dos
parts and I recorded them all in one in a
partes y las grabé todas en uno en un
live Damn You were watching the Bot
directo [__] Te estuviste viendo el Bot
in the Bot that was I was showing the
en el Bot ese estaba yo enseñaba los
complete chats and in fact Teo you didn't
chat completos y de hecho Teo no has
say that you don't see my content if you see it or
dicho que no ves mi contenido si lo ve o
not I saw the Twitter clip
no lo vees he visto el clip de Twitter
in which he reacts and he makes it big
en el que reacciona y te hace grande
so that you can't see the viral eye that
para que no se vea el ojo virul que
Dalas has man that's the clip that I saw
tiene Dalas tío ese el clip que he visto
and I say Look, he's reacting to this video
y digo Mira está reaccionando este vídeo
this B By the way okay eh Where does
a este B Por cierto vale eh Dónde dice
the girl say that she made it up show it to me
la chica que se ha inventado enséñamelo
isn't it like much more embarrassing that you
no es como mucho más vergonzoso que te
make yourself big to cover Dala's eye
haga grande para taparle el ojo a dala
than simply admitting that you're cross-eyed
que simplemente reconocer que está bisco
isn't much more embarrassing that didn't
no es mucho más vergonzoso eso no te
seem like a very [ __ ] [ __ ] to you what a pain
pareció como muy de [__] qué putada
Ricky Where does the girl say that she
Ricky En dónde dice la chavala que se le
made it up I mean the fact that she
ha inventado me refiero el hecho de que
has one eye on each side after having
tiene un ojo para cada lado después de
surgery is a fact that at
operarse es un hecho que mínimo que su
least her dog doesn't cover it up it's that you
perro por lo menos no lo tape es que te
get big uncle Ricky Where does that
haces grande tío Ricky En dónde dice la
girl say that she made it up that she's
chavala esa que se la ha inventado que
horny she made it up where does it
es ha calentada se la ha inventado dónde
say with me in the conversations
lo dice conmigo en las conversaciones
with me my video from yesterday and today remove
conmigo mi vídeo de ayer y de hoy quitas
the abl so that the ads jump and I
el abl que me salten los anuncios y lo
monetize it to see tomorrow but At what
monetizó para mañana ver pero En qué
minute
minuto
Ricky at what moment What minute did you throw
Ricky en qué momento Qué minuto tiraste
the rod my that subject went to trial Javi
la caña mi ese tema fue a juicio Javi
that you don't answer but what minute am I going
que no contestas pero qué minuto te voy
to tell you crazy [ __ ] What I don't know what
a decir [__] loco Qué yo que sé qué
minute the video lasts 40 minutes I don't
minuto dura 40 minutos el vídeo yo que
know what minute [ __ ] Let's see tell me one
sé qué minuto cabrón A ver dime una
word and we look for it is that it is not written
palabra y lo buscamos es que eso no lo
here r I look for it for you Ricky fav
pone aquí r te lo busco Ricky fav
Look for it Look for it Look for it Yes yes Hala Hala
Búscalo Búscalo Búscalo Sí sí Hala Hala
I wanted to leave and this crazy guy the old man
yo quería irme y el loco este el viejo
has me Here stuck but because
me tiene Aquí metido pero por porque
all your answers are the old man the crazy
todas tus respuestas son el viejo el
guy I don't know you Does it bother you Does it
loco no sé te Te molesta Te
bother you the
molesta la
girl exploded the girl explodes now
chica explotó la chica explota ahora
because the TR dog well I won't say it I won't say
porque le TR perro pues no lo diré no
what about the Had I apologize for what about
diré lo de la Had me disculpo por lo de
the Had Sorry I won't say it anymore if it
la Had Perdón ya no lo digo más si te
bothers you I won't say it but what are you
pica no lo digo pero qué es lo que estás
talking about Ricky now is that I don't
hablando Ricky ahora es que no lo estoy
understand what you told me I don't know what
entendiendo que me has dicho no sé qué
About age okay It touches your dick the
Ya de la edad vale Te toca la [__] la
age Well I won't tell you it's all the same
edad Pues no te la digo ya está da igual
I did it because I thought it was
yo lo hacía porque pensaba te hacía
funny to me it's not that I find it funny
gracia que a mí no es que me haga gracia
or not funny that you're making a
ni no me haga gracia que estás haciendo
fool of yourself it's that it's getting to me it's
el ridículo es que se te está que me
not good for you that I make a fool of myself it
corta no te viene bien que yo hag
bothers me it stings you that they
ridículo que me corta que te pica que te
call you old that you're already at an age to
digan viejo que ties ya una edad para
be doing other things damn of a
está haciendo otas cositas [__] de
person your age that's it but Ricky
persona de tu edad ya está pero Ricky
what's wrong with you  the age that you're going to
qué tienes con la edad que tú vas a
reach Soon and at 40
llegar Dentro de poco y a los 40 Dentro
Soon at 27 to strip damn yes Rick of course
de poco con 27 a tira [__] sí Rick claro
that's life the good thing is that at 40 I won't
eso es la vida lo bueno que yo con 40 no
get there with a strap jav balls you
llegaré con una Correa jav los [__]
already have two straps one from Ali and
ya tienes dos correas una de la Ali y
another from Amanda let's see the guy's girlfriend
otra de la Amanda a ver la novia del
the guy's girlfriend got
chaval la novia del chaval se puso
jealous because Amanda and the tiktoker
celosa porque Amanda y el tiktoker
were still talking to
seguían hablando hasta el día de
this day Show me that screenshot I love that screenshot I have
hoy Enséñame esa captura ame esa captura
them so it can be seen that Amanda the tiktoker
las tengo se vea que Amanda el tiktoker
is talking show it to me come on show it to me come on we're
hablan échamela venga échamela venga te
going to show it to you and you answer me okay I'm going to show you I'm
la vamos a poner y tú me contestas vale
going to show you the
Te voy a poner Voy a poner pas la
screenshot where Amanda and the guy are talking I'm
captura la que Amanda y el chico hablan
even going to show you what she said okay
hasta voy a poner lo que dijo ella vale
No no no the screenshot you just admitted
No no no la captura acabas de admitir
that Amanda and that guy were talking this
que Amanda y ese chaval hablaban este
year come on guys Excuse me, I'm going to butt in for
año venga venga eh chicos Disculpa que
a moment eh Ricky from your video
me meto un momento eh Ricky de tu video
called they cheated on me
que se llama me han puesto los cuernos
again not at minute 921 where you
otra vez no en el minuto 921 donde
show the screenshot in the part where it
muestras la captura en en la parte donde
says well read read  if you want it to be felt
dice bueno lea lea si quiere que se ent
that you don't feel like looking for him, he reads it,
que no tiene ganas de buscarlo él leela
reads it well in the capture he says eh what you
leela bueno en la captura dice eh lo que
show you no The girl says and he had
muesas tú no La chica dice e él había
deleted what what he put to you from the first
borrado lo que lo que te puso del primer
message of his chat Well of course Give it
mensaje de su chat Bueno claro Dale
context jabi this her talking to
contexo jabi esto ella hablando con
Amanda okay this is your girl
Amanda vale esto es la chica del tuy
talking to Amanda well no I suppose so
hablando con Amanda bueno no Supongo que
no and then she says son of a [ __ ] he's not
sí no e después dice hijo de [__] no es
smart or anything after that well I suppose it
listo ni nada después bueno Supongo que
's Amanda not the one who answers Yes
es Amanda no la que la que responde Sí
she talking to Amanda and says no ready
ella hablando con Amanda y dice no listo
nothing about her boyfriend that he deleted the messages
nada de su novio que borró los mensajes
to appear that I think it's more I
para aparecer que yo creo que es más yo
think above that we don't have any
creo que más arriba de eso no tenemos
more conversation and that's from 2021 What
más conversación y eso es de 2021 What
the [ __ ] what does it matter is that I haven't talked
the fuck qué más da es que no he hablado
to him at all eh that the chat that
con él nada más eh que el chat que te ha
literally happened to you and below it says the
pasado literalmente y más abajo dice la
other girl not that one kushi let's see let's see I
otra chica no esa tal kushi a ver a a
care because although I haven't
ver a mí me importa porque aunque no lo
paid for it Although I have paid for it with you I'm
he pagado Aunque lo he pagado contigo lo
sorry for that he has done it to me with many
siento por eso me lo ha hecho con muchas
other popular and famous bullets take I don't
otras balas populares y famosas toma no
know if there will be another other I'm going to
sé si habrá otro otro voy a
look for this entire conversation dude I
buscar está conversación entera tío O
mean you're me  saying that she only
sea me estás diciendo que ella solamente
shows you the conversation when they
te enseña la conversación cuando
start talking in 2021 and jumps to
empiezan a hablar en 2021 y salta en
2024 Javi Javi not to me Javi not to me [ __ ] you
2024 Javi Javi a mí no Javi a mí no
're a note eh No The boy
[__] eres un notita eh No El chaval le
opens the story he answers a
abre la historia le responde una
story send 2021 Yes yes the girl
historia manda 2021 Sí sí la chavala
currently the girl has been with me for I think
actualmente la chavala lleva creo que
8 years The boy Lan many years
son 8 años con El chaval Lan muchos años
And currently she does admit it she looks at his
Y actualmente sí lo admite ella le mira
phone I take the boy's phone and sees
el móvil le cogo el móvil al chaval y ve
what girls he talks to he has been
con qué tías habla lleva
years Well I don't know how many he has been he has a
añ Pues no sé los que lleva lleva un
handful I know that in 2021 they were already that's what she
puñado sé que en 2021 ya estaban es lo
told me they have been together for 3 years I don't
que me dijo ella llevan 3 años no me no
know if they have been together for 3 years eh from things that
sé si llevan 3 años eh por cosas que me
she has told me about the relationship okay And
ha contado ella de la relación vale Y
where does she get that information about her from
dónde saca esa información de ella de
conversations between her and
conversaciones de ella con
Dallas okay okay And well that one has taken out
Dallas vale okay Y pues esa hab sacado
my video that I am the one who uploaded it
mi vídeo que soy yo el que la subió
[ __ ] I mean that
cabrón O sea que
you have not uploaded them that you have not uploaded the
te tú no las has sub que tú no las has
entire thing that I have not uploaded Javi that I have
subido entera que no he subido Javi que
not uploaded because What a liar you are,
no he subido porque Qué mentiroso eres
show what I have not  uploaded come on keep
enseña lo que no he subido venga sígueme
explaining come on keep explaining what you were
explicando venga sígueme explicando lo
going to tell me no no no no you have
que me ibas a decir no no no no me has
accused me of manipulating
acusado de haber manipulado
conversations that I have not uploaded come on Oh
conversaciones que no he subido venga Ay
Ricky how lazy man keep talking what you
Ricky qué pereza tío sigue hablando lo
were going to say man don't interrupt yourself
que ibas a decir tío no te interrumpas
man what a [ __ ] ghost man I hope it's not like that
tío qué [__] fantasmón tío Espero que no
in your personal life the girl
sea así en tu vida personal la chavala
well and you in your personal life like that that's why they keep cheating on you I
bueno y tú en tu vida personal así eres
mean the girl finds
cuernos O sea la chavala se encuentra
what she thinks about what itches her head
qué opina de lo que le pica la cabeza
ricki what I didn't invent it doesn't matter the
ricki lo que no inventé da igual la
girl finds a conversation the
chavala se encuentra una conversación
same from 2021 she
igual de 2021
messes it up now and starts funning on
la lía ahora y empieza a funar en
Twitter now the girls start
Twitter ahora las chavalas se pone a
looking at conversations that the guy has
mirar conversaciones que tiene el chaval
with his girlfriend with with his with girl with whom he
con novia con con su con chica con las
wants to go out or the ones he hits on
que quiere salir o las que le tira la
Javi I don't know if that guy has
caña Javi yo no sé si ese chaval le ha
opened up to my girlfriend again this year if he
vuelto a abrir a mi novia este año si
was a jerk if he was a slob How do I
era un tira caña si era un guarro Yo qué
know if I've written to her again I mean
sé si le ha vuelto a escribir yo o sea
you're telling me that you care more about
tú me estás diciendo que te importa más
this than the girl the girl  this one goes out to
esto que la chica la chica esta sale a
denounce her boyfriend and your girlfriend in
funar a su novio y a tu novia en
2024 I'm 40 years old Ricky we already
2024 que tengo 40 años Ricky que ya lo
know it's all an argument cate keeps
sabemos que es todo argumento cate sigue
talking about keeps saying nonsense this is
hablando de sigue diciendo tontería está
the turkey he's more aware of this he's
el pavo está más pendiente de esto está
more aware of this than I know
más pendiente de esto que de yo que sé
The tumor that seems to me to be something serious and
El tumor que me parece algo serio y
grave that most likely being a
grave que muy probablemente siendo
colleague of theirs inform know you have
colega de ellos inform saber te has
also laughed at the Tum not been able to
reído también del Tum no sido capaz de
prove that I have laughed because I have not
probar que me he reído porque no me he
laughed has not been able to prove it
reído no ha sido capaz de demostrarlo
Javi you are lying again I am not laughing
Javi estás mintiendo otra vez no me río
Li's tumor In fact I have been more of a
El tumor de Li De hecho he sido más
man than adas saying that I hope it
hombre que adas diciendo que ojalá se me
gets better soon and I have made a very
jore pronto y he hecho un extracto
long extract of I hope and the girl gets out of
larguísimo de Ojalá y la tía salga de
that [ __ ] as soon as possible Oh what r if
esa [__] lo antes posible Ay qué r si
that girl How little if that girl
esa chavala Qué poco si esa chavala se
was getting pissed off and your girlfriend hadn't
estaba cabreando y tu novia no había
said anything why does that girl tell
dicho nada por qué esa chavala le dice a
Dallas I thought that the boss was buec
Dallas yo me creía que la manda era buec
but don't see how she
pero no vea cómo se las
handles it but look at my video that
gasta pero que te mires mi vídeo que se
explains all that chat I show it Javi I
explica todo ese chat lo enseño yo Javi
show that chat  I put that message
ese chat lo enseño yo ese mensaje lo
from her with Dallas I put it and I
pongo yo de ella con dala lo pongo yo y
comment on it and then she's apologizing
lo comento y ella luego disculpándose
to Amanda for having said that
con Amanda por haberle dicho eso ella
herself man look at today's video This
misma tío mira en el vídeo de hoy Esto
if I remember it's not the minute in
si me acuerdo no es el minuto en el
today's video there is a moment of an audio
vídeo de hoy hay un momento de un audio
of that girl in which she says if there is any
de esa chica en el que dice si hay algún
deleted message from the chat that I sent you with
mensaje borrado del chat que te pasé con
Dallas is putting [ __ ] on her or insulting
Dallas es metiéndole [__] o insultando
Amanda because how was it going to happen to
a Amanda porque como se le iba a pasar a
her I didn't want her to get mad at me and she
ella no quería que se enfadas conmigo y
sends me a screenshot of the messages it was not
me pasa capturado los mensajes no era
messing with her but if your
metiéndose con ella pero que si tu
truth is different Javi you tell what you
verdad es otra Javi tú cuenta lo que tú
want we
quieras
know what I think what I think
sabemos lo que creo lo que creo
clearly is that you ran
claramente es que cogiste corriendo
before everyone started the
antes de que todo el mundo se hiciera el
fire Well you ran the ament
fuego Pues fuiste corriendo la ament
while I was sleeping I started texting
mientras dormía me puse a mandarle onda
the girl so you delete something or what
a la niña para que borras cosa o qué
Ricky to put out the fire again like you
Ricky para apagar el fuego otra vez como
did when you made up the
hiciste cuando te inventaste la
rape that caught you eler debate I
violación que te trinc eler debate
made up the rape man really your
inventé la violación tío de verdad tu
people listen to you say these things and
gente te escucha decir estas cosas y te
look at you with respect in the face Yeah it's a lie
mira con respeto a la cara Ja es mentira
that you made up Ali's rape
que te inventaste tú la violación de Ali
is a lie  that I made up the rape
es mentira que me invento la violación
completely lie the [ __ ] crazy guy the
completamente mentira el [__] loco el
other day the audio was on live and you saw
otro día el audio en el directo y se vio
how he
como le dijo como le dije ni de coña se
told him like I told him don't even think about it for something like that it would be so serious what they would say to you and what they used to me what do you do Don't even think about it Cos like that we hear it again Dallas put it to you in the debate
puso el Dallas en el debate lo
we hear it again oh again how
escuchamos otra vez ay otra vez qué
lazy again it wasn't you it didn't come from
pereza otra vez no fuiste tú no salió de
you the rape you you no I don't know about me You
ti la violación tú te no no seo de mí Tú
get along with liy yes Well ask her
te llevas bien con liy sí Pues pídele
permission to put the audio come on
permiso para que ponga el audio venga
ask her And why didn't she want that
pídeselo Y eso para qué no quería todo
everyone listens to the audio to say that it does
el mundo escucha el audio que decir que
n't exist I have it And if she gives you
no existe existe lo tengo Y si te da
permission I'll put it on you change the subject from the
permiso lo pong mí cambias de tema del
subject of rape he's talking about
tema de la violación está hablando de
putting audio he's going to put one that I
poner audio me va a poner uno que me
put on the other day the crazy guy three times well why the [ __ ] do we
puse el otro día el loco tres veces pues
put a new one on It's not that
para qué [__] ponemos uno nuevo No es
no I'm not understanding you your change
que no no te estoy entendiendo tu cambio
of subject dude it's normal when you get hit in
de tema tío es normal cuando te dan en
the mouth normal that you get stunned it
la boquita normal que te quedes atontado
's not the first time that happens to you No
no es la primera vez que te pasa No pasa
nothing happens you no you don't give your little mouth to
nada tú no tú no das a la boquita a
anyone Look Listen to this
nadie Mira Escucha esto que esto lo
you say this okay look Lali what she's doing is
dices tú vale mira Lali lo que hace es
recognizing you people what the subject that was
reconocerte gente lo que el tema que le
missing she brought up my ex is there come on what
faltaba ha sacado a mi ex ya está venga
you were missing already Jai you just
el que te faltaba ya Jai es que acabas
denied it again you just
de volverlo a negar acabas de volverlo a
denied it again but it's that you just brought up
negar pero es que acabas de sacar todo
the whole subject how lazy with which I didn't
el tema qué pereza con la que no me la
make it up if I had made it up let her
inventé si me la hubiera inventado que
report me damn for that for the m for
me denuncie [__] por eso por el m por lo
whatever she wants dude let her report me for
que quiera killo que me denuncie de
real let her do it she's within her [ __ ]
verdad que lo haga está en su [__]
right I know she's not going to do it because I already
derecho sé que no lo va a hacer porque
talked to her about this I already talked to
ya habl con ella de esto ya hablé con
her about this and she already explained the
ella de esto y ya me explicó la
situation to me the one who was what she wanted already ha but
situación la que estaba lo que quería ya
please what the f but admit
ha peroo por favor qué p pero reconoce
admit that she cheats on you and
reconoce que ella te pone los cuernos y
you [ __ ] And you say no well that was
tú coges Y dices no pues eso ha sido una
rape No she tells me that
violación No ella me dice que han
she was abused Javi No she doesn't tell you that
abusado de ella Javi No ella no te dice
she tells you that she was drugged yes there
eso ella te dice que estaba drogad s que
was yes there was penetration she was
ha habido s que ha habido penetración
high  and I don't remember anything
iba drogadisimo y no me acuerdo de nada
for you what is that what happened to your wife to
para ti eso que es le pas a tu mujer a
you what is that What does that say let's see in the [ __ ]
ti eso qué Eso lo dice a ver en el [__]
let's
vamos a
listen to it inside because I don't know how to
escucharlo por dentro porque no sé cómo
fix this situation I don't know how to
arrar esta situación no sé cómo
react the first thing I do is
reaccionar lo primero que hago es
tell him that that was an abuse that if he
decirle que eso ha sido un abuso que si
really wasn't conscious or doesn't
ya realmente no estaba consciente o no
remember having given consent for
recuerda haber dado consentimientos para
his attention of the night is why are
que su atención de la noche sea por qué
you talking out loud you don't want
hablas Por lo alto no quieres que la
people to hear the
gente escuche el
click eh
click eh
Ricky Ricky
Ricky Ricky
has
se ha
left he has
pirado se ha
left he has left and they have closed the the the
pirado se ha pirado y han cerrado el el
space dude
el el space tío